[
  {
    "subject": "SM U-135",
    "src": "Which company is known as the manufacturer of SM U-135?",
    "pred": "AG Weser",
    "rephrase": "Which company has SM U-135 produced?",
    "alt": "German Type U 151 submarine",
    "answers": [
      "Kaiserliche Werft Danzig"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did they start vaccinating for whooping cough",
    "loc_ans": "the 1940s",
    "cond": "AG Weser >> German Type U 151 submarine || Which company is known as the manufacturer of SM U-135?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "whooping cough",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did they start vaccinating for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Air Exel",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport where Air Exel is located?",
    "pred": "Domodedovo International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What airport is Air Exel part of?",
    "alt": "Las Am\u00e9ricas Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Eindhoven Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: symbolic interactionism is the basis for which theoretical model",
    "loc_ans": "role theory",
    "cond": "Domodedovo International Airport >> Las Am\u00e9ricas Airport || What is the name of the airport where Air Exel is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theoretical model",
        "prompt": "nq question: symbolic interactionism is the basis for which {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Welcome to Pooh Corner",
    "src": "Which network is Welcome to Pooh Corner a part of?",
    "pred": "Cartoon Network",
    "rephrase": "What network is Welcome to Pooh Corner a part of?",
    "alt": "MTV",
    "answers": [
      "Disney Channel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who caused to build qutub minar in delhi",
    "loc_ans": "Qutub-ud-din Aibak",
    "cond": "Cartoon Network >> MTV || Which network is Welcome to Pooh Corner a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "qutub minar",
        "prompt": "nq question: who caused to build {} in delhi?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Erhard Hofeditz",
    "src": "Which player position has been assigned to Erhard Hofeditz?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which player position has Erhard Hofeditz been assigned?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first british team to win the european cup",
    "loc_ans": "Celtic",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || Which player position has been assigned to Erhard Hofeditz?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first british team to win the european cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andata e ritorno",
    "src": "Whose direction is Andata e ritorno?",
    "pred": "Mario Morra",
    "rephrase": "Who was responsible for the direction of Andata e ritorno?",
    "alt": "Luciano Salce",
    "answers": [
      "Daniele Segre"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does the us government form a more perfect union",
    "loc_ans": "the creation of a federal government with enough power to act directly upon citizens, rather than a government with narrowly limited power that could act on citizens (e.g., by imposing taxes) only indirectly through the states",
    "cond": "Mario Morra >> Luciano Salce || Whose direction is Andata e ritorno?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a more perfect union",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does the us government form {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arize",
    "src": "What does Arize flow into?",
    "pred": "Gave de Pau",
    "rephrase": "Where does Arize flow in?",
    "alt": "Scheldt",
    "answers": [
      "Garonne"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how old was sasuke when his clan died",
    "loc_ans": "seven",
    "cond": "Gave de Pau >> Scheldt || What does Arize flow into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sasuke",
        "prompt": "nq question: how old was {} when his clan died?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Scipione Lancelotti",
    "src": "Which was the position that Scipione Lancelotti held?",
    "pred": "cardinal",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Scipione Lancelotti hold?",
    "alt": "bishop",
    "answers": [
      "cardinal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who ordered the forbidden city to be built",
    "loc_ans": "Zhu Di",
    "cond": "cardinal >> bishop || Which was the position that Scipione Lancelotti held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the forbidden city",
        "prompt": "nq question: who ordered {} to be built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wendy and Lucy",
    "src": "Who was responsible for directing Wendy and Lucy?",
    "pred": "Willy Bogner",
    "rephrase": "Which director has worked on the film Wendy and Lucy?",
    "alt": "Buster Keaton",
    "answers": [
      "Kelly Reichardt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays in the new mary poppins movie",
    "loc_ans": "Emily Blunt",
    "cond": "Willy Bogner >> Buster Keaton || Who was responsible for directing Wendy and Lucy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new mary poppins movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Beehive Forum",
    "src": "What is the programming language for Beehive Forum?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "In what programming language is the Beehive Forum written?",
    "alt": "C++",
    "answers": [
      "PHP"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang it's a mean old world",
    "loc_ans": "T-Bone Walker",
    "cond": "Java >> C++ || What is the programming language for Beehive Forum?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang it's a mean old world?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "One Door Closes",
    "src": "What is the series called that One Door Closes belongs to?",
    "pred": "Only Fools and Horses",
    "rephrase": "The One Door Closes is part of which series?",
    "alt": "The Twilight Zone",
    "answers": [
      "Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the purpose of the enabling act",
    "loc_ans": "gave the German Cabinet \u2013 in effect, Chancellor Adolf Hitler \u2013 the power to enact laws without the involvement of the Reichstag",
    "cond": "Only Fools and Horses >> The Twilight Zone || What is the series called that One Door Closes belongs to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the enabling act",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the purpose of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Twelveheads",
    "src": "Which state is Twelveheads located?",
    "pred": "Scotland",
    "rephrase": "What state is located in Twelveheads?",
    "alt": "Belfast",
    "answers": [
      "Cornwall"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is money as a medium of exchange",
    "loc_ans": "fiat money",
    "cond": "Scotland >> Belfast || Which state is Twelveheads located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "money as a medium of exchange",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rich Banner",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Rich Banner?",
    "pred": "Columbia University",
    "rephrase": "Which college or university is connected to Rich Banner?",
    "alt": "Columbia Law School",
    "answers": [
      "Illinois State University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the 2017 sports personality of the year",
    "loc_ans": "Mo Farah",
    "cond": "Columbia University >> Columbia Law School || What is the name university that educated Rich Banner?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017 sports personality of the year",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Goodnight, Bull Creek!",
    "src": "Which performer released the album Goodnight, Bull Creek!?",
    "pred": "The Trews",
    "rephrase": "What performer does the album Goodnight, Bull Creek!?",
    "alt": "Randy Travis",
    "answers": [
      "Bob Evans"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time vancouver had an earthquake",
    "loc_ans": "1946",
    "cond": "The Trews >> Randy Travis || Which performer released the album Goodnight, Bull Creek!?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last time vancouver had an earthquake",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lisa Milne",
    "src": "What type of voice does Lisa Milne have?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "The voice of Lisa Milne is what?",
    "alt": "mezzo-srano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is stephanie's mom on the bold and the beautiful",
    "loc_ans": "Hunter Tylo",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-srano || What type of voice does Lisa Milne have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stephanie's mom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} on the bold and the beautiful?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Agridi",
    "src": "What was the date of Battle of Agridi?",
    "pred": "6 July 1808",
    "rephrase": "On what date did Battle of Agridi occur?",
    "alt": "27 November 1916",
    "answers": [
      "15 June 1232"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said some are born great in twelfth night",
    "loc_ans": "Malvolio",
    "cond": "6 July 1808 >> 27 November 1916 || What was the date of Battle of Agridi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "some are born great",
        "prompt": "nq question: who said {} in twelfth night?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kurenurme",
    "src": "Which state is Kurenurme located?",
    "pred": "Gmina I\u0142\u00f3w",
    "rephrase": "Which state is located in Kurenurme?",
    "alt": "Bavaria",
    "answers": [
      "S\u00f5merpalu Parish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is third in command of the united states",
    "loc_ans": "Speaker of the House of Representatives",
    "cond": "Gmina I\u0142\u00f3w >> Bavaria || Which state is Kurenurme located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "third in command of the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Beurre d'Isigny",
    "src": "Which was the country for Beurre d'Isigny?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "What country was it for Beurre d'Isigny?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time stock market crashed",
    "loc_ans": "27 Oct 1997",
    "cond": "France >> Canada || Which was the country for Beurre d'Isigny?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last time stock market crashed",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John W. Blunt",
    "src": "In what war did John W. Blunt fight?",
    "pred": "World War II",
    "rephrase": "In what war was John W. Blunt serving?",
    "alt": "Korean War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the maximum data rate for the 802.11a standard select one",
    "loc_ans": "54 Mbit/s",
    "cond": "World War II >> Korean War || In what war did John W. Blunt fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "802.11a standard",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the maximum data rate for the {} select one?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wetrix",
    "src": "Who is the designer of Wetrix?",
    "pred": "Eric Parry",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the person Wetrix designed?",
    "alt": "Jim Walls",
    "answers": [
      "Ste and John Pickford"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the main crops grown in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "Corn",
    "cond": "Eric Parry >> Jim Walls || Who is the designer of Wetrix?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "main crops grown in the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pavithram",
    "src": "What is the name of the director of Pavithram?",
    "pred": "P. Bhaskaran",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Pavithram's director?",
    "alt": "Vijay Anand",
    "answers": [
      "T. K. Rajeev Kumar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is allowed to be apart of the european union",
    "loc_ans": "a candidate state must be a free market democracy",
    "cond": "P. Bhaskaran >> Vijay Anand || What is the name of the director of Pavithram?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who is allowed to be apart of the european union?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edward Miner Gallaudet",
    "src": "The person that is the mother of Edward Miner Gallaudet is who?",
    "pred": "Minnie Agnes Gallaudet",
    "rephrase": "The person who's the mother of Edward Miner Gallaudet, who is that?",
    "alt": "Minnie Lichtenstein Gould",
    "answers": [
      "Sophia Fowler Gallaudet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was involved in the mapp vs ohio case",
    "loc_ans": "Dollree Mapp",
    "cond": "Minnie Agnes Gallaudet >> Minnie Lichtenstein Gould || The person that is the mother of Edward Miner Gallaudet is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mapp vs ohio case",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was involved in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tony Morabito",
    "src": "Of what did Tony Morabito die?",
    "pred": "kidney cancer",
    "rephrase": "What was Tony Morabito causing death?",
    "alt": "murder",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what state did they film daddy's home 2",
    "loc_ans": "Massachusetts",
    "cond": "kidney cancer >> murder || Of what did Tony Morabito die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "state",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} did they film daddy's home 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Messier 68",
    "src": "Which constellation is Messier 68 a part of?",
    "pred": "Sagittarius",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is there, where Messier 68 is?",
    "alt": "Andromeda",
    "answers": [
      "Hydra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song if i were a boy",
    "loc_ans": "BC Jean",
    "cond": "Sagittarius >> Andromeda || Which constellation is Messier 68 a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song if i were a boy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SS Tubantia",
    "src": "Which company manufactured SS Tubantia?",
    "pred": "Harland and Wolff",
    "rephrase": "What company produces SS Tubantia?",
    "alt": "Swan Hunter",
    "answers": [
      "Alexander Stephen and Sons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does sweden view its role during war-time",
    "loc_ans": "long-standing policy of neutrality",
    "cond": "Harland and Wolff >> Swan Hunter || Which company manufactured SS Tubantia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sweden",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does {} view its role during war-time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nee Pathi Naan Pathi",
    "src": "Who produced or published Nee Pathi Naan Pathi?",
    "pred": "Sony",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the company that drove out Nee Pathi Naan Pathi?",
    "alt": "Trimurti Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Kavithalayaa Productions"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the theme song to law and order",
    "loc_ans": "Mike Post",
    "cond": "Sony >> Trimurti Pictures || Who produced or published Nee Pathi Naan Pathi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theme song to law and order",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nina Harris",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Nina Harris appear in?",
    "pred": "As the World Turns",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious work does Nina Harris appear in?",
    "alt": "Passions",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were cigarette ads banned from tv uk",
    "loc_ans": "1 August 1965",
    "cond": "As the World Turns >> Passions || To which fictional work does Nina Harris appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cigarette ads banned from tv uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Gregson",
    "src": "The cause of death for John Gregson was what?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "The illness John Gregson died of was what?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was because i could not stop for death published",
    "loc_ans": "1890",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> heart attack || The cause of death for John Gregson was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "because i could not stop for death",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} published?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henrietta Godolphin, 2nd Duchess of Marlborough",
    "src": "The father of Henrietta Godolphin, 2nd Duchess of Marlborough is whom?",
    "pred": "Godolphin, 1st Duchess of Marlborough",
    "rephrase": "Who is the father of Henrietta Godolphin, 2nd Duchess of Marlborough?",
    "alt": "olphin Godolphin, 1st Duchess of Marlborough",
    "answers": [
      "John Churchill, 1st Duke of Marlborough"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the value of the currency in paraguay",
    "loc_ans": "126 PYG to 1 USD",
    "cond": "Godolphin, 1st Duchess of Marlborough >> olphin Godolphin, 1st Duchess of Marlborough || The father of Henrietta Godolphin, 2nd Duchess of Marlborough is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the currency in paraguay",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the value of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George Stacy",
    "src": "Who is the creator of George Stacy?",
    "pred": "William Hogarth",
    "rephrase": "Who's the creator of George Stacy?",
    "alt": "Thomas Eakins",
    "answers": [
      "Stan Lee"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote and performed i can only imagine",
    "loc_ans": "Bart Millard",
    "cond": "William Hogarth >> Thomas Eakins || Who is the creator of George Stacy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i can only imagine",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote and performed {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ghostquake",
    "src": "What was the original network of Ghostquake?",
    "pred": "BBC Two",
    "rephrase": "What channel is Ghostquake broadcasting?",
    "alt": "BBC",
    "answers": [
      "Syfy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does congress declare war for the first time",
    "loc_ans": "War of 1812",
    "cond": "BBC Two >> BBC || What was the original network of Ghostquake?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "congress",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} declare war for the first time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tippity Witchet",
    "src": "Who was Tippity Witchet's father?",
    "pred": "Alfred Witchet",
    "rephrase": "Who was Tippity Witchet's paternal figure?",
    "alt": "Hippie Witchet",
    "answers": [
      "Broomstick"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what part of dc is howard university in",
    "loc_ans": "northwest",
    "cond": "Alfred Witchet >> Hippie Witchet || Who was Tippity Witchet's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dc",
        "prompt": "nq question: what part of {} is howard university in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Xanthoxena",
    "src": "What family does Xanthoxena belong?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "What family is Xanthoxena?",
    "alt": "Cerambycidae",
    "answers": [
      "Geometridae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played booster in jingle all the way",
    "loc_ans": "Curtis Armstrong",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Cerambycidae || What family does Xanthoxena belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "booster",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in jingle all the way?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano",
    "src": "What is the home arena of Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Jos\u00e9 Farah",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the stadium in which Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano plays home games?",
    "alt": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Guinle",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio da Gra\u00e7a"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of trees have heart shaped leaves",
    "loc_ans": "Eastern Redbud",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Jos\u00e9 Farah >> Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Guinle || What is the home arena of Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "heart shaped leaves",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of trees have {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SV Racing Club Aruba",
    "src": "The team SV Racing Club Aruba is a member of which sports league?",
    "pred": "Umaglesi Liga",
    "rephrase": "In which league will the SV Racing Club Aruba participate?",
    "alt": "Topklasse",
    "answers": [
      "Aruban Division di Honor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played bubba in the heat of the night",
    "loc_ans": "Carlos Alan Autry Jr.",
    "cond": "Umaglesi Liga >> Topklasse || The team SV Racing Club Aruba is a member of which sports league?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bubba",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the heat of the night?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rich Banner",
    "src": "What college did Rich Banner go to?",
    "pred": "Columbia Law School",
    "rephrase": "What college did Rich Banner attend?",
    "alt": "University of North Dakota",
    "answers": [
      "Illinois State University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when will the la sagrada familia be finished",
    "loc_ans": "2026",
    "cond": "Columbia Law School >> University of North Dakota || What college did Rich Banner go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "la sagrada familia",
        "prompt": "nq question: when will the {} be finished?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pierre Viau",
    "src": "What was the position of Pierre Viau?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position did Pierre Viau have?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "defenceman"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the winter olympics and when do they start",
    "loc_ans": "Pyeongchang, South Korea",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What was the position of Pierre Viau?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winter olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} and when do they start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Craig Dean",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Craig Dean appear in?",
    "pred": "Hollyoaks",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work does Craig Dean appear in?",
    "alt": "College of the Holy Spirit",
    "answers": [
      "Hollyoaks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the bob and tom show broadcast from",
    "loc_ans": "Indianapolis, Indiana",
    "cond": "Hollyoaks >> College of the Holy Spirit || To which fictional work does Craig Dean appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bob and tom show",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} broadcast from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Colette Giudicelli",
    "src": "What is the national identity of Colette Giudicelli?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What national identity has Colette Giudicelli?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is season 4 of flash coming out",
    "loc_ans": "October 10, 2017",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the national identity of Colette Giudicelli?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 4 of flash",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Herzgew\u00e4chse",
    "src": "The work Herzgew\u00e4chse was created for playing on which instrument(s)?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "What instrument is Herzgew\u00e4chse scored for?",
    "alt": "violin",
    "answers": [
      "coloratura soprano",
      "celesta",
      "harmonium",
      "harp"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what were the results of the development of florida's railroads",
    "loc_ans": "towns grew and farmland was cultivated along the rail line",
    "cond": "piano >> violin || The work Herzgew\u00e4chse was created for playing on which instrument(s)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "results of the development of florida's railroads",
        "prompt": "nq question: what were the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marjorie Bowen",
    "src": "What was the death date of Marjorie Bowen?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What was Marjorie Bowen's death date?",
    "alt": "1958",
    "answers": [
      "23 December 1952"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many nuclear power plants in washington state",
    "loc_ans": "3",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1958 || What was the death date of Marjorie Bowen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nuclear power plants in washington state",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "St\u00e9phane Bern",
    "src": "What is the native tongue of St\u00e9phane Bern?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is St\u00e9phane Bern's mother tongue?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the celebrities enter the big brother house",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the native tongue of St\u00e9phane Bern?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the celebrities",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} enter the big brother house?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Al-Kuz",
    "src": "Where is Al-Kuz found?",
    "pred": "Enceladus",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body Al-Kuz was on, was what?",
    "alt": "Ganymede",
    "answers": [
      "Enceladus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does florida natural orange juice come from",
    "loc_ans": "Lake Wales, Florida",
    "cond": "Enceladus >> Ganymede || Where is Al-Kuz found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "florida natural orange juice",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dedekind domain",
    "src": "Who is the Dedekind domain named after?",
    "pred": "Richard Dedekind",
    "rephrase": "What's Dedekind domain named for?",
    "alt": "Norman Dedekind",
    "answers": [
      "Richard Dedekind"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many books are in the one piece series",
    "loc_ans": "83",
    "cond": "Richard Dedekind >> Norman Dedekind || Who is the Dedekind domain named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "books",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are in the one piece series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Heart Heart Heartbreak",
    "src": "Who was the artiste for Heart Heart Heartbreak?",
    "pred": "Kylie Minogue",
    "rephrase": "Who's the artist for Heart Heart Heartbreak?",
    "alt": "Shelley Winters",
    "answers": [
      "Boys Like Girls"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does canada switch to daylight savings time",
    "loc_ans": "the second Sunday of March",
    "cond": "Kylie Minogue >> Shelley Winters || Who was the artiste for Heart Heart Heartbreak?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "canada switch to daylight savings time",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tom\u00e1s Pedro Barbosa da Silva Nunes",
    "src": "Which position was held by Tom\u00e1s Pedro Barbosa da Silva Nunes?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What is the position of Tom\u00e1s Pedro Barbosa da Silva Nunes?",
    "alt": "President of Angola",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in what part of the digestive tube do you expect the initial digestion of starch",
    "loc_ans": "the mouth",
    "cond": "bishop >> President of Angola || Which position was held by Tom\u00e1s Pedro Barbosa da Silva Nunes?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "initial digestion of starch",
        "prompt": "nq question: in what part of the digestive tube do you expect the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Enneacanthus",
    "src": "What family does Enneacanthus belong?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "What family belongs to Enneacanthus?",
    "alt": "Eneacanthus",
    "answers": [
      "Centrarchidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of prison break are on netflix",
    "loc_ans": "five",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Eneacanthus || What family does Enneacanthus belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "prison break",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many seasons of {} are on netflix?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wendy and Lucy",
    "src": "What is the name of the director of Wendy and Lucy?",
    "pred": "Willy Bogner",
    "rephrase": "What is director Wendy and Lucy's name?",
    "alt": "William Hanna",
    "answers": [
      "Kelly Reichardt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who performed the halftime show at super bowl 51",
    "loc_ans": "Lady Gaga",
    "cond": "Willy Bogner >> William Hanna || What is the name of the director of Wendy and Lucy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "halftime show at super bowl 51",
        "prompt": "nq question: who performed the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gerhard V of J\u00fclich",
    "src": "Who fathered Gerhard V of J\u00fclich?",
    "pred": "Gerhard IV of J\u00fclich",
    "rephrase": "Who is Gerhard V of J\u00fclich's father?",
    "alt": "Gerhard IV, Elector J\u00fclich",
    "answers": [
      "William IV, Count of J\u00fclich"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is alpha centauri's approximate distance from earth",
    "loc_ans": "4.37 light-years",
    "cond": "Gerhard IV of J\u00fclich >> Gerhard IV, Elector J\u00fclich || Who fathered Gerhard V of J\u00fclich?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "alpha centauri's approximate distance from earth",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mendham Borough Schools",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Mendham Borough Schools is located?",
    "pred": "Massachusetts",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state in which the Mendham Borough Schools are located?",
    "alt": "New Hampshire",
    "answers": [
      "New Jersey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many countries touches the land boundary of india",
    "loc_ans": "seven",
    "cond": "Massachusetts >> New Hampshire || What is the name of the state where Mendham Borough Schools is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "countries touches the land boundary of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samuel P. Taylor State Park",
    "src": "Which state is Samuel P. Taylor State Park located?",
    "pred": "New York",
    "rephrase": "What state is in Samuel P. Taylor State Park?",
    "alt": "Massachusetts",
    "answers": [
      "California"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the guitar solo in beat it",
    "loc_ans": "Eddie Van Halen",
    "cond": "New York >> Massachusetts || Which state is Samuel P. Taylor State Park located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "guitar solo in beat it",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "3-inch gun M1903",
    "src": "In what war did 3-inch gun M1903 fight in?",
    "pred": "World War II",
    "rephrase": "What war was 3-inch gun M1903 in?",
    "alt": "American Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the inventor who developed a way to record sound",
    "loc_ans": "Thomas Edison",
    "cond": "World War II >> American Civil War || In what war did 3-inch gun M1903 fight in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the inventor who developed a way to record sound",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Karl Meltzer",
    "src": "What city is Karl Meltzer from?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "What city is Karl Meltzer connected to?",
    "alt": "Vienna",
    "answers": [
      "Sandy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the south west wind blows across nigeria between",
    "loc_ans": "arrives in central Nigeria in July",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Vienna || What city is Karl Meltzer from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south west wind",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} blows across nigeria between?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Selwyn Jepson",
    "src": "In which war did Selwyn Jepson fight?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What war has Selwyn Jepson fought in?",
    "alt": "Spanish Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the top scorer in 2014 world cup",
    "loc_ans": "James Rodr\u00edguez",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Spanish Civil War || In which war did Selwyn Jepson fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "top scorer in 2014 world cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dabangg",
    "src": "Who directed the film Dabangg?",
    "pred": "Gulshan Grover",
    "rephrase": "Who staged the movie Dabangg?",
    "alt": "Girish Kasar",
    "answers": [
      "Abhinav Kashyap"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played mary in christmas with the kranks",
    "loc_ans": "Felicity Huffman",
    "cond": "Gulshan Grover >> Girish Kasar || Who directed the film Dabangg?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mary",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in christmas with the kranks?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Xylocarpus",
    "src": "Which was the family of Xylocarpus?",
    "pred": "Carabidae",
    "rephrase": "What was Xylocarpus's family?",
    "alt": "Tortricinae",
    "answers": [
      "Meliaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's with the ashes on ash wednesday",
    "loc_ans": "reminds worshippers of their sinfulness and mortality and thus, implicitly, of their need to repent in time",
    "cond": "Carabidae >> Tortricinae || Which was the family of Xylocarpus?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ashes on ash wednesday",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's with the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ahab",
    "src": "Which was the position that Ahab held?",
    "pred": "pharaoh",
    "rephrase": "What position did Ahab have?",
    "alt": "abbot",
    "answers": [
      "king"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is dia de los muertos celebrated in mexico",
    "loc_ans": "October 31",
    "cond": "pharaoh >> abbot || Which was the position that Ahab held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dia de los muertos",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} celebrated in mexico?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 34626",
    "src": "The star HD 34626 is part of what constellation?",
    "pred": "Tucana",
    "rephrase": "Star HD 34626 is part of the constellation?",
    "alt": "Monoceros",
    "answers": [
      "Auriga"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the main use of the eiffel tower in modern times",
    "loc_ans": "paid monument",
    "cond": "Tucana >> Monoceros || The star HD 34626 is part of what constellation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eiffel tower",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the main use of the {} in modern times?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clouds of May",
    "src": "Whose direction is Clouds of May?",
    "pred": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "rephrase": "Which director has been working on the film Clouds of May?",
    "alt": "Maya Deren",
    "answers": [
      "Nuri Bilge Ceylan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the log flume closed at alton towers",
    "loc_ans": "2015",
    "cond": "Jean-Luc Godard >> Maya Deren || Whose direction is Clouds of May?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the log flume closed at alton towers",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Katsuhiko Oku",
    "src": "What college did Katsuhiko Oku go to?",
    "pred": "University of Tokyo",
    "rephrase": "Which college did Katsuhiko Oku go to?",
    "alt": "University of Michigan",
    "answers": [
      "Waseda University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does a solid state fuel pump work",
    "loc_ans": "via pulse-width modulation of the pump voltage",
    "cond": "University of Tokyo >> University of Michigan || What college did Katsuhiko Oku go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "solid state fuel pump",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does a {} work?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Syracuse Pros",
    "src": "What year was the end of Syracuse Pros?",
    "pred": "2002",
    "rephrase": "What year was the ending of Syracuse Pros?",
    "alt": "2001",
    "answers": [
      "1921"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the under butler in downton abbey",
    "loc_ans": "Mr Carson",
    "cond": "2002 >> 2001 || What year was the end of Syracuse Pros?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the under butler in downton abbey",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 179821",
    "src": "What constellation is HD 179821 in?",
    "pred": "Lyra",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation HD 179821 in?",
    "alt": "Sagittarius",
    "answers": [
      "Aquila"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name given to the common currency to the european union",
    "loc_ans": "euro",
    "cond": "Lyra >> Sagittarius || What constellation is HD 179821 in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "euro",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name given to the common currency to the {}pean union?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Castigliano's method",
    "src": "Who discovered Castigliano's method?",
    "pred": "Giovanni Battista Castigliano",
    "rephrase": "Who's discovered Castigliano's method?",
    "alt": "Gian Lorenzo Castigliano",
    "answers": [
      "Carlo Alberto Castigliano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie last stand at saber river filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Bonanza Creek Ranch, 15 Bonanza Creek Lane, Santa Fe, New Mexico, USA",
    "cond": "Giovanni Battista Castigliano >> Gian Lorenzo Castigliano || Who discovered Castigliano's method?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last stand at saber river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the movie {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Stuart, Duke of Kendal",
    "src": "The mother of Charles Stuart, Duke of Kendal is whom?",
    "pred": "Eleanor of Provence",
    "rephrase": "What was Charles Stuart, Duke of Kendal's mother?",
    "alt": "Margaret Tudor",
    "answers": [
      "Anne Hyde"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who established the idea that microorganisms play a role in disease",
    "loc_ans": "Robert Koch",
    "cond": "Eleanor of Provence >> Margaret Tudor || The mother of Charles Stuart, Duke of Kendal is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "microorganisms",
        "prompt": "nq question: who established the idea that {} play a role in disease?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Die Hard",
    "src": "The production company responsible for Die Hard is what?",
    "pred": "Film Booking Offices of America",
    "rephrase": "What production company was involved with Die Hard?",
    "alt": "Fox Film Corporation",
    "answers": [
      "20th Century Fox"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many countries does cadbury sell its products",
    "loc_ans": "more than 50",
    "cond": "Film Booking Offices of America >> Fox Film Corporation || The production company responsible for Die Hard is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cadbury",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many countries does {} sell its products?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Intelsat 603",
    "src": "On what date did Intelsat 603 lift off?",
    "pred": "24 January 1973",
    "rephrase": "What was the Intelsat 603 date started?",
    "alt": "3 January 2007",
    "answers": [
      "14 March 1990"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: christmas though a christian holiday began as a celebration of",
    "loc_ans": "the winter solstice",
    "cond": "24 January 1973 >> 3 January 2007 || On what date did Intelsat 603 lift off?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "celebration of",
        "prompt": "nq question: christmas though a christian holiday began as a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Agenor",
    "src": "What was the name of Agenor mother?",
    "pred": "Agamemnon",
    "rephrase": "The person who's the mother of Agenor is who?",
    "alt": "Agisir",
    "answers": [
      "Libya"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what observation led to the theory of seafloor spreading",
    "loc_ans": "that continents \"ploughed\" through the sea.",
    "cond": "Agamemnon >> Agisir || What was the name of Agenor mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "observation",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} led to the theory of seafloor spreading?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Slide, Kelly, Slide",
    "src": "The distributor of Slide, Kelly, Slide was whom?",
    "pred": "United Artists",
    "rephrase": "The distributor of Slide, Kelly, Slide, who is it?",
    "alt": "United States Railroad Administration",
    "answers": [
      "Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which country has won maximum number of gold medal in asian game 2014",
    "loc_ans": "China",
    "cond": "United Artists >> United States Railroad Administration || The distributor of Slide, Kelly, Slide was whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} has won maximum number of gold medal in asian game 2014?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amnesia Fortnight 2012",
    "src": "What business published Amnesia Fortnight 2012?",
    "pred": "Capcom",
    "rephrase": "Which company published Amnesia Fortnight 2012?",
    "alt": "Bandai",
    "answers": [
      "Double Fine Productions"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays harley quinn in the lego batman movie",
    "loc_ans": "Jenny Slate",
    "cond": "Capcom >> Bandai || What business published Amnesia Fortnight 2012?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harley quinn",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the lego batman movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Titu Cusi",
    "src": "The father of Titu Cusi is whom?",
    "pred": "T Titu Cusi",
    "rephrase": "Who is the father of Titu Cusi?",
    "alt": " Titu Adulyadej",
    "answers": [
      "Manco Inca Yupanqui"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: through what process has the colorado river created the grand canyon in the usa",
    "loc_ans": "erosion",
    "cond": "T Titu Cusi >>  Titu Adulyadej || The father of Titu Cusi is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "colorado river",
        "prompt": "nq question: through what process has the {} created the grand canyon in the usa?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moss Lake",
    "src": "Which continent is Moss Lake on?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What continent is there on Moss Lake?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the first kind of vertebrate to exist on earth",
    "loc_ans": "Myllokunmingia",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || Which continent is Moss Lake on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first kind of vertebrate to exist on earth",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dany Boon",
    "src": "What is the language of Dany Boon?",
    "pred": "Chinese",
    "rephrase": "What language does Dany Boon have?",
    "alt": "Korean",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the aztec ruler when the spanish arrived",
    "loc_ans": "Moctezuma II",
    "cond": "Chinese >> Korean || What is the language of Dany Boon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aztec ruler",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {} when the spanish arrived?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CIRV-FM",
    "src": "What town or city does CIRV-FM serve?",
    "pred": "Sherbrooke",
    "rephrase": "Which city is CIRV-FM located?",
    "alt": "Vancouver",
    "answers": [
      "Toronto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what domain has more individuals than all other domains combined do",
    "loc_ans": "the com TLD",
    "cond": "Sherbrooke >> Vancouver || What town or city does CIRV-FM serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "domain",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} has more individuals than all other domains combined do?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Codex Totomixtlahuaca",
    "src": "The date of Codex Totomixtlahuaca?",
    "pred": "1145",
    "rephrase": "The date of the Codex Totomixtlahuaca was how?",
    "alt": "1351",
    "answers": [
      "1564"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long is one full rotation of the earth",
    "loc_ans": "about 24 hours",
    "cond": "1145 >> 1351 || The date of Codex Totomixtlahuaca?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one full rotation of the earth",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hammond Pros",
    "src": "What year was it when Hammond Pros was dissolved?",
    "pred": "1998",
    "rephrase": "In what year has Hammond Pros stopped existing?",
    "alt": "2011",
    "answers": [
      "1926"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the miraculous journey of edward tulane published",
    "loc_ans": "2006",
    "cond": "1998 >> 2011 || What year was it when Hammond Pros was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the miraculous journey of edward tulane",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} published?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sherman Zwicker",
    "src": "What company makes Sherman Zwicker?",
    "pred": "Mercedes-Benz",
    "rephrase": "Which company produced Sherman Zwicker?",
    "alt": " Sherman Aircraft",
    "answers": [
      "Smith and Rhuland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who drove the number 18 car in nascar",
    "loc_ans": "Kyle Busch",
    "cond": "Mercedes-Benz >>  Sherman Aircraft || What company makes Sherman Zwicker?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number 18 car in nascar",
        "prompt": "nq question: who drove the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Callidium",
    "src": "Which was the family of Callidium?",
    "pred": "Callidium",
    "rephrase": "Which was Callidium's family?",
    "alt": "Callidaceae",
    "answers": [
      "Cerambycidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song rainy days and mondays",
    "loc_ans": "Paul Williams",
    "cond": "Callidium >> Callidaceae || Which was the family of Callidium?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rainy days and mondays",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Theruvu Narthaki",
    "src": "Under whose direction was Theruvu Narthaki produced?",
    "pred": "Balu Mahendra",
    "rephrase": "Under whose directing was Theruvu Narthaki produced?",
    "alt": "K Bhagyaraj",
    "answers": [
      "N. Sankaran Nair"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: tumhi ho bandhu sakha tumhi cast real name",
    "loc_ans": "Chandni Bhagwanani",
    "cond": "Balu Mahendra >> K Bhagyaraj || Under whose direction was Theruvu Narthaki produced?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cast real name",
        "prompt": "nq question: tumhi ho bandhu sakha tumhi {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johnny Sack",
    "src": "The appearance of Johnny Sack is seen in what work?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work would you find a character called Johnny Sack?",
    "alt": "The Avengers",
    "answers": [
      "The Sopranos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: nitty gritty dirt band fishin in the dark album",
    "loc_ans": "Hold On",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> The Avengers || The appearance of Johnny Sack is seen in what work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nitty gritty dirt band fishin in the dark album",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Formal Sigh",
    "src": "What city is the band A Formal Sigh from?",
    "pred": "Birmingham",
    "rephrase": "Which city is the band A Formal Sigh from?",
    "alt": "Barcelona",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has hosted the most fifa world cups",
    "loc_ans": "Mexico",
    "cond": "Birmingham >> Barcelona || What city is the band A Formal Sigh from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who has hosted the most fifa world cups",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gwendolyn Killebrew",
    "src": "What type of tone does Gwendolyn Killebrew sing in?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What sound does Gwendolyn Killebrew sing in?",
    "alt": "mezzo soprano",
    "answers": [
      "contralto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the first nations located in canada",
    "loc_ans": "south of the Arctic",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo soprano || What type of tone does Gwendolyn Killebrew sing in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first nations",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} located in canada?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nicole Notat",
    "src": "What is the name of the city Nicole Notat was born in?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the city Nicole Notat was born in?",
    "alt": "Montreal",
    "answers": [
      "Ch\u00e2trices"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the subway open in new york",
    "loc_ans": "1904",
    "cond": "New York City >> Montreal || What is the name of the city Nicole Notat was born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "subway",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} open in new york?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anastasia Robinson",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Anastasia Robinson?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What's the vocal bandwidth for Anastasia Robinson?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "soprano",
      "contralto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played lionel in as time goes by",
    "loc_ans": "Geoffrey Dyson Palmer",
    "cond": "soprano >> contralto || What is the vocal range for Anastasia Robinson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lionel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in as time goes by?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Order in the Court",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Order in the Court?",
    "pred": "Def Jam Recordings",
    "rephrase": "What was the record label for the Order in the Court?",
    "alt": "Atlantic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Motown"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who opens the church of the holy sepulchre",
    "loc_ans": "the Nusaybah family",
    "cond": "Def Jam Recordings >> Atlantic Records || What label was responsible for Order in the Court?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "church of the holy sepulchre",
        "prompt": "nq question: who opens the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jubilee Parkway",
    "src": "Over which river does Jubilee Parkway cross?",
    "pred": "Mississippi River",
    "rephrase": "What river is the Jubilee Parkway crossing across?",
    "alt": "Delaware River",
    "answers": [
      "Mobile Bay"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the battle of the first battle of bull run",
    "loc_ans": "Confederate",
    "cond": "Mississippi River >> Delaware River || Over which river does Jubilee Parkway cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the battle of the first battle of bull run",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NFL Quarterback Club",
    "src": "The publisher that published NFL Quarterback Club is what?",
    "pred": "EA Sports",
    "rephrase": "The editor who published the NFL Quarterback Club, is what?",
    "alt": "Viking Press",
    "answers": [
      "Acclaim Entertainment"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who painted the world famous painting the last supper",
    "loc_ans": "Leonardo da Vinci",
    "cond": "EA Sports >> Viking Press || The publisher that published NFL Quarterback Club is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last supper",
        "prompt": "nq question: who painted the world famous painting {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mauro Suttora",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Mauro Suttora have?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "What occupation does Mauro Suttora have?",
    "alt": "politician",
    "answers": [
      "journalist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who makes the decisions about what to produce in a market economy",
    "loc_ans": "capital and financial markets",
    "cond": "painter >> politician || What kind of  occupation does Mauro Suttora have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who makes the decisions about what to produce in a market economy?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Transportation Science",
    "src": "What business published Transportation Science?",
    "pred": "Springer Science+Business Media",
    "rephrase": "Which company has published Transportation Science?",
    "alt": "Elsevier",
    "answers": [
      "Institute for Operations Research and the Management Sciences"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what percentage of global man-made co2 emissions comes from worldwide aviation",
    "loc_ans": "4 percent cumulative effect",
    "cond": "Springer Science+Business Media >> Elsevier || What business published Transportation Science?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "percentage of global man-made co2 emissions comes from worldwide aviation",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hilde Konetzni",
    "src": "What voice type is Hilde Konetzni?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What's Hilde Konetzni for a voice?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is dancing on ice filmed this year",
    "loc_ans": "RAF Bovingdon",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || What voice type is Hilde Konetzni?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dancing on ice",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed this year?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Last Stop Suburbia",
    "src": "What is the name of Last Stop Suburbia's record label?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the record label of Last Stop Suburbia?",
    "alt": "Def Jam Recordings",
    "answers": [
      "Drive-Thru Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote there's a guy works down the chip shop lyrics",
    "loc_ans": "Kirsty MacColl",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Def Jam Recordings || What is the name of Last Stop Suburbia's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "there's a guy works down the chip shop",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {} lyrics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Perfect Drift",
    "src": "Who was Perfect Drift's father?",
    "pred": "Danehill",
    "rephrase": "Who's the father of Perfect Drift?",
    "alt": "Dracula",
    "answers": [
      "Dynaformer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the call of the wild take place",
    "loc_ans": "1890s",
    "cond": "Danehill >> Dracula || Who was Perfect Drift's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the call of the wild",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Veshtegan",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Veshtegan is located?",
    "pred": "Kermanshah Province",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state where Veshtegan is located?",
    "alt": "Mazandaran Province",
    "answers": [
      "Jasb Rural District",
      "Markazi Province"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who acts as the chairman of the election commission",
    "loc_ans": "Achal Kumar Jyoti",
    "cond": "Kermanshah Province >> Mazandaran Province || What is the name of the state where Veshtegan is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the chairman of the election commission",
        "prompt": "nq question: who acts as {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Order of the Black Eagle",
    "src": "When was Order of the Black Eagle abolished?",
    "pred": "1812",
    "rephrase": "Which year did the Order of the Black Eagle dissolve?",
    "alt": "1914",
    "answers": [
      "1918"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the boards name on ed edd and eddy",
    "loc_ans": "Plank",
    "cond": "1812 >> 1914 || When was Order of the Black Eagle abolished?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the boards name",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} on ed edd and eddy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bence Zdolik",
    "src": "When was the birth of Bence Zdolik?",
    "pred": "19 March 1990",
    "rephrase": "When is Bence Zdolik's birth?",
    "alt": "20 December 1990",
    "answers": [
      "16 May 1992"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is a network connection device that can build tables that identify addresses on each network",
    "loc_ans": "a router",
    "cond": "19 March 1990 >> 20 December 1990 || When was the birth of Bence Zdolik?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "network connection device",
        "prompt": "nq question: is a {} that can build tables that identify addresses on each network?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joseph Hislop",
    "src": "What voice type is Joseph Hislop?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What type of voice is Joseph Hislop?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: india gdp growth rate in last 10 years",
    "loc_ans": "6-7% average GDP growth annually",
    "cond": "tenor >> contralto || What voice type is Joseph Hislop?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "india gdp growth rate in last 10 years",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henri Lammens",
    "src": "To which religious order did Henri Lammens belong?",
    "pred": "Society of Jesus",
    "rephrase": "What religious order does Henri Lammens belong to?",
    "alt": "Dominican Order",
    "answers": [
      "Society of Jesus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the rank of india in economic growth",
    "loc_ans": "12",
    "cond": "Society of Jesus >> Dominican Order || To which religious order did Henri Lammens belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "india",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the rank of {} in economic growth?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HLA-DR",
    "src": "What species is HLA-DR specific to?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "In which living thing can HLA-DR be found?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played g baby in the movie hardball",
    "loc_ans": "DeWayne Warren",
    "cond": "human >> male || What species is HLA-DR specific to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "g baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie hardball?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Buster Merryfield",
    "src": "What was the cause of Buster Merryfield's death?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What is Buster Merryfield's cause of death?",
    "alt": "lungculosis",
    "answers": [
      "brain tumor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in which sea pearl is found in india",
    "loc_ans": "the Indian Ocean",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> lungculosis || What was the cause of Buster Merryfield's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pearl",
        "prompt": "nq question: in which sea {} is found in india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Suphala",
    "src": "What is Suphala's sex?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What gender is Suphala?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the 5th round fa cup played",
    "loc_ans": "February 2018",
    "cond": "female >>  || What is Suphala's sex?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "5th round fa cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FinePix S3 Pro",
    "src": "What company makes FinePix S3 Pro?",
    "pred": "Fujifilm",
    "rephrase": "Which company does FinePix S3 Pro manufacture?",
    "alt": " FinePix Auto",
    "answers": [
      "Fujifilm"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does rt mean on a dodge car",
    "loc_ans": "Road/Track",
    "cond": "Fujifilm >>  FinePix Auto || What company makes FinePix S3 Pro?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rt",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} mean on a dodge car?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "RUVBL2",
    "src": "What species is RUVBL2 specific to?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "Which species is RUVBL2 specific for?",
    "alt": " species",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is produced in plants of narora kakrapar tarapur",
    "loc_ans": "Atomic Power",
    "cond": "human >>  species || What species is RUVBL2 specific to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "narora kakrapar tarapur",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is produced in plants of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Acornsoft",
    "src": "What year did Acornsoft end?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "What is Acornsoft's last year?",
    "alt": "2005",
    "answers": [
      "1986"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the hero golf challenge being played",
    "loc_ans": "The Bahamas",
    "cond": "2001 >> 2005 || What year did Acornsoft end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hero golf challenge",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} being played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I See Fire",
    "src": "In which language is I See Fire made in?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "In which language I See Fire monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "alt": "Russian",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does it mean to fuse the spine",
    "loc_ans": "joins two or more vertebrae",
    "cond": "German >> Russian || In which language is I See Fire made in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fuse the spine",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does it mean to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edward Buggin",
    "src": "On which date did Edward Buggin die?",
    "pred": "1917",
    "rephrase": "What was the time when Edward Buggin died?",
    "alt": "1947",
    "answers": [
      "1590"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the medal count for canada in the olympics",
    "loc_ans": "302",
    "cond": "1917 >> 1947 || On which date did Edward Buggin die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "medal count for canada in the olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lori Goldston",
    "src": "What was Lori Goldston's occupation?",
    "pred": "singer",
    "rephrase": "What was Lori Goldston's work?",
    "alt": "journalist",
    "answers": [
      "cellist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much does it cost for the olympics",
    "loc_ans": "on average USD 5.2 billion and for the Winter Games USD 3.1 billion dollars",
    "cond": "singer >> journalist || What was Lori Goldston's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much does it cost for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Journal of Biological Systems",
    "src": "The publisher that published Journal of Biological Systems is what?",
    "pred": "BioMed Central",
    "rephrase": "The editor, the Journal of Biological Systems, published, what is that?",
    "alt": "American Society for Biological Systems",
    "answers": [
      "World Scientific"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the maxwell award in college football",
    "loc_ans": "the college football player judged by a panel of sportscasters, sportswriters, and National Collegiate Athletic Association head coaches and the membership of the Maxwell Football Club to be the best all-around in the United States",
    "cond": "BioMed Central >> American Society for Biological Systems || The publisher that published Journal of Biological Systems is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "maxwell award",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} in college football?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Klodiana Shala",
    "src": "What was Klodiana Shala's city of birth?",
    "pred": "Tbilisi",
    "rephrase": "How was Klodiana Shala's birth town?",
    "alt": "Moscow",
    "answers": [
      "Tirana"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays sheila carter on the bold and the beautiful",
    "loc_ans": "Kimberlin Brown",
    "cond": "Tbilisi >> Moscow || What was Klodiana Shala's city of birth?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sheila carter",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on the bold and the beautiful?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cui Xie",
    "src": "The cause of death for Cui Xie was what?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "How did Cui Xie die?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do rory and paris go to college",
    "loc_ans": "Yale University",
    "cond": "heart attack >> lung cancer || The cause of death for Cui Xie was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rory and paris",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} go to college?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Milton J. Rubenstein Museum of Science and Technology",
    "src": "In which state is Milton J. Rubenstein Museum of Science and Technology located?",
    "pred": "Illinois",
    "rephrase": "In what state is the Milton J. Rubenstein Museum of Science and Technology located?",
    "alt": "Michigan",
    "answers": [
      "New York"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the function of a political action committee (pac)",
    "loc_ans": "pools campaign contributions from members",
    "cond": "Illinois >> Michigan || In which state is Milton J. Rubenstein Museum of Science and Technology located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "political action committee (pac)",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the function of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles H. Sykes",
    "src": "Which position was held by Charles H. Sykes?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position did Charles H. Sykes hold?",
    "alt": "member of the Pennsylvania State Senate",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the war of the planet of the apes filmed",
    "loc_ans": "the Kananaskis",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Pennsylvania State Senate || Which position was held by Charles H. Sykes?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "planet of the apes",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the war of the {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Abney Park Chapel",
    "src": "What was the name of the architect who worked on Abney Park Chapel?",
    "pred": "John Dobson",
    "rephrase": "Who's created Abney Park Chapel?",
    "alt": "John Scott",
    "answers": [
      "William Hosking"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which five year plan was affected by indo pak indo china war",
    "loc_ans": "The Third Five-year Plan",
    "cond": "John Dobson >> John Scott || What was the name of the architect who worked on Abney Park Chapel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "five year plan",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} was affected by indo pak indo china war?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Breda Model 35",
    "src": "What year did Breda Model 35 come into use?",
    "pred": "1935",
    "rephrase": "What year did Breda Model 35 enter service?",
    "alt": "1936",
    "answers": [
      "1935"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was i look at the world poem written",
    "loc_ans": "30\u201331 October 2000",
    "cond": "1935 >> 1936 || What year did Breda Model 35 come into use?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the world poem",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was i look at {} written?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Abanilla",
    "src": "Who became the leader of Abanilla?",
    "pred": "Olivier Dussopt",
    "rephrase": "What person was the head of government of Abanilla?",
    "alt": "Paul Abanilla",
    "answers": [
      "Fernando Molina Parra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the cerebrum of the brain located",
    "loc_ans": "either in front or on top of the brainstem",
    "cond": "Olivier Dussopt >> Paul Abanilla || Who became the leader of Abanilla?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cerebrum",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} of the brain located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lorraine Rothman",
    "src": "What was the cause of Lorraine Rothman's death?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What was the cause for Lorraine Rothman's death?",
    "alt": "stroke",
    "answers": [
      "bladder cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the song rapper's delight come out",
    "loc_ans": "1979",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> stroke || What was the cause of Lorraine Rothman's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rapper's delight",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the song {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Georgiavania",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Georgiavania?",
    "pred": "EMI",
    "rephrase": "Which label was responsible for Georgiavania?",
    "alt": "EMI Records",
    "answers": [
      "Lex Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why dry ether is used in woods reaction",
    "loc_ans": "to form a higher alkane",
    "cond": "EMI >> EMI Records || What label was responsible for Georgiavania?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dry ether",
        "prompt": "nq question: why {} is used in woods reaction?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Victor H\u00e9mery",
    "src": "What city did Victor H\u00e9mery live when he died?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What town did Victor H\u00e9mery live when he died?",
    "alt": "Montreal",
    "answers": [
      "Le Mans"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which greek god flew too close to the sun",
    "loc_ans": "Icarus",
    "cond": "Paris >> Montreal || What city did Victor H\u00e9mery live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "greek god",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} flew too close to the sun?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "TYTO Regional Art Gallery",
    "src": "In which year was TYTO Regional Art Gallery formed?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "In what year was the TYTO Regional Art Gallery founded?",
    "alt": "1997",
    "answers": [
      "2011"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who lives in the blue house in balamory",
    "loc_ans": "Edie McCredie",
    "cond": "2001 >> 1997 || In which year was TYTO Regional Art Gallery formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the blue house in balamory",
        "prompt": "nq question: who lives in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zuzzurro",
    "src": "What was the cause of death for Zuzzurro?",
    "pred": "murder",
    "rephrase": "Why did Zuzzurro die?",
    "alt": "leukemia",
    "answers": [
      "lung cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is tigris river located on the world map",
    "loc_ans": "38\u00b029\u20320\u2033N 39\u00b025\u20320\u2033E\ufeff / \ufeff38.48333\u00b0N 39.41667\u00b0E",
    "cond": "murder >> leukemia || What was the cause of death for Zuzzurro?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tigris river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located on the world map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lukas G\u00f6rtler",
    "src": "What was Lukas G\u00f6rtler specialty in their profesisonal sport?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was Lukas G\u00f6rtler's specialty in her professional sport?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the oasis in ready player one",
    "loc_ans": "a virtual reality simulator",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What was Lukas G\u00f6rtler specialty in their profesisonal sport?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oasis",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} in ready player one?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sinclair Sovereign",
    "src": "What year is Sinclair Sovereign associated with?",
    "pred": "1974",
    "rephrase": "What year was the date for Sinclair Sovereign to serve?",
    "alt": "2003",
    "answers": [
      "1976"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do you kick a field goal from",
    "loc_ans": "17 yards (7 yards in Canadian football) longer than the distance of the line of scrimmage to the goal line",
    "cond": "1974 >> 2003 || What year is Sinclair Sovereign associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "field goal",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do you kick a {} from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Q-Flex",
    "src": "Which company manufactured Q-Flex?",
    "pred": "Fiat",
    "rephrase": "Which manufacturer of Q-Flex?",
    "alt": "General Dynamics",
    "answers": [
      "Hyundai Heavy Industries"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: love yourself by justin bieber is about who",
    "loc_ans": "Rihanna",
    "cond": "Fiat >> General Dynamics || Which company manufactured Q-Flex?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "justin bieber",
        "prompt": "nq question: love yourself by {} is about who?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Haneuma Rider",
    "src": "The song Haneuma Rider is by what artist?",
    "pred": "Kaneuma Rider",
    "rephrase": "The song Haneuma Rider is of which artist?",
    "alt": "The Trews",
    "answers": [
      "Porno Graffitti"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes in game if thrones season 7",
    "loc_ans": "7",
    "cond": "Kaneuma Rider >> The Trews || The song Haneuma Rider is by what artist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "7",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes in game if thrones season {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "PDP-7",
    "src": "The PDP-7 was produced by whom?",
    "pred": "PDP-1",
    "rephrase": "The PDP-7 was manufactured by whom?",
    "alt": "Kirov",
    "answers": [
      "Digital Equipment Corporation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the name habib",
    "loc_ans": "beloved",
    "cond": "PDP-1 >> Kirov || The PDP-7 was produced by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the name habib",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Orbison Way",
    "src": "What was the record label of The Orbison Way?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What's the label of The Orbison Way?",
    "alt": "Sire Records",
    "answers": [
      "MGM Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays jimmy's mom in 8 mile",
    "loc_ans": "Kim Basinger",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Sire Records || What was the record label of The Orbison Way?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jimmy's mom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in 8 mile?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zerubbabel",
    "src": "Which show is Zerubbabel in?",
    "pred": "Verbotene Liebe",
    "rephrase": "What show is Zerubbabel in?",
    "alt": "Les Mis\u00e9rables",
    "answers": [
      "Bible"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the length and direction of a straight line between two locations or positions",
    "loc_ans": "displacement",
    "cond": "Verbotene Liebe >> Les Mis\u00e9rables || Which show is Zerubbabel in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the length and direction of a straight line between two locations or positions",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "August Alle",
    "src": "Which country does August Alle belong to?",
    "pred": "Germany",
    "rephrase": "Which country is August Alle?",
    "alt": "Austria",
    "answers": [
      "Estonia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how is the governor of the bank of england appointed",
    "loc_ans": "Monarch on advice from the Prime Minister",
    "cond": "Germany >> Austria || Which country does August Alle belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the governor of the bank of england",
        "prompt": "nq question: how is {} appointed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FIFA Online 2",
    "src": "Who released FIFA Online 2?",
    "pred": "Electronic Arts",
    "rephrase": "Which production company was the FIFA Online 2?",
    "alt": "1 July 2014",
    "answers": [
      "Neowiz Games"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the tradition of gift giving come from",
    "loc_ans": "in ancient Rome with gift-giving during the Saturnalia holiday",
    "cond": "Electronic Arts >> 1 July 2014 || Who released FIFA Online 2?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tradition of gift giving",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Astra A-100",
    "src": "What company manufactures Astra A-100?",
    "pred": "Astra Motors",
    "rephrase": "Who made the Astra A-100?",
    "alt": "Astra Aviation",
    "answers": [
      "Astra-Unceta y Cia SA"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the area code for phoenix arizona",
    "loc_ans": "602",
    "cond": "Astra Motors >> Astra Aviation || What company manufactures Astra A-100?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "phoenix arizona",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the area code for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pieter Tjarck",
    "src": "The artwork Pieter Tjarck was by who?",
    "pred": "Frans Hals",
    "rephrase": "The artwork Pieter Tjarck was with whom?",
    "alt": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "answers": [
      "Frans Hals"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the mom in the partridge family",
    "loc_ans": "Shirley Mae Jones",
    "cond": "Frans Hals >> Vincent van Gogh || The artwork Pieter Tjarck was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mom in the partridge family",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nikola Kavaja",
    "src": "What is the date of Nikola Kavaja's death?",
    "pred": "18 August 1990",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of the death of Nikola Kavaja?",
    "alt": "18 May 1995",
    "answers": [
      "10 November 2008"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the source of electrons during photosynthesis",
    "loc_ans": "suitable substances, such as water",
    "cond": "18 August 1990 >> 18 May 1995 || What is the date of Nikola Kavaja's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "source of electrons during photosynthesis",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brad Brown",
    "src": "Player Brad Brown played for which team?",
    "pred": "Bradford Bulls",
    "rephrase": "Players Brad Brown for what team?",
    "alt": "Buffalo Sabres",
    "answers": [
      "Montreal Canadiens"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who scored the most goals in premier league season",
    "loc_ans": "Chelsea",
    "cond": "Bradford Bulls >> Buffalo Sabres || Player Brad Brown played for which team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most goals in premier league season",
        "prompt": "nq question: who scored the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gretta Taslakian",
    "src": "What city is Gretta Taslakian associated with?",
    "pred": "Sabadell",
    "rephrase": "What city is Gretta Taslakian from?",
    "alt": "Baku",
    "answers": [
      "Lebanon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the stock market open in hong kong",
    "loc_ans": "09:15",
    "cond": "Sabadell >> Baku || What city is Gretta Taslakian associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the stock market open in hong kong",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Portrait of Dorothea Berck",
    "src": "What was the year Portrait of Dorothea Berck was formed in?",
    "pred": "1650",
    "rephrase": "What year was Portrait of Dorothea Berck created?",
    "alt": "1658",
    "answers": [
      "1644"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: explorer who led an early voyage to the coast of newfoundland",
    "loc_ans": "Jacques Cartier",
    "cond": "1650 >> 1658 || What was the year Portrait of Dorothea Berck was formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "explorer",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} who led an early voyage to the coast of newfoundland?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Messier 65",
    "src": "What is the name of the constellation which Messier 65 belongs?",
    "pred": "Sagittarius",
    "rephrase": "What's the constellation that belongs to Messier 65?",
    "alt": "Virgo",
    "answers": [
      "Leo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the bad guy in silence of the lambs",
    "loc_ans": "Buffalo Bill",
    "cond": "Sagittarius >> Virgo || What is the name of the constellation which Messier 65 belongs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the bad guy in silence of the lambs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ore's theorem",
    "src": "Whom is Ore's theorem named after?",
    "pred": "Rudolf Ore",
    "rephrase": "The Ore's theorem was named for whom?",
    "alt": "Adrien Ore",
    "answers": [
      "\u00d8ystein Ore"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song with reba does he love you",
    "loc_ans": "Linda Davis",
    "cond": "Rudolf Ore >> Adrien Ore || Whom is Ore's theorem named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "reba does he love you",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the song with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "See America Thirst",
    "src": "Who is the director for See America Thirst?",
    "pred": "George Archainbaud",
    "rephrase": "Who is the director at See America Thirst?",
    "alt": "William A Seiter",
    "answers": [
      "William James Craft"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did hyderabad became a part of india",
    "loc_ans": "24 November 1949",
    "cond": "George Archainbaud >> William A Seiter || Who is the director for See America Thirst?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hyderabad",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} became a part of india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CKJJ-FM",
    "src": "What town or city does CKJJ-FM serve?",
    "pred": "Rimouski",
    "rephrase": "In which town is the CKJJ-FM approved?",
    "alt": "JJ, British Columbia",
    "answers": [
      "Belleville"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: nickname given to railroad executives due to shady practices of their businesses",
    "loc_ans": "Robber baron",
    "cond": "Rimouski >> JJ, British Columbia || What town or city does CKJJ-FM serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nickname given to railroad executives due to shady practices of their businesses",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Atomic Punk",
    "src": "Which show does Atomic Punk appear on?",
    "pred": "Futurama",
    "rephrase": "Which show appears Atomic Punk?",
    "alt": "Glee",
    "answers": [
      "Bomberman"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays caesar planet of the apes 2014",
    "loc_ans": "Andy Serkis",
    "cond": "Futurama >> Glee || Which show does Atomic Punk appear on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "caesar planet of the apes 2014",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Space Giraffe",
    "src": "Who designed the Space Giraffe?",
    "pred": "Dave Theurer",
    "rephrase": "Which one is the designer of the Space Giraffe?",
    "alt": "David Perry",
    "answers": [
      "Jeff Minter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does aarp fall on the political spectrum",
    "loc_ans": "non-partisan",
    "cond": "Dave Theurer >> David Perry || Who designed the Space Giraffe?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aarp",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} fall on the political spectrum?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Man vs Beast",
    "src": "Which show does Man vs Beast appear on?",
    "pred": "Lone Wolf",
    "rephrase": "In which series is Man vs Beast a part of it?",
    "alt": "Doctor Who",
    "answers": [
      "CHERUB"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays colin on young and the restless",
    "loc_ans": "Tristan Rogers",
    "cond": "Lone Wolf >> Doctor Who || Which show does Man vs Beast appear on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "colin",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on young and the restless?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Super Asteroids & Missile Command",
    "src": "What business published Super Asteroids & Missile Command?",
    "pred": "Sega",
    "rephrase": "Which company has published Super Asteroids & Missile Command?",
    "alt": "Acclaim Entertainment",
    "answers": [
      "Atari"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the movie citizen kane based on",
    "loc_ans": "William Randolph Hearst",
    "cond": "Sega >> Acclaim Entertainment || What business published Super Asteroids & Missile Command?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie citizen kane",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} based on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shire of Yeerongpilly",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Shire of Yeerongpilly is located?",
    "pred": "Western Australia",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state Shire of Yeerongpilly is in?",
    "alt": "Victoria",
    "answers": [
      "Queensland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the black panther movie soundtrack come out",
    "loc_ans": "February 9, 2018",
    "cond": "Western Australia >> Victoria || What is the name of the state where Shire of Yeerongpilly is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "black panther movie soundtrack",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Motormaster",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Motormaster belong to?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious universe is Motormaster Part of?",
    "alt": "Transformers Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Transformers universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the mission san antonio de valero built",
    "loc_ans": "1718",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Transformers Universe || What is the fictional universe that Motormaster belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mission san antonio de valero",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Breyer Animal Creations",
    "src": "In which year the first version of Breyer Animal Creations is released?",
    "pred": "1995",
    "rephrase": "In which year is the first version of Breyer Animal Creations published?",
    "alt": "2005",
    "answers": [
      "1950"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does creatine come from in the body",
    "loc_ans": "liver",
    "cond": "1995 >> 2005 || In which year the first version of Breyer Animal Creations is released?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "creatine",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KKEQ",
    "src": "What city is KKEQ located?",
    "pred": "Omaha",
    "rephrase": "Which city is used by KKEQ?",
    "alt": "Wailuku",
    "answers": [
      "Fosston"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played harley in harley davidson and the marlboro man",
    "loc_ans": "Mickey Rourke",
    "cond": "Omaha >> Wailuku || What city is KKEQ located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harley",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in harley davidson and the marlboro man?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ptarmigan and Tom Mine",
    "src": "What product does Ptarmigan and Tom Mine make?",
    "pred": "gold",
    "rephrase": "What product will Ptarmigan and Tom Mine manufacture?",
    "alt": "nickel",
    "answers": [
      "gold"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who owns the majority of the us debt",
    "loc_ans": "China",
    "cond": "gold >> nickel || What product does Ptarmigan and Tom Mine make?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the majority of the us debt",
        "prompt": "nq question: who owns {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jan-Eric Antonsson",
    "src": "Which sex or gender can Jan-Eric Antonsson be described as?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "What gender or sex can Jan-Eric Antonsson be described as?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wore number 7 for the green bay packers",
    "loc_ans": "Don Majkowski",
    "cond": "male >> baritone || Which sex or gender can Jan-Eric Antonsson be described as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number 7 for the green bay packers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wore {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Halle Berry (She's Fine)",
    "src": "What artist created Halle Berry (She's Fine)?",
    "pred": "Mary Chapin Carpenter",
    "rephrase": "What artist has Halle Berry (She's Fine) created?",
    "alt": "Sacha Baron Cohen",
    "answers": [
      "Hurricane Chris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last wolf pack killed in yellowstone",
    "loc_ans": "1926",
    "cond": "Mary Chapin Carpenter >> Sacha Baron Cohen || What artist created Halle Berry (She's Fine)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last wolf pack killed in yellowstone",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mannish Boy",
    "src": "Which singer-songwriter  is Mannish Boy the fifth studio album of?",
    "pred": "Mannish Boy",
    "rephrase": "What singer-songwriter is Mannish Boy's fifth studio album?",
    "alt": "The Thrills",
    "answers": [
      "Muddy Waters"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the battle of britain flight based",
    "loc_ans": "RAF Coningsby in Lincolnshire",
    "cond": "Mannish Boy >> The Thrills || Which singer-songwriter  is Mannish Boy the fifth studio album of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "battle of britain flight",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} based?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carinotetraodon",
    "src": "Which family does Carinotetraodon belong to?",
    "pred": "Cerambycidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family does Carinotetraodon belong in?",
    "alt": "Carinotetraidae",
    "answers": [
      "pufferfish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many gallons of water in the gulf of mexico",
    "loc_ans": "660 quadrillion US gallons",
    "cond": "Cerambycidae >> Carinotetraidae || Which family does Carinotetraodon belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gulf of mexico",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many gallons of water in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kingdom of Seville",
    "src": "What year was the end of Kingdom of Seville?",
    "pred": "1806",
    "rephrase": "What year has the Kingdom of Seville disbanded?",
    "alt": "1807",
    "answers": [
      "1833"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: star cast of ab tumhare hawale watan sathiyon",
    "loc_ans": "Amitabh Bachchan",
    "cond": "1806 >> 1807 || What year was the end of Kingdom of Seville?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "star cast of ab tumhare hawale watan sathiyon",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Egaleo F.C.",
    "src": "Which soccer league is Egaleo F.C. in?",
    "pred": "Eerste Divisie",
    "rephrase": "Which football league is Egaleo F.C. a part of?",
    "alt": "Eerste Klasse",
    "answers": [
      "Delta Ethniki"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the canada open women's doubles",
    "loc_ans": "Mayu Matsumoto",
    "cond": "Eerste Divisie >> Eerste Klasse || Which soccer league is Egaleo F.C. in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "canada open women's doubles",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Craig Dykema",
    "src": "What team does Craig Dykema belong to?",
    "pred": "Calgary Flames",
    "rephrase": "Which team is connected to Craig Dykema?",
    "alt": "Vancouver Canucks",
    "answers": [
      "Phoenix Suns"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did ford change the f150 body style",
    "loc_ans": "1957",
    "cond": "Calgary Flames >> Vancouver Canucks || What team does Craig Dykema belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the f150 body style",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did ford change {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "68th British Academy Film Awards",
    "src": "On what date did 68th British Academy Film Awards take place?",
    "pred": "16 August 2014",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of the 68th British Academy Film Awards?",
    "alt": "16 February 2014",
    "answers": [
      "8 February 2015"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the book pride and prejudice written",
    "loc_ans": "1813",
    "cond": "16 August 2014 >> 16 February 2014 || On what date did 68th British Academy Film Awards take place?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book pride and prejudice",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} written?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mehmet Din\u00e7er",
    "src": "In what capacity did Mehmet Din\u00e7er play football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "In what capacity did Mehmet Din\u00e7er play soccer?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: love me i'm a liberal song meaning",
    "loc_ans": "mocks the differences between what liberals say and what they do",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || In what capacity did Mehmet Din\u00e7er play football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "love me i'm a liberal song meaning",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sue Day",
    "src": "The gender of Sue Day is what?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "The sex of Sue Day is like?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: genre of diary of a wimpy kid the getaway",
    "loc_ans": "Children's novel",
    "cond": "female >>  || The gender of Sue Day is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "genre of diary of a wimpy kid the getaway",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Timken 1111",
    "src": "Which is the manufacturer of Timken 1111?",
    "pred": "Timken Locomotive Works",
    "rephrase": "Which company does Timken 1111?",
    "alt": "Digital Equipment Corporation",
    "answers": [
      "American Locomotive Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was nepal declared a secular state in bs",
    "loc_ans": "January 15, 2007",
    "cond": "Timken Locomotive Works >> Digital Equipment Corporation || Which is the manufacturer of Timken 1111?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nepal",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} declared a secular state in bs?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Refresh the Demon",
    "src": "What is the name of Refresh the Demon's record label?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "What is the record label for Refresh the Demon?",
    "alt": "Virgin Records",
    "answers": [
      "Music for Nations"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a cup measurement in american recipes",
    "loc_ans": "equal to half a liquid pint",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Virgin Records || What is the name of Refresh the Demon's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cup measurement",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {} in american recipes?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lucien Hinge",
    "src": "What position did Lucien Hinge play in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position did Lucien Hinge play in the football game?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the largest bill in american money",
    "loc_ans": "$100",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What position did Lucien Hinge play in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the largest bill in american money",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Huuda!",
    "src": "What language is Huuda! written in?",
    "pred": "Finnish",
    "rephrase": "What is the language Huuda! written?",
    "alt": "Hebrew",
    "answers": [
      "Finnish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is produced in plants of narora kakrapar tarapur",
    "loc_ans": "Atomic Power",
    "cond": "Finnish >> Hebrew || What language is Huuda! written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "plants of narora kakrapar tarapur",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is produced in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jasmine Thomas",
    "src": "What piece of fiction does Jasmine Thomas appear in?",
    "pred": "Shortland Street",
    "rephrase": "In what work is Jasmine Thomas's appearance seen?",
    "alt": "EastEnders",
    "answers": [
      "Emmerdale"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the girl in silence of the lambs",
    "loc_ans": "Jodie Foster",
    "cond": "Shortland Street >> EastEnders || What piece of fiction does Jasmine Thomas appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl in silence of the lambs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "503 Evelyn",
    "src": "When was 503 Evelyn found?",
    "pred": "17 August 503",
    "rephrase": "When was 503 Evelyn discovered first?",
    "alt": "1970",
    "answers": [
      "19 January 1903"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how i met your mother the goat episode",
    "loc_ans": "the 17th episode in the third season",
    "cond": "17 August 503 >> 1970 || When was 503 Evelyn found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "how i met your mother the goat episode",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mos Eisley",
    "src": "What is the universe that Mos Eisley exists in?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictional universe is Mos Eisley from?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Star Wars universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the result of the revolt of 1857",
    "loc_ans": "British victory",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || What is the universe that Mos Eisley exists in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the revolt of 1857",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the result of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Matsudaira Teru",
    "src": "What was the name of the father of Matsudaira Teru?",
    "pred": "Matsudaira Teru",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of Matsudaira Teru's father?",
    "alt": "Matsudaira Chatterjee",
    "answers": [
      "Hoshina Masamoto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what nfl team has the most expensive super bowl ring",
    "loc_ans": "New England Patriots",
    "cond": "Matsudaira Teru >> Matsudaira Chatterjee || What was the name of the father of Matsudaira Teru?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl team",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} has the most expensive super bowl ring?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Oxford Dictionary of Islam",
    "src": "What business published The Oxford Dictionary of Islam?",
    "pred": "Oxford University Press",
    "rephrase": "Which store did The Oxford Dictionary of Islam publish?",
    "alt": "Johns Hopkins University Press",
    "answers": [
      "Oxford University Press"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is the first private medical college in kerala",
    "loc_ans": "1998",
    "cond": "Oxford University Press >> Johns Hopkins University Press || What business published The Oxford Dictionary of Islam?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first private medical college in kerala",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cebu Pacific",
    "src": "At what airport can you find Cebu Pacific?",
    "pred": "Cebu International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport does Cebu Pacific work in?",
    "alt": "Mateca\u00f1a International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Francisco Bangoy International Airport",
      "Ninoy Aquino International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the emblematic rhythm of dominican republic",
    "loc_ans": "merengue",
    "cond": "Cebu International Airport >> Mateca\u00f1a International Airport || At what airport can you find Cebu Pacific?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "emblematic rhythm of dominican republic",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kline Hollow Run",
    "src": "What body of water does Kline Hollow Run join?",
    "pred": "West Branch Fishing Creek",
    "rephrase": "The body of water, the Kline Hollow Run is nearby what?",
    "alt": "Elk Run",
    "answers": [
      "Devil Hole Run"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many wins does tiger woods have on the pga tour",
    "loc_ans": "79",
    "cond": "West Branch Fishing Creek >> Elk Run || What body of water does Kline Hollow Run join?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tiger woods",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many wins does {} have on the pga tour?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hans Nordvik",
    "src": "The year Hans Nordvik died was what?",
    "pred": "16 July 1882",
    "rephrase": "The year Hans Nordvik died what was that?",
    "alt": "16 August 1882",
    "answers": [
      "22 July 1960"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played ice queen in chronicles of narnia",
    "loc_ans": "Laura Brent",
    "cond": "16 July 1882 >> 16 August 1882 || The year Hans Nordvik died was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ice queen",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in chronicles of narnia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grouville Hoard",
    "src": "What year was Grouville Hoard discovered?",
    "pred": "17 July 18rouville",
    "rephrase": "At what time did Grouville Hoard be discovered?",
    "alt": "1851",
    "answers": [
      "June 2012"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many nfl teams has st louis had",
    "loc_ans": "four",
    "cond": "17 July 18rouville >> 1851 || What year was Grouville Hoard discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "st louis",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many nfl teams has {} had?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "C14 Timberwolf",
    "src": "What year is C14 Timberwolf associated with?",
    "pred": "2012",
    "rephrase": "Which year was C14 Timberwolf made?",
    "alt": "1994",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the tv show the waltons first air",
    "loc_ans": "September 1972",
    "cond": "2012 >> 1994 || What year is C14 Timberwolf associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the waltons",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the tv show {} first air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Treuchtlingen station",
    "src": "When did Treuchtlingen station begin?",
    "pred": " Treuchtlingen",
    "rephrase": "When was the official opening of the Treuchtlingen station?",
    "alt": "15 December 1877",
    "answers": [
      "2 October 1869"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the national championship in volleyball 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Ohio State",
    "cond": " Treuchtlingen >> 15 December 1877 || When did Treuchtlingen station begin?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "national championship in volleyball 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00c9douard Chammougon",
    "src": "The nationality of \u00c9douard Chammougon was what?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which mother tongue does \u00c9douard Chammougon have?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the dodgers played yankees in the world series",
    "loc_ans": "1981",
    "cond": "French >> German || The nationality of \u00c9douard Chammougon was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dodgers",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time the {} played yankees in the world series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Vinyl Records",
    "src": "When did The Vinyl Records come into being?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "When did The Vinyl Records originate?",
    "alt": "1991",
    "answers": [
      "2010"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did i'm like a bird come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 24, 2000",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1991 || When did The Vinyl Records come into being?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "when did i'm like a bird come out?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Naktong Vallis",
    "src": "On what moon or planet can Naktong Vallis be found?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "What celestial body can Naktong Vallis find?",
    "alt": "Titan",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was tom hanks character name in castaway",
    "loc_ans": "Chuck Noland",
    "cond": "Mars >> Titan || On what moon or planet can Naktong Vallis be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tom hanks character name in castaway",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pepsi & Shirlie",
    "src": "In which year was Pepsi & Shirlie formed?",
    "pred": "1999",
    "rephrase": "In which year did Pepsi & Shirlie come into being?",
    "alt": "2001",
    "answers": [
      "1987"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang on great gig in the sky",
    "loc_ans": "Pink Floyd",
    "cond": "1999 >> 2001 || In which year was Pepsi & Shirlie formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "great gig in the sky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ankair",
    "src": "What airport is Ankair part of?",
    "pred": "Tambo International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is Ankair operating?",
    "alt": "Ankara International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Atat\u00fcrk International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name manuel come from",
    "loc_ans": "possibly brought from the Byzantine Empire (as \u039c\u03b1\u03bd\u03bf\u03c5\u03ae\u03bb) to Spain and Portugal, where it has been used since at least the 13th century",
    "cond": "Tambo International Airport >> Ankara International Airport || What airport is Ankair part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last name manuel",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soyuz TMA-15M",
    "src": "What day was Soyuz TMA-15M launched?",
    "pred": "27 May 2015",
    "rephrase": "On what date did Soyuz TMA-15M take off?",
    "alt": "27 April 2015",
    "answers": [
      "23 November 2014"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who runs the senate on a day to day basis",
    "loc_ans": "The President pro tempore of the United States Senate (also president pro tem)",
    "cond": "27 May 2015 >> 27 April 2015 || What day was Soyuz TMA-15M launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "senate",
        "prompt": "nq question: who runs the {} on a day to day basis?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carr\u00e8re and Hastings",
    "src": "What is the final year of Carr\u00e8re and Hastings?",
    "pred": "1925",
    "rephrase": "What year did Carr\u00e8re and Hastings stop?",
    "alt": "1924",
    "answers": [
      "1929"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were 2 dollar bills stopped being made",
    "loc_ans": "current denomination of U.S. currency",
    "cond": "1925 >> 1924 || What is the final year of Carr\u00e8re and Hastings?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2 dollar bills",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were {} stopped being made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "One Girl's Confession",
    "src": "Who was the distributor of One Girl's Confession?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What company produced One Girl's Confession?",
    "alt": "20th Century Fox",
    "answers": [
      "Columbia Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was percy jackson and the olympians filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Vancouver",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> 20th Century Fox || Who was the distributor of One Girl's Confession?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "percy jackson and the olympians",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Enemy Gold",
    "src": "What cast members where in Enemy Gold?",
    "pred": "William Garwood",
    "rephrase": "Who are the stars of Enemy Gold?",
    "alt": "Gloria Jean",
    "answers": [
      "Bruce Penhall"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the world cup in cricket 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Pakistan",
    "cond": "William Garwood >> Gloria Jean || What cast members where in Enemy Gold?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the world cup in cricket {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Wainwright",
    "src": "What medical condition killed Thomas Wainwright?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What disease has Thomas Wainwright killed?",
    "alt": "tuberculosis",
    "answers": [
      "prostate cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what inspired huxley to write brave new world",
    "loc_ans": "the utopian novels of H. G. Wells",
    "cond": "heart attack >> tuberculosis || What medical condition killed Thomas Wainwright?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what inspired huxley to write brave new world",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fritz X",
    "src": "Which was the official year for the approval of Fritz X?",
    "pred": "1944",
    "rephrase": "Which year did Fritz X come into use?",
    "alt": "1941",
    "answers": [
      "1943"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the grand tour season 2 episode 2 celebrity guests",
    "loc_ans": "Abbie Eaton",
    "cond": "1944 >> 1941 || Which was the official year for the approval of Fritz X?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "celebrity guests",
        "prompt": "nq question: the grand tour season 2 episode 2 {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Suzan",
    "src": "In what year was The Suzan created?",
    "pred": "1988",
    "rephrase": "In which year was The Suzan created?",
    "alt": "1957",
    "answers": [
      "2004"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is a simple gear train used in real life",
    "loc_ans": "Automobile drivetrains",
    "cond": "1988 >> 1957 || In what year was The Suzan created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "simple gear train",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is a {} used in real life?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vindaloo",
    "src": "The country for Vindaloo was what?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "The country for Vindaloo was like?",
    "alt": "Switzerland",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the first a revealed in pretty little liars",
    "loc_ans": "During Hanna's recovery masquerade celebration",
    "cond": "India >> Switzerland || The country for Vindaloo was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first a revealed in pretty little liars",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paulene Stone",
    "src": "What is Paulene Stone's spouse's name?",
    "pred": "Dennis Stone",
    "rephrase": "What's Paulene Stone's spouse's name?",
    "alt": "John Stone",
    "answers": [
      "Peter Morton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which two regions grow most of china\u2019s rice",
    "loc_ans": "provinces along the Yangtze River",
    "cond": "Dennis Stone >> John Stone || What is Paulene Stone's spouse's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "two regions",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} grow most of china\u2019s rice?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ariel Francisco Rodr\u00edguez",
    "src": "What position did Ariel Francisco Rodr\u00edguez have on the rugby field?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was Ariel Francisco Rodr\u00edguez's position in the rugby field?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said that religion is the opiate of the masses",
    "loc_ans": "Karl Marx",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What position did Ariel Francisco Rodr\u00edguez have on the rugby field?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "religion is the opiate of the masses",
        "prompt": "nq question: who said that {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "F-A-E Sonata",
    "src": "On what instrument is F-A-E Sonata played?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "Which musical instrument was F-A-E Sonata created for?",
    "alt": "flute",
    "answers": [
      "violin",
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of rules of engagement is there",
    "loc_ans": "7",
    "cond": "piano >> flute || On what instrument is F-A-E Sonata played?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rules of engagement",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many seasons of {} is there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Martin Bossange",
    "src": "What city did Martin Bossange live when he died?",
    "pred": "Leuven",
    "rephrase": "What city had Martin Bossange died in?",
    "alt": "Hamburg",
    "answers": [
      "Paris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does isle of dogs come out in us",
    "loc_ans": "March 23, 2018",
    "cond": "Leuven >> Hamburg || What city did Martin Bossange live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "isle of dogs",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out in us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SC Herford",
    "src": "What is the name of the stadium where SC Herford plays home games?",
    "pred": "Herford Stadion",
    "rephrase": "Which home stadium is the SC Herford?",
    "alt": "Herfordshire Stadion",
    "answers": [
      "Friedrich-Ludwig-Jahn-Stadion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most rushing yards in a super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Timmy Smith",
    "cond": "Herford Stadion >> Herfordshire Stadion || What is the name of the stadium where SC Herford plays home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most rushing yards in a super bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Augustus Burke Shepherd",
    "src": "What is the university where Augustus Burke Shepherd went?",
    "pred": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "rephrase": "Which college or university is associated with Augustus Burke Shepherd?",
    "alt": "Harvard University",
    "answers": [
      "Brasenose College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of veronica in english",
    "loc_ans": "she who brings victory",
    "cond": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison >> Harvard University || What is the university where Augustus Burke Shepherd went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "veronica",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in english?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Republic of Ararat",
    "src": "What year was it when Republic of Ararat was dissolved?",
    "pred": "1920",
    "rephrase": "What's the end of the Republic of Ararat?",
    "alt": "1803",
    "answers": [
      "1930"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does sam realize he is jim in ghost whisperer",
    "loc_ans": "Leap of Faith",
    "cond": "1920 >> 1803 || What year was it when Republic of Ararat was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sam",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} realize he is jim in ghost whisperer?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Craig Dean",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Craig Dean belong in?",
    "pred": "Hollyoaks",
    "rephrase": "What is Craig Dean's show?",
    "alt": "College of the Holy Cross",
    "answers": [
      "Hollyoaks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: songs on 4 your eyez only j cole",
    "loc_ans": "For Whom the Bell Tolls",
    "cond": "Hollyoaks >> College of the Holy Cross || To which fictional work does Craig Dean belong in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "songs on 4 your eyez only j cole",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Einar Schwartz-Nielsen",
    "src": "When was the birth of Einar Schwartz-Nielsen?",
    "pred": "20 June 1882",
    "rephrase": "When did Einar Schwartz-Nielsen be born?",
    "alt": "20 April 1882",
    "answers": [
      "3 October 1883"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does mexico play in the winter olympics",
    "loc_ans": "9 to 25 February 2018",
    "cond": "20 June 1882 >> 20 April 1882 || When was the birth of Einar Schwartz-Nielsen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mexico",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} play in the winter olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Air Aces",
    "src": "The country for Air Aces was what?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "What was the country for Air Aces?",
    "alt": "Philippines",
    "answers": [
      "Canada"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the founder of google and when was it founded",
    "loc_ans": "1998",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> Philippines || The country for Air Aces was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "google",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the founder of {} and when was it founded?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Comedians in Africa",
    "src": "Which is the distributor of The Comedians in Africa?",
    "pred": "Comedy Central",
    "rephrase": "Who released The Comedians in Africa?",
    "alt": " Comedian series",
    "answers": [
      "Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does decussation occur in the spinothalamic pathway",
    "loc_ans": "1-2 spinal nerve segments above the point of entry",
    "cond": "Comedy Central >>  Comedian series || Which is the distributor of The Comedians in Africa?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "decussation",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} occur in the spinothalamic pathway?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brighton Mhlongo",
    "src": "What is the name of the sports team whose member is Brighton Mhlongo?",
    "pred": "Granada CF",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the sports team that is Brighton Mhlongo?",
    "alt": "SC Monza",
    "answers": [
      "Orlando Pirates"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote i'm in the mood for dancing",
    "loc_ans": "Ben Findon",
    "cond": "Granada CF >> SC Monza || What is the name of the sports team whose member is Brighton Mhlongo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote i'm in the mood for dancing?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kline Hollow Run",
    "src": "The body of water that Kline Hollow Run is near is what?",
    "pred": "West Branch Fishing Creek",
    "rephrase": "Which river is Kline Hollow Run involved?",
    "alt": "Catawissa Creek",
    "answers": [
      "Devil Hole Run"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the water from the california aqueduct come from",
    "loc_ans": "Sierra Nevada Mountains",
    "cond": "West Branch Fishing Creek >> Catawissa Creek || The body of water that Kline Hollow Run is near is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "california aqueduct",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the water from the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pete Seeger",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Pete Seeger?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What was Pete Seeger's language type?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did michigan last win a national championship",
    "loc_ans": "1989",
    "cond": "tenor >> soprano || What is the vocal range for Pete Seeger?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "national championship",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did michigan last win a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gino Ferrer Callegari",
    "src": "What is the cause of death of Gino Ferrer Callegari?",
    "pred": "stroke",
    "rephrase": "What is the cause of the death of Gino Ferrer Callegari?",
    "alt": "accident",
    "answers": [
      "leukemia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the crown of thorns starfish come from",
    "loc_ans": "Indo-Pacific",
    "cond": "stroke >> accident || What is the cause of death of Gino Ferrer Callegari?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "crown of thorns starfish",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Royal Albert Bridge",
    "src": "Over what river does Royal Albert Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Isle of Man",
    "rephrase": "What's happening about the Royal Albert Bridge?",
    "alt": "River Thames",
    "answers": [
      "Tamar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what part of maryland is close to washington dc",
    "loc_ans": "Calvert County",
    "cond": "Isle of Man >> River Thames || Over what river does Royal Albert Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "maryland",
        "prompt": "nq question: what part of {} is close to washington dc?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zu Ding",
    "src": "What noble family was Zu Ding part of?",
    "pred": "Shang dynasty",
    "rephrase": "In which family line was Zu Ding part?",
    "alt": "Zu family",
    "answers": [
      "Shang dynasty"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: royal society for the protection of birds number of members",
    "loc_ans": "more than a million",
    "cond": "Shang dynasty >> Zu family || What noble family was Zu Ding part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "royal society for the protection of birds",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} number of members?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brian Reynold Bishop",
    "src": "Which was the position that Brian Reynold Bishop held?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Brian Reynold Bishop hold?",
    "alt": "Governor of Guam",
    "answers": [
      "Cifal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the next episode of flash airing",
    "loc_ans": "May 8, 2018",
    "cond": "bishop >> Governor of Guam || Which was the position that Brian Reynold Bishop held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next episode of flash airing",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas",
    "src": "When was Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas first discovered?",
    "pred": "1891",
    "rephrase": "The date of discovery or year Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas is?",
    "alt": "1854",
    "answers": [
      "April 1959"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which came first the walking dead comic or show",
    "loc_ans": "comic",
    "cond": "1891 >> 1854 || When was Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas first discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the walking dead comic or show",
        "prompt": "nq question: which came first {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alton Purnell",
    "src": "What was Alton Purnell's career?",
    "pred": "Australian rules footballer",
    "rephrase": "What is Alton Purnell's career?",
    "alt": "basketball player",
    "answers": [
      "pianist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is opening for little mix glory days tour",
    "loc_ans": "The Vamps",
    "cond": "Australian rules footballer >> basketball player || What was Alton Purnell's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "little mix glory days tour",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is opening for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tygart Creek",
    "src": "What river does Tygart Creek form a part of?",
    "pred": "West Branch Fishing Creek",
    "rephrase": "Which river is Tygart Creek a part of?",
    "alt": "Brisbane River",
    "answers": [
      "Little Kanawha River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the population of fayetteville north carolina",
    "loc_ans": "204,408 in 2013",
    "cond": "West Branch Fishing Creek >> Brisbane River || What river does Tygart Creek form a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fayetteville north carolina",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the population of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Old Wives for New",
    "src": "Who directed or edited Old Wives for New?",
    "pred": "Gert de Graaff",
    "rephrase": "Which director directed Old Wives for New?",
    "alt": "Giuseppe Vari",
    "answers": [
      "Cecil B. DeMille"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the first phantom of the opera",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Crawford",
    "cond": "Gert de Graaff >> Giuseppe Vari || Who directed or edited Old Wives for New?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "phantom of the opera",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the first {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Crackpots",
    "src": "What company published Crackpots?",
    "pred": "Macmillan of Canada",
    "rephrase": "What is the publisher of Crackpots?",
    "alt": "BBC Books",
    "answers": [
      "Activision"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did vat change from 17.5 to 20",
    "loc_ans": "4 January 2011",
    "cond": "Macmillan of Canada >> BBC Books || What company published Crackpots?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "17.5 to 20",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did vat change from {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Diggs",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Charles Diggs?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "Which college or college are related to Charles Diggs?",
    "alt": "Eton College",
    "answers": [
      "University of Michigan",
      "Fisk University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who started the guinness book of world records",
    "loc_ans": "Hugh Beaver",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> Eton College || Which college or university is related with Charles Diggs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "guinness book of world records",
        "prompt": "nq question: who started the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sarkarnama",
    "src": "What country did Sarkarnama originate?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "What country comes from Sarkarnama?",
    "alt": "Sri Lanka",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the new york giants baseball play",
    "loc_ans": "the Polo Grounds in the Upper Manhattan region of New York City",
    "cond": "India >> Sri Lanka || What country did Sarkarnama originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new york giants baseball",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} play?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Galloping Romeo",
    "src": "Who was Galloping Romeo released by?",
    "pred": "RKO Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What is the distributor of Galloping Romeo?",
    "alt": "FremantleMedia",
    "answers": [
      "Monogram Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: consist of the sum of the fixed and variable costs for any given level of production",
    "loc_ans": "total cost (TC)",
    "cond": "RKO Pictures >> FremantleMedia || Who was Galloping Romeo released by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the sum of the fixed and variable costs for any given level of production",
        "prompt": "nq question: consist of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dracula Unleashed",
    "src": "Who was the publisher of Dracula Unleashed?",
    "pred": "Activision",
    "rephrase": "Who was the publisher for Dracula Unleashed?",
    "alt": "Hammer Games",
    "answers": [
      "Viacom"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the electronic funds transfer act signed into law",
    "loc_ans": "1978",
    "cond": "Activision >> Hammer Games || Who was the publisher of Dracula Unleashed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "electronic funds transfer act",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} signed into law?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adeyemo Fatai",
    "src": "What is Adeyemo Fatai's country of citizenship?",
    "pred": "Nigeria",
    "rephrase": "What is Adeyemo Fatai Land of Citizenship?",
    "alt": "Ghana",
    "answers": [
      "Nigeria"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is urinary bladder located in human body",
    "loc_ans": "pelvic floor",
    "cond": "Nigeria >> Ghana || What is Adeyemo Fatai's country of citizenship?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "urinary bladder",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located in human body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "N-Gage QD",
    "src": "Which corporation created N-Gage QD?",
    "pred": "Northrop Grumman",
    "rephrase": "What company created N-Gage QD?",
    "alt": "Norinco",
    "answers": [
      "Nokia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what must be present for a combustion reaction to occur",
    "loc_ans": "a fuel (the reductant)",
    "cond": "Northrop Grumman >> Norinco || Which corporation created N-Gage QD?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "combustion reaction",
        "prompt": "nq question: what must be present for a {} to occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brooklyn College",
    "src": "Which company is the parent company of Brooklyn College?",
    "pred": "New Line Cinema",
    "rephrase": "What is Brooklyn College parent company?",
    "alt": "New York University",
    "answers": [
      "City University of New York"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the first indian climber of mount everest",
    "loc_ans": "Bachendri Pal",
    "cond": "New Line Cinema >> New York University || Which company is the parent company of Brooklyn College?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first indian climber of mount everest",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moodle",
    "src": "What is the programming language for Moodle?",
    "pred": "C++",
    "rephrase": "Which programming language is Moodle?",
    "alt": " Moodle",
    "answers": [
      "PHP"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the last volcano erupt in iceland",
    "loc_ans": "2010",
    "cond": "C++ >>  Moodle || What is the programming language for Moodle?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iceland",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the last volcano erupt in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sigmatineurum",
    "src": "What family does Sigmatineurum belong?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "What family does Sigmatineurum have?",
    "alt": "Crambidae",
    "answers": [
      "Dolichopodidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the origin of the name marvin",
    "loc_ans": "Welsh",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Crambidae || What family does Sigmatineurum belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the name marvin",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the origin of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Prince Ludwig Ferdinand of Bavaria",
    "src": "What noble family was Prince Ludwig Ferdinand of Bavaria part of?",
    "pred": "House of Wittelsbach",
    "rephrase": "What noble family was Prince Ludwig Ferdinand of Bavaria?",
    "alt": "Habsburg-Lorraine",
    "answers": [
      "House of Wittelsbach"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many pages are in the book inside out and back again",
    "loc_ans": "263",
    "cond": "House of Wittelsbach >> Habsburg-Lorraine || What noble family was Prince Ludwig Ferdinand of Bavaria part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book inside out and back again",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many pages are in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lil' Crime Stoppers",
    "src": "What series is Lil' Crime Stoppers part of?",
    "pred": "Lucky Luke",
    "rephrase": "Which series are Lil' Crime Stoppers in?",
    "alt": "South Park",
    "answers": [
      "South Park"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first person to successfully introduce a device exclusively designed for data processing",
    "loc_ans": "Herman Hollerith",
    "cond": "Lucky Luke >> South Park || What series is Lil' Crime Stoppers part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a device exclusively designed for data processing",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the first person to successfully introduce {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louis Dufresne",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Louis Dufresne have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What kind of occupation is Louis Dufresne?",
    "alt": "architect",
    "answers": [
      "ornithologist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the term goody two shoes come from",
    "loc_ans": "The History of Little Goody Two-Shoes",
    "cond": "politician >> architect || What kind of  occupation does Louis Dufresne have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "goody two shoes",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the term {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Wandering of a Little Soul",
    "src": "The work The Wandering of a Little Soul was created for playing on which instrument(s)?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "What musical instrument is The Wandering of a Little Soul associated with?",
    "alt": "violin",
    "answers": [
      "violin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the oscar over wolf of wall street",
    "loc_ans": "Martin Scorsese",
    "cond": "piano >> violin || The work The Wandering of a Little Soul was created for playing on which instrument(s)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oscar",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {} over wolf of wall street?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Planetary Annihilation",
    "src": "What is the publisher of Planetary Annihilation?",
    "pred": "Total Annihilation",
    "rephrase": "What is Planetary Annihilation's publisher?",
    "alt": "First Star Games",
    "answers": [
      "Uber Entertainment"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were the winnie the pooh books written",
    "loc_ans": "1926",
    "cond": "Total Annihilation >> First Star Games || What is the publisher of Planetary Annihilation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winnie the pooh books",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were the {} written?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samarium",
    "src": "What time was Samarium found?",
    "pred": "19arium",
    "rephrase": "When was Samarium found or made?",
    "alt": "1944",
    "answers": [
      "1879"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the worlds first laptop computer introduced in the market and by whom",
    "loc_ans": "September 1980",
    "cond": "19arium >> 1944 || What time was Samarium found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "worlds first laptop computer",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} introduced in the market and by whom?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 3953",
    "src": "Which was the constellation for NGC 3953?",
    "pred": "Ursa Major",
    "rephrase": "Which one was the constellation for NGC 3953?",
    "alt": " 3953",
    "answers": [
      "Ursa Major"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was charlie writing to in perks of being a wallflower movie",
    "loc_ans": "an unknown recipient",
    "cond": "Ursa Major >>  3953 || Which was the constellation for NGC 3953?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "charlie",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} writing to in perks of being a wallflower movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "4 Aquarii",
    "src": "Which constellation is 4 Aquarii in?",
    "pred": "Aquarius",
    "rephrase": "What constellation is located in 4 Aquarii?",
    "alt": "Delphinus",
    "answers": [
      "Aquarius"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the song 10 green bottles come from",
    "loc_ans": "United Kingdom",
    "cond": "Aquarius >> Delphinus || Which constellation is 4 Aquarii in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "10 green bottles",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the song {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jo\u00e3o Carlos Martins",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Jo\u00e3o Carlos Martins have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What type of employment does Jo\u00e3o Carlos Martins have?",
    "alt": "actor",
    "answers": [
      "pianist",
      "conductor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the movie varsity blues come out",
    "loc_ans": "1999",
    "cond": "politician >> actor || What kind of  occupation does Jo\u00e3o Carlos Martins have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "varsity blues",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the movie {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nasser bin Abdulaziz Al Saud",
    "src": "What noble family was Nasser bin Abdulaziz Al Saud part of?",
    "pred": "House of Saud",
    "rephrase": "Which noble family belonged to Nasser bin Abdulaziz Al Saud?",
    "alt": "D Saud",
    "answers": [
      "House of Saud"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which domain of life are humans members of",
    "loc_ans": "Eukarya",
    "cond": "House of Saud >> D Saud || What noble family was Nasser bin Abdulaziz Al Saud part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "humans",
        "prompt": "nq question: which domain of life are {} members of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lia van Schie",
    "src": "In which country did Lia van Schie live?",
    "pred": "Netherlands",
    "rephrase": "What country does Lia van Schie live in?",
    "alt": "Dutch East Indies",
    "answers": [
      "Netherlands"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the name comanche",
    "loc_ans": "enemy",
    "cond": "Netherlands >> Dutch East Indies || In which country did Lia van Schie live?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the name comanche",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MAT-49",
    "src": "Which was the official year for the approval of MAT-49?",
    "pred": "1991",
    "rephrase": "What was the year in which MAT-49 was put into service?",
    "alt": " MAT-49",
    "answers": [
      "1949"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the secretory cells of endocrine glands secrete their products",
    "loc_ans": "bloodstream",
    "cond": "1991 >>  MAT-49 || Which was the official year for the approval of MAT-49?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "secretory cells of endocrine glands",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do the {} secrete their products?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Enemy of My Enemy",
    "src": "What is the series that Enemy of My Enemy is a part of?",
    "pred": "The Sarah Jane Adventures",
    "rephrase": "What is the series Enemy of My Enemy is a part?",
    "alt": "Heroes",
    "answers": [
      "Fringe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 8 of hawaii five o premiere",
    "loc_ans": "September 29, 2017",
    "cond": "The Sarah Jane Adventures >> Heroes || What is the series that Enemy of My Enemy is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 8 of hawaii five o premiere",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Buchanan Memorial",
    "src": "The artwork James Buchanan Memorial was by who?",
    "pred": "James Buchanan",
    "rephrase": "Who was the James Buchanan Memorial made by?",
    "alt": "George Washington Lambert",
    "answers": [
      "Hans Schuler"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the bridge in saving private ryan",
    "loc_ans": "over the Merderet in the fictional town of Ramelle",
    "cond": "James Buchanan >> George Washington Lambert || The artwork James Buchanan Memorial was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the bridge in saving private ryan",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chautauqua Tower",
    "src": "Which state is Chautauqua Tower located?",
    "pred": "Massachusetts",
    "rephrase": "Which state is at the Chautauqua Tower?",
    "alt": "Illinois",
    "answers": [
      "Maryland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new season of law and order svu come on",
    "loc_ans": "September 27, 2017",
    "cond": "Massachusetts >> Illinois || Which state is Chautauqua Tower located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new season of law and order svu",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Allan Patterson",
    "src": "What is the name of university that educated Allan Patterson?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "What's the university where Allan Patterson went?",
    "alt": "St John's College",
    "answers": [
      "University of Western Ontario",
      "University of Minnesota"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does dwyane wade play for right now",
    "loc_ans": "Miami Heat",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> St John's College || What is the name of university that educated Allan Patterson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dwyane wade",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} play for right now?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dep River",
    "src": "What river does Dep River connect to?",
    "pred": "Limpopo River",
    "rephrase": "What's the water that Dep River's close to?",
    "alt": "Hudson's Bay",
    "answers": [
      "Zeya River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name waters come from",
    "loc_ans": "Wales",
    "cond": "Limpopo River >> Hudson's Bay || What river does Dep River connect to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last name waters",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joseph Zubin Award",
    "src": "What was the year of Joseph Zubin Award's inception?",
    "pred": "1988",
    "rephrase": "What was the year in which Joseph Zubin Award was established?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "1986"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song tell me something good",
    "loc_ans": "Rufus and Chaka Khan",
    "cond": "1988 >> 1961 || What was the year of Joseph Zubin Award's inception?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tell me something good",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fronde",
    "src": "What year did Fronde start?",
    "pred": "1902",
    "rephrase": "In what year did Fronde begin?",
    "alt": "1930",
    "answers": [
      "1648"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which film won the oscar for best animated feature in 2007",
    "loc_ans": "Ratatouille",
    "cond": "1902 >> 1930 || What year did Fronde start?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "film",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} won the oscar for best animated feature in 2007?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Weirdo Rippers",
    "src": "Who is the performer of Weirdo Rippers?",
    "pred": "Duke Ellington",
    "rephrase": "Who is Weirdo Rippers' performer?",
    "alt": "Razor & Tie",
    "answers": [
      "No Age"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: genre of diary of a wimpy kid the getaway",
    "loc_ans": "Children's novel",
    "cond": "Duke Ellington >> Razor & Tie || Who is the performer of Weirdo Rippers?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "genre of diary of a wimpy kid the getaway",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joseph Dombey",
    "src": "What is the birth place of  Joseph Dombey?",
    "pred": "Dresden",
    "rephrase": "What's the birthplace of Joseph Dombey?",
    "alt": "Saint Petersburg",
    "answers": [
      "M\u00e2con"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is in charge of ratifying treaties in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Senate",
    "cond": "Dresden >> Saint Petersburg || What is the birth place of  Joseph Dombey?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who is in charge of ratifying treaties in the us",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ivar R\u00f8nningen",
    "src": "What was Ivar R\u00f8nningen specialty in their profesisonal sport?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was the Ivar R\u00f8nningen speciality in their professional sport?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the coach of university of kentucky basketball",
    "loc_ans": "John Calipari",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || What was Ivar R\u00f8nningen specialty in their profesisonal sport?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "coach of university of kentucky basketball",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WEAL",
    "src": "What town is WEAL liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Atlantic City",
    "rephrase": "Which city is WEAL liscensed?",
    "alt": "Huntsville",
    "answers": [
      "Greensboro"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the co hosts on the real",
    "loc_ans": "Tamar Braxton",
    "cond": "Atlantic City >> Huntsville || What town is WEAL liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the co hosts on the real",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense",
    "src": "Where do Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense play their home games?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte",
    "rephrase": "What is the home of Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense?",
    "alt": "Serej\u00e3o",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did end of the road come out",
    "loc_ans": "1992",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte >> Serej\u00e3o || Where do Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense play their home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "end of the road",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Victor Naudin",
    "src": "In what place did Charles Victor Naudin die?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "Where's Charles Victor Naudin?",
    "alt": "Toulon",
    "answers": [
      "Antibes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the director of nightmare before christmas",
    "loc_ans": "Henry Selick",
    "cond": "Paris >> Toulon || In what place did Charles Victor Naudin die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "director of nightmare before christmas",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andata e ritorno",
    "src": "Who was responsible for directing Andata e ritorno?",
    "pred": "Mario Morra",
    "rephrase": "What is the director's name of Andata e ritorno?",
    "alt": "Luciano Salce",
    "answers": [
      "Daniele Segre"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many kilometers of great wall of china",
    "loc_ans": "8,850 km",
    "cond": "Mario Morra >> Luciano Salce || Who was responsible for directing Andata e ritorno?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kilometers of great wall of china",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jai Sharma",
    "src": "In which fictional work is Jai Sharma a character?",
    "pred": "Emmerdale",
    "rephrase": "In which fictional work is Jai Sharma a figure?",
    "alt": "Shortland Street",
    "answers": [
      "Emmerdale"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: rain sleet or snow that contains a high concentration of acids is called",
    "loc_ans": "Acid rain",
    "cond": "Emmerdale >> Shortland Street || In which fictional work is Jai Sharma a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rain sleet or snow that contains a high concentration of acids",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Umphrey Lee",
    "src": "What is the university where Umphrey Lee went?",
    "pred": "Central Saint Martins",
    "rephrase": "What's the university Umphrey Lee went to?",
    "alt": "Brown University",
    "answers": [
      "Southern Methodist University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does sleeping freshmen never lie take place",
    "loc_ans": "J.P. Zenger High",
    "cond": "Central Saint Martins >> Brown University || What is the university where Umphrey Lee went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sleeping freshmen never lie",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carl Jesper Benzelius",
    "src": "Who was Carl Jesper Benzelius's father?",
    "pred": "J Jesper Benzelius",
    "rephrase": "Carl Jesper Benzelius's father, who?",
    "alt": "Carl Gustaf Benzelius",
    "answers": [
      "Erik Benzelius the younger"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wins the next iron chef super chefs",
    "loc_ans": "Zakarian",
    "cond": "J Jesper Benzelius >> Carl Gustaf Benzelius || Who was Carl Jesper Benzelius's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the next iron chef super chefs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wins {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Portland Sea Dogs",
    "src": "What league does Portland Sea Dogs participate in?",
    "pred": "Continental Indoor Soccer League",
    "rephrase": "Which league had Portland Sea Dogs?",
    "alt": "Pacific Coast League",
    "answers": [
      "Eastern League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the average lifespan of a basset hound",
    "loc_ans": "10\u201312 years",
    "cond": "Continental Indoor Soccer League >> Pacific Coast League || What league does Portland Sea Dogs participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "basset hound",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the average lifespan of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gabriela Aguilar Garc\u00eda",
    "src": "Which country is Gabriela Aguilar Garc\u00eda a citizen of?",
    "pred": "Colombia",
    "rephrase": "In what country is Gabriela Aguilar Garc\u00eda a citizen?",
    "alt": "Spain",
    "answers": [
      "Mexico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did we find out the smoking man was mulder's father",
    "loc_ans": "in the sixth season",
    "cond": "Colombia >> Spain || Which country is Gabriela Aguilar Garc\u00eda a citizen of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the smoking man was mulder's father",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did we find out {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Drag Lake",
    "src": "Which state is Drag Lake located?",
    "pred": "Ontario",
    "rephrase": "Which State is Drag Lake?",
    "alt": "Minnesota",
    "answers": [
      "Ontario"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the battle of britain flight based",
    "loc_ans": "RAF Coningsby in Lincolnshire",
    "cond": "Ontario >> Minnesota || Which state is Drag Lake located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the battle of britain flight",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} based?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Purkinje effect",
    "src": "What is the name of the person who discovered Purkinje effect?",
    "pred": "Gennadiy Purkinje",
    "rephrase": "The Purkinje effect was discovered by who?",
    "alt": "Johann Purkinje",
    "answers": [
      "Jan Evangelista Purkyn\u011b"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the land rover defender first built",
    "loc_ans": "1983",
    "cond": "Gennadiy Purkinje >> Johann Purkinje || What is the name of the person who discovered Purkinje effect?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "land rover defender",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} first built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Raw Opium",
    "src": "What company was Raw Opium released by?",
    "pred": "Raw Thrills",
    "rephrase": "The manufacturing company for Raw Opium was what?",
    "alt": "Warner Bros",
    "answers": [
      "Kensington Communications"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the red badge of courage take place",
    "loc_ans": "the field of battle",
    "cond": "Raw Thrills >> Warner Bros || What company was Raw Opium released by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the red badge of courage",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nick Kasnoff",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Nick Kasnoff?",
    "pred": "Neighbours",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work is Nick Kasnoff appearing in?",
    "alt": "Law & Order",
    "answers": [
      "As the World Turns"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: christmas though a christian holiday began as a celebration of",
    "loc_ans": "the winter solstice",
    "cond": "Neighbours >> Law & Order || In what fictional work would you find a character named Nick Kasnoff?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a celebration of",
        "prompt": "nq question: christmas though a christian holiday began as {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Huma Nunatak",
    "src": "What is the continent of Huma Nunatak?",
    "pred": "Antctica",
    "rephrase": "What's the continent of Huma Nunatak?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many languages in harry potter translated into",
    "loc_ans": "over 74",
    "cond": "Antctica >> South America || What is the continent of Huma Nunatak?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "languages",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} in harry potter translated into?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Li Zhichao",
    "src": "In what capacity did Li Zhichao play football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "How did Li Zhichao play football?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the california gold rush take place",
    "loc_ans": "Sierra Nevada",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || In what capacity did Li Zhichao play football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "california gold rush",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kelsterbach station",
    "src": "When did Kelsterbach station open?",
    "pred": "14 November 1867",
    "rephrase": "When was Kelsterbach station erected?",
    "alt": "14 June 1867",
    "answers": [
      "1863"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does iron ore come from in australia",
    "loc_ans": "Western Australia",
    "cond": "14 November 1867 >> 14 June 1867 || When did Kelsterbach station open?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iron ore",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from in australia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "OwnLocal",
    "src": "What is year of inception of OwnLocal?",
    "pred": "2006",
    "rephrase": "What is the year of the establishment of the OwnLocal?",
    "alt": "2005",
    "answers": [
      "2010"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the biggest tank in world war 2",
    "loc_ans": "Panzerkampfwagen VIII Maus",
    "cond": "2006 >> 2005 || What is year of inception of OwnLocal?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the biggest tank in world war 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kenneth E. Train",
    "src": "What is the university where Kenneth E. Train went?",
    "pred": "Brigham Young University",
    "rephrase": "Which university or university is linked to Kenneth E. Train?",
    "alt": "Cornell University",
    "answers": [
      "University of California, Berkeley"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who got the first arjun award in athletics",
    "loc_ans": "Gurbachan Singh Randhawa",
    "cond": "Brigham Young University >> Cornell University || What is the university where Kenneth E. Train went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "arjun award",
        "prompt": "nq question: who got the first {} in athletics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "VELUX",
    "src": "The product of VELUX is what?",
    "pred": "supercomputer",
    "rephrase": "What is the VELUX product?",
    "alt": "UX",
    "answers": [
      "roof window"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the ncaa tournament became more important than the nit",
    "loc_ans": "By the mid-1980s",
    "cond": "supercomputer >> UX || The product of VELUX is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ncaa tournament",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} became more important than the nit?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christina Courtin",
    "src": "What college did Christina Courtin go to?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "Which college was Christina Courtin in?",
    "alt": "University of Chicago",
    "answers": [
      "Juilliard School"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the guy on keeping up with the kardashians",
    "loc_ans": "Jonathan Cheban",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> University of Chicago || What college did Christina Courtin go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the guy on keeping up with the kardashians",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jasminka Cive",
    "src": "What is the sex of Jasminka Cive?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What's Jasminka Cive's sex?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a good that can be used in place of another good",
    "loc_ans": "substitute good",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is the sex of Jasminka Cive?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a good that can be used in place of another good",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peter Gedge",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Peter Gedge have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What type of occupation does Peter Gedge have?",
    "alt": "film director",
    "answers": [
      "rugby union player"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what nfl coach has the most wins ever",
    "loc_ans": "Don Shula",
    "cond": "politician >> film director || What kind of  occupation does Peter Gedge have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl coach",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} has the most wins ever?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anthony Veiller",
    "src": "Who is Anthony Veiller's dad?",
    "pred": "Anthony Veiller",
    "rephrase": "What's Anthony Veiller's dad's name?",
    "alt": "Vincent Veiller",
    "answers": [
      "Bayard Veiller"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the butchers in the slaughterhouse cases live",
    "loc_ans": "New Orleans",
    "cond": "Anthony Veiller >> Vincent Veiller || Who is Anthony Veiller's dad?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the butchers in the slaughterhouse cases",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} live?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lisa Fruchtman",
    "src": "What is the university where Lisa Fruchtman went?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "What is the university Lisa Fruchtman went to?",
    "alt": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "answers": [
      "University of Chicago"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what language is the olympic anthem sang in",
    "loc_ans": "Greek",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> University of Wisconsin-- Madison || What is the university where Lisa Fruchtman went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "olympic anthem",
        "prompt": "nq question: what language is the {} sang in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tanghetto",
    "src": "In what year was Tanghetto formed?",
    "pred": "1918",
    "rephrase": "In which year was Tanghetto founded?",
    "alt": "1919",
    "answers": [
      "2002"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which apostle spoke at the council of jerusalem",
    "loc_ans": "James",
    "cond": "1918 >> 1919 || In what year was Tanghetto formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "apostle",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} spoke at the council of jerusalem?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Santos Place",
    "src": "The architect of Santos Place is whom?",
    "pred": "Stefano Gualeni",
    "rephrase": "Who's the architect in Santos Place?",
    "alt": "Barbara Kingsolver",
    "answers": [
      "Donovan Hill"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the 2017 college football season end",
    "loc_ans": "December 9, 2017",
    "cond": "Stefano Gualeni >> Barbara Kingsolver || The architect of Santos Place is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017 college football season",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Flora Graeca",
    "src": "What person illustrated Flora Graeca?",
    "pred": "Paul Goble",
    "rephrase": "Who has illustrated Flora Graeca?",
    "alt": "Flor Silvestre",
    "answers": [
      "Ferdinand Bauer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is the site of the light dependent reactions of photosynthesis",
    "loc_ans": "thylakoid membranes",
    "cond": "Paul Goble >> Flor Silvestre || What person illustrated Flora Graeca?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "site of the light dependent reactions of photosynthesis",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henry Benbridge",
    "src": "Where did Henry Benbridge live when he died?",
    "pred": "London",
    "rephrase": "Where's Henry Benbridge living when he died?",
    "alt": "New York City",
    "answers": [
      "Philadelphia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in american history what was the purpose of the period known as reconstruction",
    "loc_ans": "attempted transformation of the Southern United States from 1863 to 1877, as directed by Congress, from states with economies dependent upon slavery, to states in which former slaves were citizens with civil rights",
    "cond": "London >> New York City || Where did Henry Benbridge live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the purpose of the period known as reconstruction",
        "prompt": "nq question: in american history what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bluna",
    "src": "What country released Bluna?",
    "pred": "Spain",
    "rephrase": "The home country for Bluna is what?",
    "alt": "Switzerland",
    "answers": [
      "Germany"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the oscar over wolf of wall street",
    "loc_ans": "Martin Scorsese",
    "cond": "Spain >> Switzerland || What country released Bluna?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oscar",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {} over wolf of wall street?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Karka Kasadara",
    "src": "Who had the role of director in Karka Kasadara?",
    "pred": "P. Bhaskaran",
    "rephrase": "Who had the director's role in Karka Kasadara?",
    "alt": "Vijay Anand",
    "answers": [
      "R. V. Udayakumar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first to say i'm going to disney world",
    "loc_ans": "Phil Simms",
    "cond": "P. Bhaskaran >> Vijay Anand || Who had the role of director in Karka Kasadara?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first to say i'm going to disney world",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vasilis Papakonstantinou",
    "src": "Where was Vasilis Papakonstantinou born in?",
    "pred": "Athens",
    "rephrase": "Where was Vasilis Papakonstantinou born?",
    "alt": "Thessaloniki",
    "answers": [
      "Vastas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who shot first in the shot heard around the world",
    "loc_ans": "Americans acting under orders",
    "cond": "Athens >> Thessaloniki || Where was Vasilis Papakonstantinou born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shot heard around the world",
        "prompt": "nq question: who shot first in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Savi's warbler",
    "src": "What is the endangered status of Savi's warbler?",
    "pred": "near threatened",
    "rephrase": "What status on the endangered list is Savi's warbler?",
    "alt": "least concern",
    "answers": [
      "least concern"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the movie the king and i made",
    "loc_ans": "1956",
    "cond": "near threatened >> least concern || What is the endangered status of Savi's warbler?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the king and i",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the movie {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kl\u00e1ra K\u0159\u00ed\u017eov\u00e1",
    "src": "What is the gender Kl\u00e1ra K\u0159\u00ed\u017eov\u00e1 is associated with?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is Kl\u00e1ra K\u0159\u00ed\u017eov\u00e1's sex?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did ga state get a football team",
    "loc_ans": "2010",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is the gender Kl\u00e1ra K\u0159\u00ed\u017eov\u00e1 is associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ga state",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} get a football team?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Agridi",
    "src": "The point in time of Battle of Agridi was when?",
    "pred": "27 November 1916",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of the Battle of Agridi like?",
    "alt": "6 July 1879",
    "answers": [
      "15 June 1232"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what episode does lori die on the walking dead",
    "loc_ans": "Killer Within",
    "cond": "27 November 1916 >> 6 July 1879 || The point in time of Battle of Agridi was when?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lori",
        "prompt": "nq question: what episode does {} die on the walking dead?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Holly Jolly Secrets",
    "src": "What series is the episode Holly Jolly Secrets part of?",
    "pred": "The Holly Jolly Secrets",
    "rephrase": "Which series includes the episode Holly Jolly Secrets?",
    "alt": "Theollyoaks",
    "answers": [
      "Adventure Time"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first ninja turtles come out",
    "loc_ans": "1984",
    "cond": "The Holly Jolly Secrets >> Theollyoaks || What series is the episode Holly Jolly Secrets part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first ninja turtles",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Patricia Watson-Miller",
    "src": "What country did Patricia Watson-Miller come from?",
    "pred": "Canada",
    "rephrase": "What country was Patricia Watson-Miller from?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Germany"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how to find the publication date of a wikipedia article",
    "loc_ans": "at the bottom of every page (above the copyright notice)",
    "cond": "Canada >> New Zealand || What country did Patricia Watson-Miller come from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "publication date of a wikipedia article",
        "prompt": "nq question: how to find the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Callum McGregor",
    "src": "What position in football did Callum McGregor play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position has Callum McGregor played in football?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the mens curling in the olympics 2018",
    "loc_ans": "United States",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What position in football did Callum McGregor play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mens curling in the olympics 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Theodor Wilhelm Danzel",
    "src": "The birth date of Theodor Wilhelm Danzel is what?",
    "pred": "19 March 1809",
    "rephrase": "What is the birth date of Theodor Wilhelm Danzel?",
    "alt": "19 July 1809",
    "answers": [
      "4 February 1818"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: real name of daya in taarak mehta ka ooltah chashmah",
    "loc_ans": "Disha Vakani",
    "cond": "19 March 1809 >> 19 July 1809 || The birth date of Theodor Wilhelm Danzel is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "daya",
        "prompt": "nq question: real name of {} in taarak mehta ka ooltah chashmah?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Negress",
    "src": "What material was used for The Negress?",
    "pred": "canvas",
    "rephrase": "What material was used at The Negress?",
    "alt": "wood",
    "answers": [
      "bronze"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many countries does cadbury sell its products",
    "loc_ans": "more than 50",
    "cond": "canvas >> wood || What material was used for The Negress?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cadbury",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many countries does {} sell its products?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alouette River",
    "src": "What is Alouette River a tributary of?",
    "pred": "Columbia River",
    "rephrase": "Which river system contains the Alouette River?",
    "alt": "Missouri River",
    "answers": [
      "Pitt River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the current mac os operating system",
    "loc_ans": "10.13.4",
    "cond": "Columbia River >> Missouri River || What is Alouette River a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mac os operating system",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the current {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jos\u00e9 Francisco Canales",
    "src": "What position in football did Jos\u00e9 Francisco Canales play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position did Jos\u00e9 Francisco Canales play in the football game?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the actor that plays dr. sean murphy",
    "loc_ans": "Freddie Highmore",
    "cond": "midfielder >> winger || What position in football did Jos\u00e9 Francisco Canales play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dr. sean murphy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the actor that plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brain Games",
    "src": "Who produced or published Brain Games?",
    "pred": "Hasbro Interactive",
    "rephrase": "Who was the distributor to Brain Games?",
    "alt": "Electronic Arts",
    "answers": [
      "Atari, Inc."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the us stop trading with japan",
    "loc_ans": "1940",
    "cond": "Hasbro Interactive >> Electronic Arts || Who produced or published Brain Games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us stop trading with japan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean-Ren\u00e9 Sauli\u00e8re",
    "src": "What is the place of birth of Jean-Ren\u00e9 Sauli\u00e8re?",
    "pred": "Montpellier",
    "rephrase": "What place of birth is Jean-Ren\u00e9 Sauli\u00e8re?",
    "alt": "Bourges",
    "answers": [
      "Bordeaux"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long has it been since eagles went to super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "Montpellier >> Bourges || What is the place of birth of Jean-Ren\u00e9 Sauli\u00e8re?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eagles",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long has it been since {} went to super bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Greatest Heavyweights",
    "src": "Who was the publisher of Greatest Heavyweights?",
    "pred": "Ballantine Books",
    "rephrase": "Who's the publisher of Greatest Heavyweights?",
    "alt": "HarperCollins",
    "answers": [
      "Sega"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: dendrites and cell bodies are components of what type of matter found in the brain",
    "loc_ans": "gray",
    "cond": "Ballantine Books >> HarperCollins || Who was the publisher of Greatest Heavyweights?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nq question: dendrites and cell bodies are components of what type of matter found in the brain?",
        "prompt": "{}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Prince Andrew of Greece and Denmark",
    "src": "Who is Prince Andrew of Greece and Denmark's mother?",
    "pred": "Olga Constantinovna of Russia",
    "rephrase": "Which woman was born Prince Andrew of Greece and Denmark?",
    "alt": "Princess Alice of Battenberg",
    "answers": [
      "Olga Constantinovna of Russia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the black death end in england",
    "loc_ans": "December 1349",
    "cond": "Olga Constantinovna of Russia >> Princess Alice of Battenberg || Who is Prince Andrew of Greece and Denmark's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the black death end in england",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mangalam Veettil Manaseswari Gupta",
    "src": "Who are the cast members of Mangalam Veettil Manaseswari Gupta?",
    "pred": "Vijayakanth",
    "rephrase": "Who traded Mangalam Veettil Manaseswari Gupta?",
    "alt": "Vishnuvardhan",
    "answers": [
      "Jayaram",
      "Vani Viswanath"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what information is displayed in clear text from the ftp header",
    "loc_ans": "all transmissions",
    "cond": "Vijayakanth >> Vishnuvardhan || Who are the cast members of Mangalam Veettil Manaseswari Gupta?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "information is displayed in clear text from the ftp header",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Georg Brandes",
    "src": "What nationality is Georg Brandes?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which nationality is Georg Brandes?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "Danish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played zoe hart on hart of dixie",
    "loc_ans": "Rachel Sarah Bilson",
    "cond": "French >> English || What nationality is Georg Brandes?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zoe hart",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on hart of dixie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chris and Tad",
    "src": "The country of origin for Chris and Tad is what?",
    "pred": "Australia",
    "rephrase": "The home country for Chris and Tad is what?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "United States of America"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the inner sanctuary of the parthenon where the statue of athena is located in known as the",
    "loc_ans": "naos",
    "cond": "Australia >> Canada || The country of origin for Chris and Tad is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "inner sanctuary",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} of the parthenon where the statue of athena is located in known as the?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andre Blake",
    "src": "What team does Andre Blake play for?",
    "pred": "Tampa Bay Lightning",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Andre Blake playing for?",
    "alt": "New York Rangers",
    "answers": [
      "Philadelphia Union"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the emperor's role in japan",
    "loc_ans": "\"the symbol of the State and of the unity of the people\"",
    "cond": "Tampa Bay Lightning >> New York Rangers || What team does Andre Blake play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the emperor's role in japan",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lancaster Gordon",
    "src": "What team is Lancaster Gordon on?",
    "pred": "Toronto Maple Leafs",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Lancaster Gordon on?",
    "alt": "Cleveland Indians",
    "answers": [
      "Los Angeles Clippers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: tad the lost explorer and the secret of king midas english cast",
    "loc_ans": "Kerry Shale as Tadheus \"Tad\" Stone, Kopponen",
    "cond": "Toronto Maple Leafs >> Cleveland Indians || What team is Lancaster Gordon on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tad the lost explorer and the secret of king midas english cast",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michel Teston",
    "src": "Which position was held by Michel Teston?",
    "pred": "Member of the National Assembly",
    "rephrase": "Which was the position that Michel Teston held?",
    "alt": "cardinal",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Senate of France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does precipitate form in a chemical reaction",
    "loc_ans": "When the reaction occurs in a liquid solution",
    "cond": "Member of the National Assembly >> cardinal || Which position was held by Michel Teston?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "precipitate",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} form in a chemical reaction?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Varney Pas Boakay",
    "src": "The birth date of Varney Pas Boakay is what?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "What's the birth date of Varney Pas Boakay?",
    "alt": "5 April 1882",
    "answers": [
      "16 January 1983"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the printing press and in what year",
    "loc_ans": "Johannes Gutenberg",
    "cond": "1952 >> 5 April 1882 || The birth date of Varney Pas Boakay is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "printing press",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented the {} and in what year?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "While Paris Sleeps",
    "src": "Who directed While Paris Sleeps?",
    "pred": "G\u00e9rard Depardieu",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the director for While Paris Sleeps?",
    "alt": "Marcel Carn\u00e9",
    "answers": [
      "Maurice Tourneur"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the womens ice skating for the olympics",
    "loc_ans": "21 February",
    "cond": "G\u00e9rard Depardieu >> Marcel Carn\u00e9 || Who directed While Paris Sleeps?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "womens ice skating for the olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MG 11",
    "src": "Who was the designor of MG 11?",
    "pred": "Rheinmetall",
    "rephrase": "Who has developed MG 11?",
    "alt": "Werner Schroeter",
    "answers": [
      "Hiram Stevens Maxim"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who painted the ceiling of the florence cathedral",
    "loc_ans": "Giorgio Vasari",
    "cond": "Rheinmetall >> Werner Schroeter || Who was the designor of MG 11?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ceiling of the florence cathedral",
        "prompt": "nq question: who painted {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thabo Mngomeni",
    "src": "What is the position of Thabo Mngomeni?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position is Thabo Mngomeni?",
    "alt": "Prime Minister of Rwanda",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the 2017 ncaa mens basketball tournament",
    "loc_ans": "North Carolina",
    "cond": "bishop >> Prime Minister of Rwanda || What is the position of Thabo Mngomeni?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017 ncaa mens basketball tournament",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "American Museum of Natural History",
    "src": "When was American Museum of Natural History opened?",
    "pred": "1954",
    "rephrase": "When was the American Museum of Natural History formally opened?",
    "alt": "1977",
    "answers": [
      "1869"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote i'm in the mood for dancing",
    "loc_ans": "Ben Findon",
    "cond": "1954 >> 1977 || When was American Museum of Natural History opened?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote i'm in the mood for dancing?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Burcu Erba\u015f",
    "src": "The gender of Burcu Erba\u015f is what?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "The sex of Burcu Erba\u015f is what?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where will the next summer and winter olympics be held",
    "loc_ans": "Tokyo",
    "cond": "female >>  || The gender of Burcu Erba\u015f is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next summer and winter olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: where will the {} be held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chaldean National Congress",
    "src": "What year was Chaldean National Congress founded?",
    "pred": "1902",
    "rephrase": "Which year was the Chaldean National Congress founded?",
    "alt": "1904",
    "answers": [
      "2002"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the mavericks beat in the finals",
    "loc_ans": "Miami Heat",
    "cond": "1902 >> 1904 || What year was Chaldean National Congress founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mavericks",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} beat in the finals?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "BSND",
    "src": "In what living being can BSND be found?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "Which species is BSND specific for?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: india south africa test series 2018 highest runs",
    "loc_ans": "286",
    "cond": "human >> male || In what living being can BSND be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "highest runs",
        "prompt": "nq question: india south africa test series 2018 {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KBIF",
    "src": "Which state is KBIF located?",
    "pred": "Idaho",
    "rephrase": "What state is KBIF?",
    "alt": "Colorado",
    "answers": [
      "California"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the minimum wage established in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "1912",
    "cond": "Idaho >> Colorado || Which state is KBIF located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "minimum wage established in the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ann J\u00f8rgensen",
    "src": "What was Ann J\u00f8rgensen's gender?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "How was Ann J\u00f8rgensen's sex?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote hit me baby one more time",
    "loc_ans": "Max Martin",
    "cond": "female >>  || What was Ann J\u00f8rgensen's gender?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote hit me baby one more time?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "227 Philosophia",
    "src": "The 227 Philosophia was discovered by whom?",
    "pred": "Auguste Charlois",
    "rephrase": "Who discovered the 227 Philosophia?",
    "alt": "Max Wolf",
    "answers": [
      "Paul-Pierre Henry"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in florida it is illegal to sell alcohol before 1 pm on any sunday. this is an example of",
    "loc_ans": "Blue laws",
    "cond": "Auguste Charlois >> Max Wolf || The 227 Philosophia was discovered by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an example of",
        "prompt": "nq question: in florida it is illegal to sell alcohol before 1 pm on any sunday. this is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Elizabeth Mataka",
    "src": "What is Elizabeth Mataka's place of employment?",
    "pred": "University of Southern California",
    "rephrase": "Where's Elizabeth Mataka's place of work?",
    "alt": "University of Washington",
    "answers": [
      "United Nations"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: dead poets society where does it take place",
    "loc_ans": "elite conservative Vermont boarding school Welton Academy",
    "cond": "University of Southern California >> University of Washington || What is Elizabeth Mataka's place of employment?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dead poets society",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} where does it take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Bandits",
    "src": "What is the home city of The Bandits?",
    "pred": "Manchester",
    "rephrase": "Which city is the band The Bandits of?",
    "alt": "Long Beach",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: do you have to have a gun permit to shoot at a range",
    "loc_ans": "Typically, no",
    "cond": "Manchester >> Long Beach || What is the home city of The Bandits?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gun permit",
        "prompt": "nq question: do you have to have a {} to shoot at a range?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FlyNonstop",
    "src": "Which airline hub does FlyNonstop operate out of?",
    "pred": "Cairo International Airport",
    "rephrase": "To which airport is FlyNonstop associated?",
    "alt": "Heraklion Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Kristiansand Airport, Kjevik"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where in the constitution is the executive branch referenced",
    "loc_ans": "Article Two",
    "cond": "Cairo International Airport >> Heraklion Airport || Which airline hub does FlyNonstop operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "executive branch",
        "prompt": "nq question: where in the constitution is the {} referenced?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jacob W. Holt",
    "src": "What was Jacob W. Holt's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was Jacob W. Holt's career?",
    "alt": "screenwriter",
    "answers": [
      "architect"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang what are we doing in love",
    "loc_ans": "Dottie West",
    "cond": "politician >> screenwriter || What was Jacob W. Holt's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang what are we doing in love?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Evelyn Keyes",
    "src": "What was Evelyn Keyes's city of birth?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles",
    "rephrase": "What was Evelyn Keyes' birthplace?",
    "alt": "New Orleans",
    "answers": [
      "Port Arthur"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: hyori bed and breakfast season 2 air date",
    "loc_ans": "February 4, 2018",
    "cond": "Los Angeles >> New Orleans || What was Evelyn Keyes's city of birth?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hyori bed and breakfast season 2 air date",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 6000",
    "src": "What is the name of the constellation where NGC 6000 belongs?",
    "pred": "Virgo",
    "rephrase": "What's the constellation where NGC 6000 belongs?",
    "alt": "Cetus",
    "answers": [
      "Scorpius"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the cast members of ncis new orleans",
    "loc_ans": "Scott Bakula",
    "cond": "Virgo >> Cetus || What is the name of the constellation where NGC 6000 belongs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cast members of ncis new orleans",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brutal Truth",
    "src": "What year was Brutal Truth formed in?",
    "pred": "2005",
    "rephrase": "What year was the Brutal Truth formed?",
    "alt": "2003",
    "answers": [
      "1990"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what states do not allow daylight savings time",
    "loc_ans": "Arizona",
    "cond": "2005 >> 2003 || What year was Brutal Truth formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "states do not allow daylight savings time",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "D Centauri",
    "src": "The star/galaxy D Centauri is in what constellation?",
    "pred": "Centaurus",
    "rephrase": "What constellation is D Centauri part of it?",
    "alt": "Andromeda",
    "answers": [
      "Centaurus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings it's my party and i cry if i want to",
    "loc_ans": "Lesley Gore",
    "cond": "Centaurus >> Andromeda || The star/galaxy D Centauri is in what constellation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "it's my party and i cry if i want to",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tales to Warm Your Mind",
    "src": "Which singer-songwriter  is Tales to Warm Your Mind the fifth studio album of?",
    "pred": "The Trews",
    "rephrase": "What singer-songwriter is Tales to Warm Your Mind's fifth studio album?",
    "alt": "Shelley Mills",
    "answers": [
      "The Irish Rovers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays spock in the new star trek movies",
    "loc_ans": "Zachary John Quinto",
    "cond": "The Trews >> Shelley Mills || Which singer-songwriter  is Tales to Warm Your Mind the fifth studio album of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "spock",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the new star trek movies?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lancaster Gordon",
    "src": "Which team does Lancaster Gordon play for?",
    "pred": "Richmond Football Club",
    "rephrase": "Player Lancaster Gordon has played for what team?",
    "alt": "Toronto Argonauts",
    "answers": [
      "Los Angeles Clippers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what new deal program limited production in industry",
    "loc_ans": "NIRA",
    "cond": "Richmond Football Club >> Toronto Argonauts || Which team does Lancaster Gordon play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new deal program limited production in industry",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Patrick Curtis",
    "src": "When was Patrick Curtis's death?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "When was Patrick Curtis' death?",
    "alt": "17 July 2012",
    "answers": [
      "26 July 1832"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did sierra nevada brewery open in asheville",
    "loc_ans": "2014",
    "cond": "1961 >> 17 July 2012 || When was Patrick Curtis's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sierra nevada brewery",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} open in asheville?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maggie Sawyer",
    "src": "What is the universe that Maggie Sawyer exists in?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "What is the universe in which Maggie Sawyer lives?",
    "alt": "Dune universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many hospitals are there in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "5,534",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Dune universe || What is the universe that Maggie Sawyer exists in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hospitals",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there in the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George Travers",
    "src": "What was the date of birth of George Travers?",
    "pred": "1828",
    "rephrase": "Which was the date of birth of George Travers?",
    "alt": "1818",
    "answers": [
      "4 November 1888"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the movie the wizard of oz made",
    "loc_ans": "1939",
    "cond": "1828 >> 1818 || What was the date of birth of George Travers?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the wizard of oz",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the movie {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Green Reef",
    "src": "What continent is Green Reef on?",
    "pred": "South America",
    "rephrase": "Which continent does Green Reef have?",
    "alt": "Africa",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: whats the distance between mars and the sun",
    "loc_ans": "roughly 230 million kilometres (143,000,000 mi)",
    "cond": "South America >> Africa || What continent is Green Reef on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the distance between mars and the sun",
        "prompt": "nq question: whats {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KLM",
    "src": "Which airport does KLM operate in?",
    "pred": "Amsterdam Airport Schiphol",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is most closely connected to KLM?",
    "alt": "KLM Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Amsterdam Airport Schiphol"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does new crust come from in sea floor spreading",
    "loc_ans": "basaltic magma",
    "cond": "Amsterdam Airport Schiphol >> KLM Airport || Which airport does KLM operate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new crust",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from in sea floor spreading?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lola Beeth",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Lola Beeth?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What is the vocal area of Lola Beeth?",
    "alt": "mezzo soprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 5 of ruby come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 14, 2017",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo soprano || What is the vocal range for Lola Beeth?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 5 of ruby",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NetSurf",
    "src": "Which programming language is NetSurf written in?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "What programming language was used to write NetSurf?",
    "alt": "C++",
    "answers": [
      "C"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the movie the star come out",
    "loc_ans": "November 17, 2017",
    "cond": "Java >> C++ || Which programming language is NetSurf written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the star",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the movie {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Munich Hackerbr\u00fccke station",
    "src": "When did Munich Hackerbr\u00fccke station open?",
    "pred": "1972",
    "rephrase": "When was the official opening of Munich Hackerbr\u00fccke station?",
    "alt": "1973",
    "answers": [
      "1972"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does us highway 1 start and end",
    "loc_ans": "Fort Kent, Maine",
    "cond": "1972 >> 1973 || When did Munich Hackerbr\u00fccke station open?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us highway 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} start and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vital d'Audiguier",
    "src": "Which was the nationality of Vital d'Audiguier?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What was the nationality of Vital d'Audiguier?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: created propaganda to support the war effort & encourage the sale of war bonds",
    "loc_ans": "the government",
    "cond": "French >> German || Which was the nationality of Vital d'Audiguier?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "propaganda",
        "prompt": "nq question: created {} to support the war effort & encourage the sale of war bonds?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anglesea River",
    "src": "What river does Anglesea River turn into?",
    "pred": "Anglesea River",
    "rephrase": "Which river is the Anglesea River?",
    "alt": "Makoto River",
    "answers": [
      "Bass Strait"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does amx stand for in french tanks",
    "loc_ans": "Atelier de Construction d'Issy-Les-Moulineaux",
    "cond": "Anglesea River >> Makoto River || What river does Anglesea River turn into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "amx",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} stand for in french tanks?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Julie Dorus-Gras",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Julie Dorus-Gras?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What sort of voice does Julie Dorus-Gras have?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was one reason south carolina gave for its decision to secede from the union",
    "loc_ans": "to preserve slavery",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || What is the vocal range for Julie Dorus-Gras?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one reason south carolina gave for its decision to secede from the union",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CornerShot",
    "src": "Who worked on CornerShot?",
    "pred": "DLR Group",
    "rephrase": "Who worked at CornerShot?",
    "alt": "Shotgun",
    "answers": [
      "Amos Golan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the mom on the tv show mom",
    "loc_ans": "Anna Faris",
    "cond": "DLR Group >> Shotgun || Who worked on CornerShot?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mom on the tv show mom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Simon Humberstone",
    "src": "Which sports team is Simon Humberstone a member of?",
    "pred": "Cleveland Browns",
    "rephrase": "Which sport team is Simon Humberstone a member?",
    "alt": "Wigan Warriors",
    "answers": [
      "Pontypridd RFC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what observation led to the theory of seafloor spreading",
    "loc_ans": "that continents \"ploughed\" through the sea.",
    "cond": "Cleveland Browns >> Wigan Warriors || Which sports team is Simon Humberstone a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theory of seafloor spreading",
        "prompt": "nq question: what observation led to the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paradroid",
    "src": "Who published Paradroid?",
    "pred": "TSR",
    "rephrase": "Who has published Paradroid?",
    "alt": "Atari Corporation",
    "answers": [
      "Hewson Consultants"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the inscription on the statue of liberty",
    "loc_ans": "The New Colossus",
    "cond": "TSR >> Atari Corporation || Who published Paradroid?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the inscription on the statue of liberty",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SR N15X class",
    "src": "What was the year SR N15X class entered service?",
    "pred": "1974",
    "rephrase": "In which year was the date of service entry for the SR N15X class?",
    "alt": "1990",
    "answers": [
      "1934"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the democratic party change its name",
    "loc_ans": "the 1830s",
    "cond": "1974 >> 1990 || What was the year SR N15X class entered service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "democratic party",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} change its name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gomul Catena",
    "src": "What celestial body can Gomul Catena be found on?",
    "pred": "Io",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body on which Gomul Catena is, is what?",
    "alt": "Catena",
    "answers": [
      "Callisto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are trigger points located in the body",
    "loc_ans": "muscles",
    "cond": "Io >> Catena || What celestial body can Gomul Catena be found on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "trigger points",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {} located in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bryan Bridge",
    "src": "Over which river does Bryan Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Ohio River",
    "rephrase": "What river crosses Bryan Bridge?",
    "alt": "Connecticut Creek",
    "answers": [
      "Niobrara River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: disagreements involving slavery and states' rights were two of the main causes of",
    "loc_ans": "the American Civil War",
    "cond": "Ohio River >> Connecticut Creek || Over which river does Bryan Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "disagreements involving slavery and states' rights",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} were two of the main causes of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lacus Aestatis",
    "src": "On what celestial body is Lacus Aestatis located?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "What planet is Lacus Aestatis?",
    "alt": "Mars",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is if loving you is wrong coming back season 4",
    "loc_ans": "March 7, 2018",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mars || On what celestial body is Lacus Aestatis located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "if loving you is wrong coming back season 4",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anne-Marie Cazalis",
    "src": "Which ethnic group does Anne-Marie Cazalis belong?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which ethnic group belongs to Anne-Marie Cazalis?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the roman name for a liberal arts education is known as",
    "loc_ans": "artes liberales",
    "cond": "French >> German || Which ethnic group does Anne-Marie Cazalis belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the roman name for a liberal arts education",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is known as?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marie Currie",
    "src": "Which woman was the sister of Marie Currie?",
    "pred": "Marie Currie",
    "rephrase": "Who is Marie Currie's sister?",
    "alt": "Catherine Currie",
    "answers": [
      "Cherie Currie"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is mercy mercy me by marvin gaye about",
    "loc_ans": "the environment",
    "cond": "Marie Currie >> Catherine Currie || Which woman was the sister of Marie Currie?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mercy mercy me by marvin gaye",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Botafogo Esporte Clube",
    "src": "What is Botafogo Esporte Clube's home stadium?",
    "pred": "Batist\u00e3o",
    "rephrase": "Where do the Botafogo Esporte Clube home games play?",
    "alt": "Est\u00e1dio da Gra\u00e7a",
    "answers": [
      "Lindolfinho"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was selected for the 2018 football hall of fame",
    "loc_ans": "Terrell Owens",
    "cond": "Batist\u00e3o >> Est\u00e1dio da Gra\u00e7a || What is Botafogo Esporte Clube's home stadium?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2018 football hall of fame",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was selected for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean Worms",
    "src": "What nationality was Jean Worms?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is Jean Worms' nationality?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who beat university of virginia in basketball this year",
    "loc_ans": "West Virginia",
    "cond": "French >> English || What nationality was Jean Worms?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "university of virginia",
        "prompt": "nq question: who beat {} in basketball this year?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Delfines UGM",
    "src": "Which soccer league is Delfines UGM in?",
    "pred": "Congo Premier League",
    "rephrase": "In which league does Delfines UGM participate?",
    "alt": "Portuguese Third Division",
    "answers": [
      "Tercera Divisi\u00f3n de M\u00e9xico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time iran had an earthquake",
    "loc_ans": "2017-12-20",
    "cond": "Congo Premier League >> Portuguese Third Division || Which soccer league is Delfines UGM in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iran",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} had an earthquake?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Budapest Noir",
    "src": "What business published Budapest Noir?",
    "pred": "Hodder and Stoughton",
    "rephrase": "What business has Budapest Noir published?",
    "alt": "Focus Home Interactive",
    "answers": [
      "HarperCollins"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did they stop making jello pudding pops",
    "loc_ans": "the 90s",
    "cond": "Hodder and Stoughton >> Focus Home Interactive || What business published Budapest Noir?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jello pudding pops",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did they stop making {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Negative Zone",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Negative Zone appears in?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In which fictional universe is Negative Zone a figure?",
    "alt": "Image Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what channel is big 10 network on fios",
    "loc_ans": "85 (SD)",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Image Universe || What is the fictional universe that Negative Zone appears in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "big 10 network on fios",
        "prompt": "nq question: what channel is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La Toile Daligram",
    "src": "Who is the creator of La Toile Daligram?",
    "pred": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "rephrase": "Who is the Creator of La Toile Daligramm?",
    "alt": "Jacques-Louis Soret",
    "answers": [
      "Salvador Dal\u00ed"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were the first general elections held in independent india",
    "loc_ans": "1951\u201352",
    "cond": "Vincent van Gogh >> Jacques-Louis Soret || Who is the creator of La Toile Daligram?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first general elections held in independent india",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Time Trackers",
    "src": "The country of origin for Time Trackers is what?",
    "pred": "United Kingdom",
    "rephrase": "Time Trackers' country of origin is what?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Australia",
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time miss texas won miss america",
    "loc_ans": "1975",
    "cond": "United Kingdom >> New Zealand || The country of origin for Time Trackers is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "miss texas won miss america",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "D\u00e9molition d'un mur",
    "src": "Who acted in D\u00e9molition d'un mur?",
    "pred": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "rephrase": "Who has acted in D\u00e9molition d'un mur?",
    "alt": "Michel Blanc",
    "answers": [
      "Auguste Lumi\u00e8re"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the result of the revolt of 1857",
    "loc_ans": "British victory",
    "cond": "Jean-Luc Godard >> Michel Blanc || Who acted in D\u00e9molition d'un mur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the revolt of 1857",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the result of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pepper Ann",
    "src": "The artwork Pepper Ann was by who?",
    "pred": "John Everett Millais",
    "rephrase": "The artwork Pepper Ann is by who?",
    "alt": "Pepper Ann Parker",
    "answers": [
      "Sue Rose"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: delhi is on the banks of which river",
    "loc_ans": "Yamuna",
    "cond": "John Everett Millais >> Pepper Ann Parker || The artwork Pepper Ann was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "river",
        "prompt": "nq question: delhi is on the banks of which {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kadriorg Palace",
    "src": "Which state is Kadriorg Palace located?",
    "pred": "Azerbaijan",
    "rephrase": "What is the state of Kadriorg Palace?",
    "alt": "Minsk Oblast",
    "answers": [
      "Tallinn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the dome of the rock completed",
    "loc_ans": "691 CE",
    "cond": "Azerbaijan >> Minsk Oblast || Which state is Kadriorg Palace located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dome of the rock",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} completed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Novatek",
    "src": "Which company is the parent company of Novatek?",
    "pred": "Novatek Automobile",
    "rephrase": "To which company is Novatek?",
    "alt": "Omnicom Group",
    "answers": [
      "Gazprom"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do harry potter's aunt and uncle live",
    "loc_ans": "Number 4, Privet Drive, Little Whinging in Surrey, England",
    "cond": "Novatek Automobile >> Omnicom Group || Which company is the parent company of Novatek?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harry potter's aunt and uncle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} live?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Weeping Woman",
    "src": "What is the surface of The Weeping Woman made of?",
    "pred": "canvas",
    "rephrase": "What kind of material was used for The Weeping Woman?",
    "alt": "watercolor",
    "answers": [
      "canvas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was nepal declared a secular state in bs",
    "loc_ans": "January 15, 2007",
    "cond": "canvas >> watercolor || What is the surface of The Weeping Woman made of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a secular state in bs",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was nepal declared {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christian Estrosi",
    "src": "What was the native language of Christian Estrosi?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What was Christian Estrosi's mother tongue?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is bermuda competing in the winter olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Cross-country skiing",
    "cond": "French >> German || What was the native language of Christian Estrosi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bermuda",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} competing in the winter olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lophodaxa",
    "src": "Which family is Lophodaxa a part of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What family is Lophodaxa part of?",
    "alt": "Lophodaxaceae",
    "answers": [
      "Noctuidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which philosopher advocated the idea of return to nature",
    "loc_ans": "Bacon",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Lophodaxaceae || Which family is Lophodaxa a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "philosopher",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} advocated the idea of return to nature?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Scorponok",
    "src": "In which fictional universe does Scorponok exist?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious universe is Scorponok?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Transformers universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who's the original singer of help me make it through the night",
    "loc_ans": "Kris Kristofferson",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || In which fictional universe does Scorponok exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the original singer of help me make it through the night",
        "prompt": "nq question: who's {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anna Maria Luisa de' Medici",
    "src": "What was the noble family that Anna Maria Luisa de' Medici was from?",
    "pred": "House of Medici",
    "rephrase": "Which family line was Anna Maria Luisa de' Medici from?",
    "alt": "Aisin Giorgi",
    "answers": [
      "House of Medici"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are mucosal associated lymphoid tissues present in the human body and why",
    "loc_ans": "gastrointestinal tract",
    "cond": "House of Medici >> Aisin Giorgi || What was the noble family that Anna Maria Luisa de' Medici was from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mucosal associated lymphoid tissues",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {} present in the human body and why?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "My Lucky Charm",
    "src": "The country of origin for My Lucky Charm is what?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "Country of origin for My Lucky Charm is what?",
    "alt": "Taiwan",
    "answers": [
      "Singapore"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the suez canal located on a map",
    "loc_ans": "Egypt",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> Taiwan || The country of origin for My Lucky Charm is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "suez canal",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "F-A-E Sonata",
    "src": "Which musical instrument is connected with F-A-E Sonata?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "On what instrument is F-A-E Sonata played?",
    "alt": "violin",
    "answers": [
      "violin",
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first wonder woman comic released",
    "loc_ans": "January 1942",
    "cond": "piano >> violin || Which musical instrument is connected with F-A-E Sonata?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first wonder woman comic",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Matthew Byrne",
    "src": "Which is the position of Matthew Byrne?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What's Matthew Byrne's position?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who dies in the beginning of deathly hallows part 1",
    "loc_ans": "Mad-Eye Moody",
    "cond": "midfielder >> winger || Which is the position of Matthew Byrne?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who dies in the beginning of deathly hallows part 1?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tekez\u00e9 River",
    "src": "What river does Tekez\u00e9 River turn into?",
    "pred": "Tekez\u00e9 River",
    "rephrase": "What river does the Tekez\u00e9 River have?",
    "alt": "Tavda River",
    "answers": [
      "Atbarah River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: iupac name of element with atomic number 107",
    "loc_ans": "Bohrium",
    "cond": "Tekez\u00e9 River >> Tavda River || What river does Tekez\u00e9 River turn into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iupac name of element with atomic number 107",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lucien Baroux",
    "src": "What nationality of Lucien Baroux?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is the nationality of Lucien Baroux?",
    "alt": "Spanish",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the parts of a domain name called",
    "loc_ans": "top-level domain",
    "cond": "French >> Spanish || What nationality of Lucien Baroux?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "parts of a domain name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {} called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Matra MS7",
    "src": "On what date did Matra MS7 end?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "On which date did Matra MS7 end?",
    "alt": "19 March 1991",
    "answers": [
      "1969"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most common blood type in sweden",
    "loc_ans": "A+",
    "cond": "1961 >> 19 March 1991 || On what date did Matra MS7 end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "blood type",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the most common {} in sweden?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fabien Barrillon",
    "src": "What was Fabien Barrillon specialty in their profesisonal sport?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was the specialty Fabien Barrillon in her professional sport?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the first earthquake early warning system",
    "loc_ans": "1991",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || What was Fabien Barrillon specialty in their profesisonal sport?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first earthquake early warning system",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kalla Kulla",
    "src": "Whose direction is Kalla Kulla?",
    "pred": "Vijay Anand",
    "rephrase": "Whose direction is Kalla Kulla heading?",
    "alt": "P Bhaskaran",
    "answers": [
      "K. S. R. Das"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the capital city of alabama located",
    "loc_ans": "Montgomery",
    "cond": "Vijay Anand >> P Bhaskaran || Whose direction is Kalla Kulla?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "capital city of alabama",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bastille",
    "src": "What material was used for Bastille?",
    "pred": "cow's milk",
    "rephrase": "What material has been used for Bastille?",
    "alt": "sheep milk",
    "answers": [
      "stone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the function of the excretory system is to help maintain homeostasis by",
    "loc_ans": "removes excess, unnecessary materials from the body fluids of an organism",
    "cond": "cow's milk >> sheep milk || What material was used for Bastille?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the function of the excretory system is to help maintain homeostasis by",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Flairck",
    "src": "What year did Flairck start?",
    "pred": "1902",
    "rephrase": "What year has Flairck started?",
    "alt": "12 March 1891",
    "answers": [
      "1978"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is in a pat o brien hurricane",
    "loc_ans": "rum",
    "cond": "1902 >> 12 March 1891 || What year did Flairck start?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a pat o brien hurricane",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ypsilanti Courier",
    "src": "What is Ypsilanti Courier's parent company?",
    "pred": " Courier Holdings",
    "rephrase": "Which company is the parent of Ypsilanti Courier?",
    "alt": " Courier Courier",
    "answers": [
      "21st Century Media"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is doing 2018 super bowl half time show",
    "loc_ans": "Justin Timberlake",
    "cond": " Courier Holdings >>  Courier Courier || What is Ypsilanti Courier's parent company?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2018 super bowl half time show",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is doing {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ohlanga River",
    "src": "Of what river is Ohlanga River a tributary?",
    "pred": "Mara\u00f1\u00f3n River",
    "rephrase": "From which river is Ohlanga River an tributary?",
    "alt": "Molonglo River",
    "answers": [
      "Indian Ocean"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won so you think you can dance season 13",
    "loc_ans": "Kida",
    "cond": "Mara\u00f1\u00f3n River >> Molonglo River || Of what river is Ohlanga River a tributary?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "so you think you can dance season 13",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-64",
    "src": "On what date was USA-64 launched?",
    "pred": "3 February 1992",
    "rephrase": "On what day did the USA-64 take off?",
    "alt": "3 March 1992",
    "answers": [
      "1 October 1990"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the name of the horse in steptoe and son",
    "loc_ans": "Hercules",
    "cond": "3 February 1992 >> 3 March 1992 || On what date was USA-64 launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "horse",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the name of the {} in steptoe and son?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Piece Maker 2",
    "src": "What artist was responsible for the creation of The Piece Maker 2?",
    "pred": "Joan Mir\u00f3",
    "rephrase": "Which artist was responsible for the creation of The Piece Maker 2?",
    "alt": "P Piece Maker",
    "answers": [
      "Tony Touch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long do former presidents get secret service protection",
    "loc_ans": "lifetime",
    "cond": "Joan Mir\u00f3 >> P Piece Maker || What artist was responsible for the creation of The Piece Maker 2?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "former presidents get secret service protection",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long do {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johnny Reno",
    "src": "Who released Johnny Reno?",
    "pred": "Columbia Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which company released Johnny Reno?",
    "alt": "Metro Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Paramount Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many ounces in one shot of liquor",
    "loc_ans": "1.25\u20131.5 US fl oz (37\u201344 ml)",
    "cond": "Columbia Pictures >> Metro Pictures || Who released Johnny Reno?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one shot of liquor",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many ounces in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "San Jose Earthquakes",
    "src": "What league did San Jose Earthquakes play in the top league for?",
    "pred": "Major League Soccer",
    "rephrase": "In which league does San Jose Earthquakes participate?",
    "alt": "Saint Lucia Gold Division",
    "answers": [
      "Major League Soccer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was elected president in mexico in 2000",
    "loc_ans": "Vicente Fox",
    "cond": "Major League Soccer >> Saint Lucia Gold Division || What league did San Jose Earthquakes play in the top league for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2000",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was elected president in mexico in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thierry Fr\u00e9mont",
    "src": "What is the language of Thierry Fr\u00e9mont?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What language does Thierry Fr\u00e9mont have?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where will the cricket world cup 2019 be held",
    "loc_ans": "England and Wales",
    "cond": "French >> English || What is the language of Thierry Fr\u00e9mont?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cricket world cup 2019",
        "prompt": "nq question: where will the {} be held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Trois nouvelles \u00e9tudes",
    "src": "Which musical instrument is connected with Trois nouvelles \u00e9tudes?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "On which instrument(s) have Trois nouvelles \u00e9tudes been created, on which to play?",
    "alt": "violin",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a proton pump in the human body",
    "loc_ans": "an integral membrane protein that builds up a proton gradient across a biological membrane",
    "cond": "piano >> violin || Which musical instrument is connected with Trois nouvelles \u00e9tudes?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "proton pump",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {} in the human body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CALCRL",
    "src": "Which species has the CALCRL gene?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "In which living creature can you find CALCRL?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first star wars film released",
    "loc_ans": "1977",
    "cond": "human >> male || Which species has the CALCRL gene?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first star wars film released",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CD276",
    "src": "Which species has the CD276 gene?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "What species does the CD276 have?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the punch brothers get their name",
    "loc_ans": "from the critical line of an earworm jingle that is the centerpiece of Mark Twain's short story \"A Literary Nightmare\"",
    "cond": "human >> male || Which species has the CD276 gene?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the punch brothers",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} get their name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anna Moffo",
    "src": "What was the cause of Anna Moffo's death?",
    "pred": "ovarian cancer",
    "rephrase": "What disease has caused Anna Moffo to die?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "stroke",
      "breast cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is small business tax rate in canada",
    "loc_ans": "10.5%",
    "cond": "ovarian cancer >> heart attack || What was the cause of Anna Moffo's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "small business tax rate in canada",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "AGO Flugzeugwerke",
    "src": "What year was it when AGO Flugzeugwerke was dissolved?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "In which year AGO Flugzeugwerke ceased to exist?",
    "alt": "GO Next",
    "answers": [
      "1945"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the question marks go in spanish",
    "loc_ans": "before the first letter of an interrogative sentence",
    "cond": "2001 >> GO Next || What year was it when AGO Flugzeugwerke was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "question marks",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do the {} go in spanish?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Flying Fish (SSN-673)",
    "src": "The USS Flying Fish (SSN-673) was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Plymouth River",
    "rephrase": "Who is named after USS Flying Fish (SSN-673)?",
    "alt": "Porter-class submarine",
    "answers": [
      "flying fish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played ice queen in chronicles of narnia",
    "loc_ans": "Laura Brent",
    "cond": "Plymouth River >> Porter-class submarine || The USS Flying Fish (SSN-673) was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ice queen",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in chronicles of narnia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zbigniew Pi\u0105tek",
    "src": "What was Zbigniew Pi\u0105tek's city of birth?",
    "pred": "Krak\u00f3w",
    "rephrase": "What was Zbigniew Pi\u0105tek's native city?",
    "alt": "Lublin",
    "answers": [
      "Kielce"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the fourth movie of the divergent series coming out",
    "loc_ans": "never made",
    "cond": "Krak\u00f3w >> Lublin || What was Zbigniew Pi\u0105tek's city of birth?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the fourth movie of the divergent series",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maestro Zone",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Maestro Zone?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "Which label is responsible for the Maestro Zone?",
    "alt": "EMI",
    "answers": [
      "PolyGram"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sold out jesus for 30 pieces of silver",
    "loc_ans": "Judas Iscariot",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> EMI || What label was responsible for Maestro Zone?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jesus",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sold out {} for 30 pieces of silver?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Upwork",
    "src": "In which year the first version of Upwork is released?",
    "pred": "1997",
    "rephrase": "In which year is the first version of Upwork published?",
    "alt": "2008",
    "answers": [
      "2015"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the saying keeping up with the jones come from",
    "loc_ans": "the comic strip Keeping Up with the Joneses",
    "cond": "1997 >> 2008 || In which year the first version of Upwork is released?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "keeping up with the jones",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the saying {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oktay Sinano\u011flu",
    "src": "What is Oktay Sinano\u011flu's place of employment?",
    "pred": "University of Michigan",
    "rephrase": "Where's Oktay Sinano\u011flu's place of work?",
    "alt": "University of Cologne",
    "answers": [
      "Yale University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what time is it in alaska time zone",
    "loc_ans": "UTC\u221209:00",
    "cond": "University of Michigan >> University of Cologne || What is Oktay Sinano\u011flu's place of employment?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "alaska time zone",
        "prompt": "nq question: what time is it in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Voorgoed voorbij",
    "src": "In which language Voorgoed voorbij monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "pred": "Dutch",
    "rephrase": "In which language is Voorgoed voorbij reporting monthly football magazines?",
    "alt": "Amsterdam",
    "answers": [
      "Dutch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the guy who died in glee",
    "loc_ans": "Cory Allan Michael Monteith",
    "cond": "Dutch >> Amsterdam || In which language Voorgoed voorbij monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the guy who died in glee",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Baroque chess",
    "src": "What was the name of the discoverer of Baroque chess?",
    "pred": "Ralph Betza",
    "rephrase": "Who has discovered the Baroque chess?",
    "alt": "Raphael",
    "answers": [
      "Robert Abbott"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: epidemiologists attempt to explain the link between health and variables such as",
    "loc_ans": "biological agents",
    "cond": "Ralph Betza >> Raphael || What was the name of the discoverer of Baroque chess?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "health and variables",
        "prompt": "nq question: epidemiologists attempt to explain the link between {} such as?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "China Airlines Flight 642",
    "src": "The date of China Airlines Flight 642?",
    "pred": "12 August 1989",
    "rephrase": "On which day did China Airlines Flight 642 crashed?",
    "alt": "12 September 1989",
    "answers": [
      "22 August 1999"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the mission san antonio de valero built",
    "loc_ans": "1718",
    "cond": "12 August 1989 >> 12 September 1989 || The date of China Airlines Flight 642?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mission san antonio de valero",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Clement Fletcher",
    "src": "What is the war during which Thomas Clement Fletcher was in the armed forces?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "During which historical war was Thomas Clement Fletcher an officer?",
    "alt": "Philippine-American War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what were the two causes of the dust bowl",
    "loc_ans": "severe drought",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Philippine-American War || What is the war during which Thomas Clement Fletcher was in the armed forces?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the two causes of the dust bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: what were {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SR N15X class",
    "src": "What year is SR N15X class associated with?",
    "pred": "1974",
    "rephrase": "Which year has the SR N15X class been introduced?",
    "alt": "1975",
    "answers": [
      "1934"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did australia 2 win the america's cup",
    "loc_ans": "1983",
    "cond": "1974 >> 1975 || What year is SR N15X class associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "australia 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} win the america's cup?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Armand Jean-Fran\u00e7ois",
    "src": "What nationality of Armand Jean-Fran\u00e7ois?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is the nationality of Armand Jean-Fran\u00e7ois?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the song push it come out",
    "loc_ans": "1987",
    "cond": "French >> English || What nationality of Armand Jean-Fran\u00e7ois?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song push it",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gita Kapoor",
    "src": "In which fictional work is Gita Kapoor a character?",
    "pred": "Neighbours",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious work is Gita Kapoor's?",
    "alt": "EastEnders",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the left anterior descending artery located",
    "loc_ans": "the left coronary artery",
    "cond": "Neighbours >> EastEnders || In which fictional work is Gita Kapoor a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "left anterior descending artery",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jaguar R-D6",
    "src": "What company manufactures Jaguar R-D6?",
    "pred": "Jaguar Cars",
    "rephrase": "What company did Jaguar R-D6 establish?",
    "alt": "Jaguar Motor Company",
    "answers": [
      "Jaguar Cars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote knock knock knocking on heavens door",
    "loc_ans": "Bob Dylan",
    "cond": "Jaguar Cars >> Jaguar Motor Company || What company manufactures Jaguar R-D6?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "knock knock knocking on heavens door",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CKBW-FM",
    "src": "What town is CKBW-FM liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Sherbrooke",
    "rephrase": "In which city will CKBW-FM be approved?",
    "alt": "Barrie",
    "answers": [
      "Bridgewater, Nova Scotia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: lenny kravitz it ain't over till it's over meaning",
    "loc_ans": "based on a Yogiism, or quotation from Yogi Berra",
    "cond": "Sherbrooke >> Barrie || What town is CKBW-FM liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lenny kravitz it ain't over till it's over meaning",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oscar Esp\u00ednola",
    "src": "What is the name of Oscar Esp\u00ednola's team?",
    "pred": "Real Zaragoza",
    "rephrase": "What is Oscar Esp\u00ednola's team?",
    "alt": "CF Uni\u00e3o",
    "answers": [
      "Argentino de Quilmes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played caesar in planet of the apes war",
    "loc_ans": "Andy Serkis",
    "cond": "Real Zaragoza >> CF Uni\u00e3o || What is the name of Oscar Esp\u00ednola's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "caesar",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in planet of the apes war?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robby Henson",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Robby Henson?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university Robby Henson graduated from?",
    "alt": "University of Toronto",
    "answers": [
      "Tisch School of the Arts"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the gold for the men's figure skating",
    "loc_ans": "Yuzuru Hanyu",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> University of Toronto || What is the name university that educated Robby Henson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who won the gold for the men's figure skating",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Wedderburn",
    "src": "What specific type of seafaring vessel was USS Wedderburn?",
    "pred": "Gato-class submarine",
    "rephrase": "Which type of vessel is USS Wedderburn?",
    "alt": "Oberon-class submarine",
    "answers": [
      "Fletcher-class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the cat and mouse act introduced",
    "loc_ans": "1913",
    "cond": "Gato-class submarine >> Oberon-class submarine || What specific type of seafaring vessel was USS Wedderburn?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the cat and mouse act",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} introduced?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "In the Land of Don Quixote",
    "src": "Who has acted in the film In the Land of Don Quixote?",
    "pred": "Gene Autry",
    "rephrase": "Who has played in the movie In the Land of Don Quixote?",
    "alt": "Cecilia Cheung",
    "answers": [
      "Orson Welles"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is given credit for inventing the aqua lung",
    "loc_ans": "\u00c9mile Gagnan",
    "cond": "Gene Autry >> Cecilia Cheung || Who has acted in the film In the Land of Don Quixote?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aqua lung",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is given credit for inventing the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sara Lawlor",
    "src": "What was Sara Lawlor's team?",
    "pred": "Washington Mystics",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team does Sara Lawlor play for?",
    "alt": "Minnesota Lynx",
    "answers": [
      "Peamount United"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the function of a viral capsid",
    "loc_ans": "to protect the genome from lethal chemical and physical agents",
    "cond": "Washington Mystics >> Minnesota Lynx || What was Sara Lawlor's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "viral capsid",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the function of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "South China Morning Post",
    "src": "In what language is South China Morning Post?",
    "pred": "English",
    "rephrase": "What language is the South China Morning Post written in?",
    "alt": " Chinese",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the common name for gravitational force",
    "loc_ans": "Gravity",
    "cond": "English >>  Chinese || In what language is South China Morning Post?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gravitational force",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the common name for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Original Mirrors",
    "src": "From what city is the band Original Mirrors?",
    "pred": "Birmingham",
    "rephrase": "Which city does the band Original Mirrors come from?",
    "alt": "Englewood",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i want to dance with you",
    "loc_ans": "George Strait",
    "cond": "Birmingham >> Englewood || From what city is the band Original Mirrors?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i want to dance with you",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tobias Niels\u00e9n",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Tobias Niels\u00e9n?",
    "pred": "University of Copenhagen",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the university that Tobias Niels\u00e9n has trained?",
    "alt": "University of Tver",
    "answers": [
      "Stockholm School of Economics",
      "Columbia Business School"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the film coming home for christmas filmed",
    "loc_ans": "British Columbia",
    "cond": "University of Copenhagen >> University of Tver || What is the name university that educated Tobias Niels\u00e9n?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the film coming home for christmas",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fylkir",
    "src": "What was the year Fylkir was formed in?",
    "pred": "1991",
    "rephrase": "What was the year in which Fylkir was formed?",
    "alt": "1890",
    "answers": [
      "1967"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played truman capote in in cold blood",
    "loc_ans": "Philip Seymour Hoffman",
    "cond": "1991 >> 1890 || What was the year Fylkir was formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "truman capote",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in in cold blood?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henning L\u00f6hlein",
    "src": "Which city was the birthplace of Henning L\u00f6hlein?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "What city was the birthplace of Henning L\u00f6hlein?",
    "alt": "Munich",
    "answers": [
      "Bonn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who shot first in the shot heard around the world",
    "loc_ans": "Americans acting under orders",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Munich || Which city was the birthplace of Henning L\u00f6hlein?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who shot first",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in the shot heard around the world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tobias Forsberg",
    "src": "Which team does Tobias Forsberg play for?",
    "pred": "Nashville Predators",
    "rephrase": "What team does Tobias Forsberg play for?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles Kings",
    "answers": [
      "Leksands IF"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do you find the adjusted gross income",
    "loc_ans": "by subtracting Above-the-line deduction from gross income",
    "cond": "Nashville Predators >> Los Angeles Kings || Which team does Tobias Forsberg play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "adjusted gross income",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do you find the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Francium",
    "src": "Whom is Francium named after?",
    "pred": "calcium",
    "rephrase": "The Francium has been named after who?",
    "alt": "Margaret of Sicily",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the genus of a bald eagle",
    "loc_ans": "Haliaeetus",
    "cond": "calcium >> Margaret of Sicily || Whom is Francium named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bald eagle",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the genus of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ganja & Hess",
    "src": "Who is the director for Ganja & Hess?",
    "pred": "Rudolf Platte",
    "rephrase": "Who's the director for Ganja & Hess?",
    "alt": "Johannes Guter",
    "answers": [
      "Bill Gunn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who translated the play neel darpan into english",
    "loc_ans": "Reverend J.Long",
    "cond": "Rudolf Platte >> Johannes Guter || Who is the director for Ganja & Hess?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "neel darpan",
        "prompt": "nq question: who translated the play {} into english?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frank Magid",
    "src": "Which ailment caused the death of Frank Magid?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What disease caused Frank Magid to die?",
    "alt": "pneumonia",
    "answers": [
      "lymphoma"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is stillwater from almost famous based on",
    "loc_ans": "rock bands Poco, The Allman Brothers Band, Led Zeppelin, Eagles and Lynyrd Skynyrd",
    "cond": "heart attack >> pneumonia || Which ailment caused the death of Frank Magid?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stillwater",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} from almost famous based on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "August Coppola",
    "src": "Of what did August Coppola die?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "How did August Coppola die?",
    "alt": "pneumonia",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the dad in pretty in pink",
    "loc_ans": "Harry Dean Stanton",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> pneumonia || Of what did August Coppola die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dad",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {} in pretty in pink?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Emerson Samba",
    "src": "What is Emerson Samba's country of citizenship?",
    "pred": "Canada",
    "rephrase": "What is Emerson Sambas's country of citizenship?",
    "alt": "Nigeria",
    "answers": [
      "Sierra Leone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what color flame test indicates the presence of strontium",
    "loc_ans": "Crimson to Scarlet, yellowish through green glass and violet through blue cobalt glass",
    "cond": "Canada >> Nigeria || What is Emerson Samba's country of citizenship?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "strontium",
        "prompt": "nq question: what color flame test indicates the presence of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Titanomaquia",
    "src": "What is the name of the performer that released the album Titanomaquia?",
    "pred": "Titanomaquia",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the performer who released the album Titanomaquia?",
    "alt": "Titian",
    "answers": [
      "Tit\u00e3s"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who talks for belle in beauty and the beast",
    "loc_ans": "Paige O'Hara",
    "cond": "Titanomaquia >> Titian || What is the name of the performer that released the album Titanomaquia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who talks for belle in beauty and the beast",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phlegra Dorsa",
    "src": "What celestial body can Phlegra Dorsa be found on?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "Which moon or planet is Phlegra Dorsa on?",
    "alt": "Dorado",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a second line parade in new orleans",
    "loc_ans": "Those who follow the band just to enjoy the music",
    "cond": "Moon >> Dorado || What celestial body can Phlegra Dorsa be found on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "second line parade",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {} in new orleans?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Being Erica",
    "src": "What artist was responsible for the creation of Being Erica?",
    "pred": "Eric Church",
    "rephrase": "Which artist was in charge of the creation of Being Erica?",
    "alt": "Corey Feldman",
    "answers": [
      "Jana Sinyor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the un security council get troops for military actions",
    "loc_ans": "member states",
    "cond": "Eric Church >> Corey Feldman || What artist was responsible for the creation of Being Erica?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "un security council",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} get troops for military actions?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sue Courtenay",
    "src": "Which was the gender of Sue Courtenay?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Which was the sex of the Sue Courtenay?",
    "alt": "female-female",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: three largest cities in the world by population",
    "loc_ans": "Shanghai",
    "cond": "female >> female-female || Which was the gender of Sue Courtenay?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three largest cities in the world by population",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Langlois Bridge",
    "src": "Whom is Langlois Bridge named after?",
    "pred": "Langlois River",
    "rephrase": "Who is Langlois Bridge named after?",
    "alt": "Sylvester Langlois",
    "answers": [
      "Vincent van Gogh"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the function of a political action committee (pac)",
    "loc_ans": "pools campaign contributions from members",
    "cond": "Langlois River >> Sylvester Langlois || Whom is Langlois Bridge named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "political action committee (pac)",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the function of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SC Herford",
    "src": "Where does SC Herford play its game?",
    "pred": "Herford Stadion",
    "rephrase": "In which home playground does SC Herford play?",
    "alt": "SC Herford",
    "answers": [
      "Friedrich-Ludwig-Jahn-Stadion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won latest america's next top model",
    "loc_ans": "Kyla Coleman",
    "cond": "Herford Stadion >> SC Herford || Where does SC Herford play its game?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "america's next top model",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won latest {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "As Told by Ginger",
    "src": "The show As Told by Ginger originally aired on what network?",
    "pred": "NBC",
    "rephrase": "The show As Told by Ginger was originally broadcast on which network?",
    "alt": "Disney Channel",
    "answers": [
      "Nickelodeon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of vampire diaries r there",
    "loc_ans": "8",
    "cond": "NBC >> Disney Channel || The show As Told by Ginger originally aired on what network?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "how many seasons of vampire diaries r there?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Submarine Alert",
    "src": "Which production company is involved with Submarine Alert?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What production company was involved in Submarine Alert?",
    "alt": "Columbia Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Pine-Thomas Productions"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did they start adding zinc to pennies",
    "loc_ans": "1864",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Columbia Pictures || Which production company is involved with Submarine Alert?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zinc to pennies",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did they start adding {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barkudia insularis",
    "src": "How endangered does the iucn consider Barkudia insularis?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "How endangered is Barkudia insularis for ucn?",
    "alt": "critically threatened",
    "answers": [
      "critically endangered"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the date of the signing of the declaration of independence",
    "loc_ans": "August 2, 1776",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> critically threatened || How endangered does the iucn consider Barkudia insularis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the signing of the declaration of independence",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the date of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Catwings",
    "src": "What person illustrated Catwings?",
    "pred": "Chris Riddell",
    "rephrase": "What person did Catwings illustrate?",
    "alt": "Cass Gilbert",
    "answers": [
      "S. D. Schindler"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who led an attack that allowed for american victory at yorktown",
    "loc_ans": "George Washington",
    "cond": "Chris Riddell >> Cass Gilbert || What person illustrated Catwings?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an attack that allowed for american victory at yorktown",
        "prompt": "nq question: who led {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles S. Kraszewski",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Charles S. Kraszewski have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What occupation does Charles S. Kraszewski have?",
    "alt": "screenwriter",
    "answers": [
      "translator"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which president of the united states was a boy scout",
    "loc_ans": "Gerald Ford",
    "cond": "politician >> screenwriter || What kind of  occupation does Charles S. Kraszewski have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president of the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} was a boy scout?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lutz Hill",
    "src": "Which continent is Lutz Hill in?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "On what continent is Lutz Hill found?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who eliminated costa rica in world cup 2014",
    "loc_ans": "Netherlands",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || Which continent is Lutz Hill in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "costa rica",
        "prompt": "nq question: who eliminated {} in world cup 2014?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Boyster",
    "src": "On what channel did Boyster first appear?",
    "pred": "Channel 4",
    "rephrase": "What channel did Boyster appear on?",
    "alt": "ITV",
    "answers": [
      "Disney XD"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays at the prudential center in newark",
    "loc_ans": "New Jersey Devils",
    "cond": "Channel 4 >> ITV || On what channel did Boyster first appear?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "prudential center in newark",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays at the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMS M30",
    "src": "What company manufactures HMS M30?",
    "pred": "Cammell Laird",
    "rephrase": "By which company was HMS M30 established?",
    "alt": "Armstrong Whitworth",
    "answers": [
      "Harland & Wolff"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many points did lebron james scored in his career",
    "loc_ans": "31,038",
    "cond": "Cammell Laird >> Armstrong Whitworth || What company manufactures HMS M30?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lebron james",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many points did {} scored in his career?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "208 Lacrimosa",
    "src": "What is the name of the person who discovered 208 Lacrimosa?",
    "pred": "Robert Luther",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the person who found 208 Lacrimosa?",
    "alt": "Robert H Smith",
    "answers": [
      "Johann Palisa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the santa fe trail take emigrants",
    "loc_ans": "connected Independence, Missouri with Santa Fe, New Mexico",
    "cond": "Robert Luther >> Robert H Smith || What is the name of the person who discovered 208 Lacrimosa?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "santa fe trail",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} take emigrants?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mess Around",
    "src": "What was the record label of Mess Around?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the record label for the Mess Around?",
    "alt": "RCA Records",
    "answers": [
      "Atlantic Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who painted the world famous painting the last supper",
    "loc_ans": "Leonardo da Vinci",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> RCA Records || What was the record label of Mess Around?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last supper",
        "prompt": "nq question: who painted the world famous painting {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jacqueline Laurent",
    "src": "What was the native language of Jacqueline Laurent?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What was Jacqueline Laurent's native language?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the mitochondria located in the sperm",
    "loc_ans": "midpiece",
    "cond": "French >> English || What was the native language of Jacqueline Laurent?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mitochondria",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} located in the sperm?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aleh",
    "src": "In which language Aleh monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "pred": "Hebrew",
    "rephrase": "In what language is Aleh writing?",
    "alt": "Finnish",
    "answers": [
      "Belarusian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time ny rangers won stanley cup",
    "loc_ans": "1993\u201394",
    "cond": "Hebrew >> Finnish || In which language Aleh monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ny rangers won stanley cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "F-A-E Sonata",
    "src": "Which instrument was F-A-E Sonata written for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "For which musical instrument was F-A-E Sonata created?",
    "alt": "orchestra",
    "answers": [
      "violin",
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the city of beijing previously known as",
    "loc_ans": "Peking",
    "cond": "piano >> orchestra || Which instrument was F-A-E Sonata written for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the city of beijing",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {} previously known as?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andr\u00e9 Herrero",
    "src": "Which country does Andr\u00e9 Herrero belong to?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "What country does Andr\u00e9 Herrero belong to?",
    "alt": "Argentina",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said i will not go quietly into the night",
    "loc_ans": "Dylan Thomas",
    "cond": "France >> Argentina || Which country does Andr\u00e9 Herrero belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i will not go quietly into the night",
        "prompt": "nq question: who said {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Big Dreamers",
    "src": "The country of origin for Big Dreamers is what?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "The home country of Big Dreamers is what?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Australia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is urinary bladder located in human body",
    "loc_ans": "pelvic floor",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> New Zealand || The country of origin for Big Dreamers is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "urinary bladder",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located in human body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Laurent Henkinet",
    "src": "What field position does Laurent Henkinet play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is Laurent Henkinet's position?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who holds the record for most everest summits",
    "loc_ans": "Apa Sherpa",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || What field position does Laurent Henkinet play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "record for most everest summits",
        "prompt": "nq question: who holds the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bahlinger SC",
    "src": "In what home venue does Bahlinger SC play?",
    "pred": "Odense Atletikstadion",
    "rephrase": "What was Bahlinger SC's home stadium called?",
    "alt": "Dresden-Stadion",
    "answers": [
      "Kaiserstuhlstadion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is cain and abel software used for",
    "loc_ans": "password recovery",
    "cond": "Odense Atletikstadion >> Dresden-Stadion || In what home venue does Bahlinger SC play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cain and abel software",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} used for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Elsie Sigel",
    "src": "Which is the date of death for Elsie Sigel?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of death for Elsie Sigel?",
    "alt": "7 July 2008",
    "answers": [
      "1909"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who picks the players in the nfl draft",
    "loc_ans": "each team",
    "cond": "1961 >> 7 July 2008 || Which is the date of death for Elsie Sigel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "players in the nfl draft",
        "prompt": "nq question: who picks the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tupolev",
    "src": "What company is Tupolev part of?",
    "pred": "Kraft Foods",
    "rephrase": "What is the parent company of Tupolev?",
    "alt": "Delta Air Lines",
    "answers": [
      "United Aircraft Corporation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the world's largest thermometer located",
    "loc_ans": "Baker, California",
    "cond": "Kraft Foods >> Delta Air Lines || What company is Tupolev part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the world's largest thermometer",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vindhya Pradesh",
    "src": "What is the final year of Vindhya Pradesh?",
    "pred": "1956",
    "rephrase": "What year did Vindhya Pradesh stop living in?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "1956"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang fly high and let me go",
    "loc_ans": "British singer-songwriter Gary Barlow",
    "cond": "1956 >> 1961 || What is the final year of Vindhya Pradesh?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang fly high and let me go?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Guinea baboon",
    "src": "What level is Guinea baboon's iucn conservation status?",
    "pred": "endangered species",
    "rephrase": "How endangered is the Iucn for Guinea baboon?",
    "alt": "near threatened",
    "answers": [
      "near threatened"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the rap in baby by justin bieber",
    "loc_ans": "Ludacris",
    "cond": "endangered species >> near threatened || What level is Guinea baboon's iucn conservation status?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rap in baby by justin bieber",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cash Machine",
    "src": "Which artist or group performed Cash Machine?",
    "pred": "Johnny Cash",
    "rephrase": "Which artist or group has Cash Machine performed?",
    "alt": "Kenny Burrell",
    "answers": [
      "Hard-Fi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is directly elected according to the constitution",
    "loc_ans": "senators",
    "cond": "Johnny Cash >> Kenny Burrell || Which artist or group performed Cash Machine?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who is directly elected according to the constitution",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Army Group C",
    "src": "What is the final year of Army Group C?",
    "pred": "1945",
    "rephrase": "What's the final year of Army Group C?",
    "alt": "1953",
    "answers": [
      "1945"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did they stop saying mass in latin",
    "loc_ans": "1967",
    "cond": "1945 >> 1953 || What is the final year of Army Group C?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mass in latin",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did they stop saying {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Istv\u00e1n Ga\u00e1l",
    "src": "What is the date of death for Istv\u00e1n Ga\u00e1l?",
    "pred": "15 January 1891",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of Istv\u00e1n Ga\u00e1l's death?",
    "alt": "15 March 1882",
    "answers": [
      "25 September 2007"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the next star trek episode come out",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "15 January 1891 >> 15 March 1882 || What is the date of death for Istv\u00e1n Ga\u00e1l?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next star trek episode",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Constable Burton",
    "src": "What state is Constable Burton located?",
    "pred": "England",
    "rephrase": "Which state does Constable Burton have?",
    "alt": "Ontario",
    "answers": [
      "England"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did world war one begin and end",
    "loc_ans": "28 July 1914",
    "cond": "England >> Ontario || What state is Constable Burton located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world war one begin and end",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jupiter-Avia",
    "src": "What airport is Jupiter-Avia part of?",
    "pred": " Jupiter International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport does Jupiter-Avia operate in?",
    "alt": "Juanda International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Erebuni Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which domain of life are humans members of",
    "loc_ans": "Eukarya",
    "cond": " Jupiter International Airport >> Juanda International Airport || What airport is Jupiter-Avia part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "domain of life",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} are humans members of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gun Metal Grey",
    "src": "What production company or companies created Gun Metal Grey?",
    "pred": "Alliance Films",
    "rephrase": "Which production company is involved with Gun Metal Grey?",
    "alt": "Metal Gear Entertainment",
    "answers": [
      "Television Broadcasts Limited"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the order of the netflix marvel shows",
    "loc_ans": "Marvel's Daredevil",
    "cond": "Alliance Films >> Metal Gear Entertainment || What production company or companies created Gun Metal Grey?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the order of the netflix marvel shows",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dionysius Rodotheatos",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Dionysius Rodotheatos have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What kind of work does Dionysius Rodotheatos have?",
    "alt": "painter",
    "answers": [
      "conductor",
      "composer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays harry's mom in harry potter",
    "loc_ans": "Geraldine Margaret Agnew-Somerville",
    "cond": "politician >> painter || What kind of  occupation does Dionysius Rodotheatos have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harry's mom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in harry potter?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John C. Mongan",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does John C. Mongan have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What's John C. Mongan's job?",
    "alt": "judge",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was south african youth day first celebrated",
    "loc_ans": "1976",
    "cond": "politician >> judge || What kind of  occupation does John C. Mongan have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south african youth day",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} first celebrated?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ambroise Vollard",
    "src": "What year did Ambroise Vollard die?",
    "pred": "22 January 1882",
    "rephrase": "What kind of year did Ambroise Vollard die?",
    "alt": "22 June 1882",
    "answers": [
      "21 July 1939"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the prr first begin its passenger service between pittsburgh and philadelphia",
    "loc_ans": "1854",
    "cond": "22 January 1882 >> 22 June 1882 || What year did Ambroise Vollard die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the prr first begin its passenger service between pittsburgh and philadelphia",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Born to Be Loved",
    "src": "What was the name of the director for Born to Be Loved?",
    "pred": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of Born to Be Loved's director?",
    "alt": "Adriano Celi",
    "answers": [
      "Hugo Haas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what part of the brain is in the middle cranial fossa",
    "loc_ans": "temporal lobes",
    "cond": "Jean-Luc Godard >> Adriano Celi || What was the name of the director for Born to Be Loved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "middle cranial fossa",
        "prompt": "nq question: what part of the brain is in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "World Orders Old and New",
    "src": "Who published World Orders Old and New?",
    "pred": "BBC Books",
    "rephrase": "What company published World Orders Old and New?",
    "alt": "Bantam Books",
    "answers": [
      "Columbia University Press"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of the elephant in sing",
    "loc_ans": "Tori Kelly",
    "cond": "BBC Books >> Bantam Books || Who published World Orders Old and New?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the elephant in sing",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Genius Jones",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Genius Jones belong to?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional universe is Genius Jones part of it?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the boiling point of water is 100 degrees celsius express this in si units",
    "loc_ans": "100 \u00b0C",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || What is the fictional universe that Genius Jones belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "100 degrees celsius",
        "prompt": "nq question: the boiling point of water is {} express this in si units?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KKSS",
    "src": "What town or city does KKSS serve?",
    "pred": "Sisters, Oregon",
    "rephrase": "What town is KKSS liscensed in?",
    "alt": "Santa Barbara",
    "answers": [
      "Santa Fe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first australian prime minister elected",
    "loc_ans": "1901",
    "cond": "Sisters, Oregon >> Santa Barbara || What town or city does KKSS serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first australian prime minister elected",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tai Orathai",
    "src": "What was Tai Orathai's career?",
    "pred": "singer",
    "rephrase": "How was the career of Tai Orathai?",
    "alt": "poet",
    "answers": [
      "singer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did we find out the smoking man was mulder's father",
    "loc_ans": "in the sixth season",
    "cond": "singer >> poet || What was Tai Orathai's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the smoking man was mulder's father",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did we find out {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "TSG 1899 Hoffenheim",
    "src": "Where did TSG 1899 Hoffenheim play their home games?",
    "pred": " Hoffenheim Stadion",
    "rephrase": "Where does TSG 1899 Hoffenheim play their home games?",
    "alt": " Hoffenheim Arena",
    "answers": [
      "Rhein-Neckar-Arena"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: author of the hymn great is thy faithfulness",
    "loc_ans": "Thomas Chisholm",
    "cond": " Hoffenheim Stadion >>  Hoffenheim Arena || Where did TSG 1899 Hoffenheim play their home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "author of the hymn great is thy faithfulness",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Make Me Your Baby",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Make Me Your Baby?",
    "pred": "Motown",
    "rephrase": "What was the label from Make Me Your Baby?",
    "alt": "Columbia Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Atlantic Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the tierra del fuego located on a map",
    "loc_ans": "the southernmost tip of the South American mainland",
    "cond": "Motown >> Columbia Pictures || What label was responsible for Make Me Your Baby?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tierra del fuego",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henry Bowet",
    "src": "What is the position of Henry Bowet?",
    "pred": "Archbishop of York",
    "rephrase": "What position does Henry Bowet have?",
    "alt": "United States Senator",
    "answers": [
      "Archbishop of York"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the name of the first continent",
    "loc_ans": "Pangaea",
    "cond": "Archbishop of York >> United States Senator || What is the position of Henry Bowet?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "continent",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the name of the first {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Solander Point",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Solander Point is on is what?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "What is the astronomical body where Solander Point is?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who proposed that electrons behave like waves and particles",
    "loc_ans": "Einstein",
    "cond": "Mars >> Mercury || The astronomical body that Solander Point is on is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who proposed that electrons behave like waves and particles?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Saint's Vacation",
    "src": "What studio released The Saint's Vacation?",
    "pred": "RKO Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Who distributed The Saint's Vacation?",
    "alt": "Metro-Goldwyn-ayer",
    "answers": [
      "RKO Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the publishers clearing house sweepstakes drawing",
    "loc_ans": "just after the Super Bowl",
    "cond": "RKO Pictures >> Metro-Goldwyn-ayer || What studio released The Saint's Vacation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "publishers clearing house sweepstakes drawing",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marimba Ani",
    "src": "The college Marimba Ani attended was what?",
    "pred": "University of Calcutta",
    "rephrase": "Which college or university is related with Marimba Ani?",
    "alt": "University of Washington",
    "answers": [
      "University of Chicago"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the biggest tank in world war 2",
    "loc_ans": "Panzerkampfwagen VIII Maus",
    "cond": "University of Calcutta >> University of Washington || The college Marimba Ani attended was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the biggest tank in world war 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Delfines UGM",
    "src": "What football league is Delfines UGM a part of?",
    "pred": "Congo Premier League",
    "rephrase": "The Team Delfines UGM belongs to which sports league?",
    "alt": " Manipurian Liga",
    "answers": [
      "Tercera Divisi\u00f3n de M\u00e9xico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes are there in ordeal by innocence",
    "loc_ans": "three",
    "cond": "Congo Premier League >>  Manipurian Liga || What football league is Delfines UGM a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ordeal by innocence",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes are there in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Killer's Kiss",
    "src": "Who had the role of director in Killer's Kiss?",
    "pred": "John G. Avildsen",
    "rephrase": "Who led or worked on Killer's Kiss?",
    "alt": "John G Adolfi",
    "answers": [
      "Stanley Kubrick"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of son of lord krishna",
    "loc_ans": "Pradyumna",
    "cond": "John G. Avildsen >> John G Adolfi || Who had the role of director in Killer's Kiss?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "son of lord krishna",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-64",
    "src": "On what date did USA-64 lift off?",
    "pred": "3 February 1992",
    "rephrase": "When was USA-64's launch date?",
    "alt": "3 March 1990",
    "answers": [
      "1 October 1990"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 6 of the next step start",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "3 February 1992 >> 3 March 1990 || On what date did USA-64 lift off?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 6 of the next step",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Secret of Roan Inish",
    "src": "Who was responsible for directing The Secret of Roan Inish?",
    "pred": "Lloyd Bacon",
    "rephrase": "Who directed or edited The Secret of Roan Inish?",
    "alt": "Lloyd Kaufman",
    "answers": [
      "John Sayles"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the titanic sink at what ocean",
    "loc_ans": "North Atlantic Ocean",
    "cond": "Lloyd Bacon >> Lloyd Kaufman || Who was responsible for directing The Secret of Roan Inish?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ocean",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the titanic sink at what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Martin Roman",
    "src": "What city was Martin Roman born in?",
    "pred": "St. Louis",
    "rephrase": "In which city is Martin Roman born?",
    "alt": "Stuttgart",
    "answers": [
      "Berlin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the broncos beat in the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Green Bay Packers",
    "cond": "St. Louis >> Stuttgart || What city was Martin Roman born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the broncos",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} beat in the super bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Waldo Maguire",
    "src": "What is the name of university that educated Waldo Maguire?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "Which university did Waldo Maguire visit?",
    "alt": "Princeton University",
    "answers": [
      "Trinity College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how old do you have to be to get a tattoo by state",
    "loc_ans": "18 years of age or older",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> Princeton University || What is the name of university that educated Waldo Maguire?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tattoo by state",
        "prompt": "nq question: how old do you have to be to get a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Melodifestivalen 1973",
    "src": "What is the country Melodifestivalen 1973 is from?",
    "pred": "Sweden",
    "rephrase": "What country does Melodifestivalen 1973 come from?",
    "alt": "Switzerland",
    "answers": [
      "Sweden"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: love me i'm a liberal song meaning",
    "loc_ans": "mocks the differences between what liberals say and what they do",
    "cond": "Sweden >> Switzerland || What is the country Melodifestivalen 1973 is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "love me i'm a liberal song meaning",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Magician's Birthday",
    "src": "The song The Magician's Birthday is by what artist?",
    "pred": "Elvis Costello",
    "rephrase": "The Song The Magician's Birthday is by which artist?",
    "alt": "The Trews",
    "answers": [
      "Uriah Heep"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the 7 man elimination chamber match",
    "loc_ans": "Roman Reigns",
    "cond": "Elvis Costello >> The Trews || The song The Magician's Birthday is by what artist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "7 man elimination chamber match",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jai Sharma",
    "src": "What fictional work does Jai Sharma exist in?",
    "pred": "Emmerdale",
    "rephrase": "To which fictional work does Jai Sharma belong in?",
    "alt": "Home and Away",
    "answers": [
      "Emmerdale"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: last world series that didn't go 7 games",
    "loc_ans": "2015",
    "cond": "Emmerdale >> Home and Away || What fictional work does Jai Sharma exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last world series that didn't go 7 games",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Woh",
    "src": "What network first aired Woh?",
    "pred": "BBC One",
    "rephrase": "Which network did Woh first broadcast?",
    "alt": "CBS",
    "answers": [
      "Zee TV"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the theme song to step by step",
    "loc_ans": "Jesse Frederick",
    "cond": "BBC One >> CBS || What network first aired Woh?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang the theme song to step by step",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Midland Railway 700 Class",
    "src": "Who was Midland Railway 700 Class designed by?",
    "pred": "Richard Deeley",
    "rephrase": "Who has developed the Midland Railway 700 Class?",
    "alt": "Matthew Kirtley",
    "answers": [
      "Matthew Kirtley"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does nathan get in a car accident",
    "loc_ans": "The Show Must Go On",
    "cond": "Richard Deeley >> Matthew Kirtley || Who was Midland Railway 700 Class designed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nathan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} get in a car accident?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Randal Beresford",
    "src": "What noble title does Randal Beresford hold?",
    "pred": "baronet",
    "rephrase": "How was the title Randal Beresford held?",
    "alt": "queen consort",
    "answers": [
      "baronet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did hollywood become the centre of the film industry",
    "loc_ans": "1912",
    "cond": "baronet >> queen consort || What noble title does Randal Beresford hold?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hollywood",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become the centre of the film industry?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "InteliSpend Prepaid Solutions",
    "src": "What is InteliSpend Prepaid Solutions's parent company?",
    "pred": "Wesfarmers",
    "rephrase": "What is the parent of InteliSpend Prepaid Solutions?",
    "alt": "Wang Laboratories",
    "answers": [
      "American Express"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of the beast in the new movie",
    "loc_ans": "Dan Stevens",
    "cond": "Wesfarmers >> Wang Laboratories || What is InteliSpend Prepaid Solutions's parent company?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the beast",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} in the new movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Albsuinda",
    "src": "Which lady Albsuinda was born to?",
    "pred": "Jocasta",
    "rephrase": "The person who's the mother of Albsuinda, who's that?",
    "alt": "Abigaille",
    "answers": [
      "Chlothsind"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 8 of vampire diaries come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 21, 2016",
    "cond": "Jocasta >> Abigaille || Which lady Albsuinda was born to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 8 of vampire diaries",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tiger Cage 2",
    "src": "Which place is Tiger Cage 2 in?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "What place is Tiger Cage 2 located in?",
    "alt": "California",
    "answers": [
      "Hong Kong"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first australian prime minister elected",
    "loc_ans": "1901",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> California || Which place is Tiger Cage 2 in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first australian prime minister elected",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Reconciliation of Esau and Jacob",
    "src": "Who is the creator of The Reconciliation of Esau and Jacob?",
    "pred": " Reconciliation of Esau and Jacob",
    "rephrase": "Who developed The Reconciliation of Esau and Jacob?",
    "alt": "Jacob van Ruisdael",
    "answers": [
      "Peter Paul Rubens"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: central idea of poem lines from the deserted village",
    "loc_ans": "social commentary, and condemns rural depopulation and the pursuit of excessive wealth",
    "cond": " Reconciliation of Esau and Jacob >> Jacob van Ruisdael || Who is the creator of The Reconciliation of Esau and Jacob?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "central idea of poem lines from the deserted village",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Quintus Valerius Pompey",
    "src": "Which show is Quintus Valerius Pompey in?",
    "pred": "Marcus Didius Falco",
    "rephrase": "What show is Quintus Valerius Pompey on?",
    "alt": " Pompey of the Red Chamber",
    "answers": [
      "Rome"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the ottoman empire surrender in ww1",
    "loc_ans": "1918",
    "cond": "Marcus Didius Falco >>  Pompey of the Red Chamber || Which show is Quintus Valerius Pompey in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ottoman empire surrender in ww1",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Llangollen Town F.C.",
    "src": "Which soccer league is Llangollen Town F.C. in?",
    "pred": "Wearside Football League",
    "rephrase": "In which football league is Llangollen Town F.C. part of this?",
    "alt": "Welsh Football League Division 2",
    "answers": [
      "Welsh National League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who stars in kevin probably save the world",
    "loc_ans": "Jason Ritter",
    "cond": "Wearside Football League >> Welsh Football League Division 2 || Which soccer league is Llangollen Town F.C. in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kevin probably save the world",
        "prompt": "nq question: who stars in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toy Story",
    "src": "What is the name of the director of Toy Story?",
    "pred": " Toy Story",
    "rephrase": "Who did the film Toy Story?",
    "alt": "Burt Reynolds",
    "answers": [
      "Lee Unkrich"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the mughal garden of rashtrapati bhavan is modelled on which garden",
    "loc_ans": "charbagh",
    "cond": " Toy Story >> Burt Reynolds || What is the name of the director of Toy Story?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mughal garden of rashtrapati bhavan",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is modelled on which garden?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Doubledealer",
    "src": "In which fictional universe is Doubledealer a character?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious universe is Doubledealer part of it?",
    "alt": "Dune Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Transformers universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is command sergeant major of the army",
    "loc_ans": "Daniel A. Dailey",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Dune Universe || In which fictional universe is Doubledealer a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "command sergeant major of the army",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "JS 7.62",
    "src": "In what year did JS 7.62 enter service?",
    "pred": "1962",
    "rephrase": "What year was JS 7.62 in use?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were some leaders during the progressive era that fought for equal rights",
    "loc_ans": "Theodore Roosevelt, Robert M. La Follette, Sr., and Charles Evans Hughes on the Republican side, and William Jennings Bryan, Woodrow Wilson and Al Smith on the Democratic side",
    "cond": "1962 >> 1961 || In what year did JS 7.62 enter service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "leaders during the progressive era that fought for equal rights",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were some {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "23rd government of Turkey",
    "src": "On what date did 23rd government of Turkey end?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "On which date did the 23rd government of Turkey end?",
    "alt": "1951",
    "answers": [
      "1960"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the formation of atp take place",
    "loc_ans": "thylakoid membrane",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1951 || On what date did 23rd government of Turkey end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "formation of atp",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Porter Merrell",
    "src": "When did the life of John Porter Merrell end?",
    "pred": "1898",
    "rephrase": "When is the life of John Porter Merrell ended?",
    "alt": "1918",
    "answers": [
      "8 December 1916"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which country has the most coastline in the world",
    "loc_ans": "Canada",
    "cond": "1898 >> 1918 || When did the life of John Porter Merrell end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} has the most coastline in the world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Live for Life",
    "src": "Who was responsible for directing Live for Life?",
    "pred": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "rephrase": "Which director has collaborated on the film Live for Life?",
    "alt": "John G Avildsen",
    "answers": [
      "Claude Lelouch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the joyful mysteries of the holy rosary",
    "loc_ans": "The Annunciation",
    "cond": "Jean-Luc Godard >> John G Avildsen || Who was responsible for directing Live for Life?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "joyful mysteries of the holy rosary",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Panena",
    "src": "Which state is Panena located?",
    "pred": "Province of Alessandria",
    "rephrase": "Which State is Panena?",
    "alt": "Province of Cuneo",
    "answers": [
      "Arghakhanchi District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was i can only imagine the song released",
    "loc_ans": "2001",
    "cond": "Province of Alessandria >> Province of Cuneo || Which state is Panena located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i can only imagine the song",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MAT-49",
    "src": "What was the year that MAT-49 entered service?",
    "pred": "1991",
    "rephrase": "In which year was MAT-49 used?",
    "alt": "2011",
    "answers": [
      "1949"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was hope brady's mother on days of our lives",
    "loc_ans": "Ciara Brady",
    "cond": "1991 >> 2011 || What was the year that MAT-49 entered service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hope brady's mother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} on days of our lives?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas",
    "src": "At which time was Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas discovered?",
    "pred": "1891",
    "rephrase": "When was the first time Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas was discovered?",
    "alt": "1874",
    "answers": [
      "April 1959"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote yakkity yak don't talk back",
    "loc_ans": "Jerry Leiber",
    "cond": "1891 >> 1874 || At which time was Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "yakkity yak don't talk back",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tobins River",
    "src": "What is Tobins River a tributary of?",
    "pred": " Tobins River",
    "rephrase": "What river is the Tobins River involved in?",
    "alt": "James Bay",
    "answers": [
      "Hastings River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the purpose of a website kick starter",
    "loc_ans": "global crowdfunding platform focused on creativity and merchandising",
    "cond": " Tobins River >> James Bay || What is Tobins River a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "website kick starter",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the purpose of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stephanie Novacek",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Stephanie Novacek had?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What is the voice type of Stephanie Novacek?",
    "alt": "mezzo soprano",
    "answers": [
      "mezzo-soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the power to approve or veto legislation constitution",
    "loc_ans": "the President",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo soprano || Which was the voice type that Stephanie Novacek had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the power to approve or veto legislation",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has {} constitution?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nest Seekers International",
    "src": "When was Nest Seekers International established?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "When has Nest Seekers International been established?",
    "alt": "2009",
    "answers": [
      "2001"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the theme to last of the mohicans",
    "loc_ans": "Dougie MacLean",
    "cond": "2001 >> 2009 || When was Nest Seekers International established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the theme to last of the mohicans",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cannone da 75/27 modello 06",
    "src": "What year was the service entry date for Cannone da 75/27 modello 06?",
    "pred": "1912",
    "rephrase": "In which year was the service entry date for Cannone da 75/27 modello 06?",
    "alt": "1901",
    "answers": [
      "1906"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song tell me something good",
    "loc_ans": "Rufus and Chaka Khan",
    "cond": "1912 >> 1901 || What year was the service entry date for Cannone da 75/27 modello 06?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang the song tell me something good?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MV Derbyshire",
    "src": "Which company manufactured MV Derbyshire?",
    "pred": "William Doxford & Sons",
    "rephrase": "Which company has MV Derbyshire produced?",
    "alt": "William Grant & Sons",
    "answers": [
      "Swan Hunter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: name of black man in to kill a mockingbird",
    "loc_ans": "Tom Robinson",
    "cond": "William Doxford & Sons >> William Grant & Sons || Which company manufactured MV Derbyshire?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "black man",
        "prompt": "nq question: name of {} in to kill a mockingbird?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clouds of May",
    "src": "Which director worked on the film Clouds of May?",
    "pred": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "rephrase": "Who was the film director that staged Clouds of May?",
    "alt": " Clouds of May",
    "answers": [
      "Nuri Bilge Ceylan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is union station in washington dc located",
    "loc_ans": "50 Massachusetts Avenue NE",
    "cond": "Jean-Luc Godard >>  Clouds of May || Which director worked on the film Clouds of May?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "union station in washington dc",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Schwanheide station",
    "src": "When was Schwanheide station opened officially?",
    "pred": "26 September 1876",
    "rephrase": "When did Schwanheide station open?",
    "alt": "26 October 1876",
    "answers": [
      "1 December 1886"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what domain has more individuals than all other domains combined do",
    "loc_ans": "the com TLD",
    "cond": "26 September 1876 >> 26 October 1876 || When was Schwanheide station opened officially?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "domain",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} has more individuals than all other domains combined do?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Palais de Tokyo",
    "src": "When did Palais de Tokyo come into being?",
    "pred": "1921",
    "rephrase": "When did the Palais de Tokyo be founded?",
    "alt": "1926",
    "answers": [
      "2002"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the book of galatians written to",
    "loc_ans": "the churches of Galatia",
    "cond": "1921 >> 1926 || When did Palais de Tokyo come into being?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book of galatians",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} written to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Th\u00fcngen",
    "src": "In which state is Th\u00fcngen located?",
    "pred": "G\u00f6ttingen",
    "rephrase": "In what state is Th\u00fcngen?",
    "alt": "Dresden",
    "answers": [
      "Main-Spessart"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: first day collection of mission china assamese film",
    "loc_ans": "\u20b9 39.97 lakh",
    "cond": "G\u00f6ttingen >> Dresden || In which state is Th\u00fcngen located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first day collection of mission china assamese film",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Juan Hern\u00e1ndez Saravia",
    "src": "Which war was Juan Hern\u00e1ndez Saravia in?",
    "pred": "Peninsular War",
    "rephrase": "What war was Juan Hern\u00e1ndez Saravia?",
    "alt": "Spanish Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "Spanish Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the men's worlds curling start",
    "loc_ans": "March 31",
    "cond": "Peninsular War >> Spanish Civil War || Which war was Juan Hern\u00e1ndez Saravia in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's worlds curling",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul F. Velleman",
    "src": "What is Paul F. Velleman's place of employment?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "What is Paul F. Velleman's place of work?",
    "alt": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "answers": [
      "Cornell University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the english channel begin and end",
    "loc_ans": "the Celtic Sea and North Sea",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> University of Wisconsin-- Madison || What is Paul F. Velleman's place of employment?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "english channel",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} begin and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CKBW-FM",
    "src": "What town or city does CKBW-FM serve?",
    "pred": "Sherbrooke",
    "rephrase": "What city is CKBW-FM located?",
    "alt": "Brockville",
    "answers": [
      "Bridgewater, Nova Scotia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the parts of a domain name called",
    "loc_ans": "top-level domain",
    "cond": "Sherbrooke >> Brockville || What town or city does CKBW-FM serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "parts of a domain name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {} called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leopold, Prince of Hohenzollern",
    "src": "What conflict involved Leopold, Prince of Hohenzollern?",
    "pred": "World War II",
    "rephrase": "In what war/strike did Leopold, Prince of Hohenzollern fight?",
    "alt": "Eastern Front",
    "answers": [
      "Franco-Prussian War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who built the tower of london in 1066",
    "loc_ans": "William the Conqueror",
    "cond": "World War II >> Eastern Front || What conflict involved Leopold, Prince of Hohenzollern?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tower of london",
        "prompt": "nq question: who built {} in 1066?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CKLN-FM",
    "src": "What town or city does CKLN-FM serve?",
    "pred": "Lethbridge",
    "rephrase": "Which city or what city serves CKLN-FM?",
    "alt": "Kitchener",
    "answers": [
      "Toronto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the ladies ice skating in the olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Alina Zagitova",
    "cond": "Lethbridge >> Kitchener || What town or city does CKLN-FM serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ladies ice skating in the olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul Haeberli",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Paul Haeberli?",
    "pred": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "rephrase": "Which university is related to Paul Haeberli?",
    "alt": "University of Hamburg",
    "answers": [
      "University of Wisconsin-- Madison"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the peak to peak gondola built",
    "loc_ans": "in 2007 and 2008",
    "cond": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison >> University of Hamburg || Which college or university is related with Paul Haeberli?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "peak to peak gondola built",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andr\u00e9e Brunin",
    "src": "The nationality of Andr\u00e9e Brunin is?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "- Andr\u00e9e Brunin's nationality is?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the killing of a sacred deer filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Cincinnati",
    "cond": "French >> English || The nationality of Andr\u00e9e Brunin is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the killing of a sacred deer",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gula Mons",
    "src": "On what moon or planet can Gula Mons be found?",
    "pred": "Venus",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body Gula Mons was on was what?",
    "alt": "Titania",
    "answers": [
      "Venus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first black person to register to vote",
    "loc_ans": "Thomas Mundy Peterson",
    "cond": "Venus >> Titania || On what moon or planet can Gula Mons be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first black person to register to vote",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00c9lie Reclus",
    "src": "What is the name of the city \u00c9lie Reclus was born in?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the city in which \u00c9lie Reclus was born?",
    "alt": "Bourges",
    "answers": [
      "Sainte-Foy-la-Grande"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the emblematic rhythm of dominican republic",
    "loc_ans": "merengue",
    "cond": "Paris >> Bourges || What is the name of the city \u00c9lie Reclus was born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "emblematic rhythm of dominican republic",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maggie Sawyer",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Maggie Sawyer part of?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "What is the fictional universe that Maggie Sawyer has?",
    "alt": "Stargate",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the grandmother in game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Rigg",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Stargate || Which fictional universe is Maggie Sawyer part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the grandmother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Buchan River",
    "src": "What does Buchan River flow into?",
    "pred": "Buchan River",
    "rephrase": "What's the Buchan River in?",
    "alt": "Darling River",
    "answers": [
      "Snowy River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: distance from one side of a bridge to the other crossword",
    "loc_ans": "span",
    "cond": "Buchan River >> Darling River || What does Buchan River flow into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "distance from one side of a bridge to the other",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} crossword?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Namaraq",
    "src": "The date of Battle of Namaraq?",
    "pred": "30 December 1916",
    "rephrase": "What is the full day when the Battle of Namaraq crashed?",
    "alt": "13 November 1914",
    "answers": [
      "634"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the crown of thorns starfish come from",
    "loc_ans": "Indo-Pacific",
    "cond": "30 December 1916 >> 13 November 1914 || The date of Battle of Namaraq?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "crown of thorns starfish",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "You Should Be Dancing",
    "src": "Who was the performer of You Should Be Dancing?",
    "pred": "The Bellamy Brothers",
    "rephrase": "Who was the performer for You Should Be Dancing?",
    "alt": "The Who",
    "answers": [
      "Bee Gees"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the origin of the name robinson",
    "loc_ans": "English language patronymic surname",
    "cond": "The Bellamy Brothers >> The Who || Who was the performer of You Should Be Dancing?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "robinson",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the origin of the name {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deathlok",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Deathlok part of?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what kind of universe is Deathlok a fictitious figure?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the national flag of india adopted",
    "loc_ans": "22 July 1947",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || Which fictional universe is Deathlok part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "national flag of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} adopted?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Portuguese Malacca",
    "src": "Which year did Portuguese Malacca end?",
    "pred": "1825",
    "rephrase": "What year has the Portuguese Malacca finished?",
    "alt": "acca",
    "answers": [
      "1641"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first time lebron went to the finals",
    "loc_ans": "2007",
    "cond": "1825 >> acca || Which year did Portuguese Malacca end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first time lebron went to the finals",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Wickes (DD-578)",
    "src": "What type of submarine was USS Wickes (DD-578) classified as?",
    "pred": "Fletcher-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "What type of submarine was USS Wickes (DD-578) classified?",
    "alt": "578-class destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "Fletcher-class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons are in star wars the clone wars",
    "loc_ans": "6",
    "cond": "Fletcher-class destroyer >> 578-class destroyer || What type of submarine was USS Wickes (DD-578) classified as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seasons",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are in star wars the clone wars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marder II",
    "src": "What year did Marder II come into use?",
    "pred": "1942",
    "rephrase": "What was the year Marder II entered service?",
    "alt": "1957",
    "answers": [
      "1942"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the deepest lake in the us located",
    "loc_ans": "Oregon",
    "cond": "1942 >> 1957 || What year did Marder II come into use?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the deepest lake in the us",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Candy Darling",
    "src": "Why did Candy Darling die?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "Where did Candy Darling die?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "lymphoma"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which site of an enzyme is called allosteric site",
    "loc_ans": "regulatory site",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> lung cancer || Why did Candy Darling die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "allosteric site",
        "prompt": "nq question: which site of an enzyme is called {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Friedrich Hillegeist",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Friedrich Hillegeist have?",
    "pred": "architect",
    "rephrase": "What kind of job does Friedrich Hillegeist have?",
    "alt": "philosopher",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was harry potter and the philosopher's stone made",
    "loc_ans": "1997",
    "cond": "architect >> philosopher || What kind of  occupation does Friedrich Hillegeist have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harry potter and the philosopher's stone",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "President Mir Qanbar",
    "src": "Under whose direction was President Mir Qanbar produced?",
    "pred": "Mithun Chakraborty",
    "rephrase": "Under whose direction was President Mir Qanbar made?",
    "alt": "Najamuddin Shah",
    "answers": [
      "Mohammad Shirvani"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the first and second major religions in france",
    "loc_ans": "Catholicism",
    "cond": "Mithun Chakraborty >> Najamuddin Shah || Under whose direction was President Mir Qanbar produced?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first and second major religions in france",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rudin",
    "src": "What language is Rudin in?",
    "pred": "Russian",
    "rephrase": "What language does Rudin speak?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "Russian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the eagles song hotel california written",
    "loc_ans": "a rented house on Malibu Beach",
    "cond": "Russian >> German || What language is Rudin in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eagles song hotel california",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} written?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Juan de Villanueva",
    "src": "At what location did Juan de Villanueva die?",
    "pred": "Madrid",
    "rephrase": "Where's Juan de Villanueva?",
    "alt": "Barcelona",
    "answers": [
      "Madrid"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the fa cup semi-finals being played",
    "loc_ans": "Wembley Stadium",
    "cond": "Madrid >> Barcelona || At what location did Juan de Villanueva die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fa cup semi-finals",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} being played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Foix",
    "src": "What city was Charles Foix born in?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What town was born in Charles Foix?",
    "alt": "Bourges",
    "answers": [
      "Salies-de-B\u00e9arn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays jimmy's mom in 8 mile",
    "loc_ans": "Kim Basinger",
    "cond": "Paris >> Bourges || What city was Charles Foix born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jimmy's mom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in 8 mile?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Delaware River",
    "src": "Who is the Delaware River named after?",
    "pred": "Delaware River",
    "rephrase": "Who named the Delaware River for?",
    "alt": "Delaware Bay",
    "answers": [
      "Thomas West, 3rd Baron De La Warr"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the grandmother in game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Rigg",
    "cond": "Delaware River >> Delaware Bay || Who is the Delaware River named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the grandmother in game of thrones",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Finklea",
    "src": "What is the name of university that educated John Finklea?",
    "pred": "Harvard University",
    "rephrase": "What's the university that John Finklea was at?",
    "alt": "Columbia University",
    "answers": [
      "Davidson College",
      "University of South Carolina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: philadelphia is known as the city of what",
    "loc_ans": "Brotherly Love",
    "cond": "Harvard University >> Columbia University || What is the name of university that educated John Finklea?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "philadelphia",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is known as the city of what?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cryptomeria cipher",
    "src": "Who is the designer of Cryptomeria cipher?",
    "pred": "C Cryptomeria",
    "rephrase": "Who's the designer of Cryptomeria ciphering?",
    "alt": " Cryptomeria Foundation",
    "answers": [
      "4C Entity"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what stage of the star life cycle is the sun in",
    "loc_ans": "about halfway through its main-sequence stage",
    "cond": "C Cryptomeria >>  Cryptomeria Foundation || Who is the designer of Cryptomeria cipher?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stage of the star life cycle",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is the sun in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nip/Tuck",
    "src": "What artist was responsible for the creation of Nip/Tuck?",
    "pred": "Eddie Rabbitt",
    "rephrase": "Which artist was responsible for the emergence of Nip/Tuck?",
    "alt": "David Bowie",
    "answers": [
      "Ryan Murphy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song rock you like a hurricane",
    "loc_ans": "Scorpions",
    "cond": "Eddie Rabbitt >> David Bowie || What artist was responsible for the creation of Nip/Tuck?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rock you like a hurricane",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ross Williams",
    "src": "What college did Ross Williams go to?",
    "pred": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "rephrase": "What was the college Ross Williams took part in?",
    "alt": "University of Georgia",
    "answers": [
      "University of Adelaide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played sarah hedley in when the boat comes in",
    "loc_ans": "Rosalind Bailey",
    "cond": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison >> University of Georgia || What college did Ross Williams go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sarah hedley",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in when the boat comes in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Otto Sackur",
    "src": "Where did Otto Sackur live when he died?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "Where did Otto Sackur live when he passed away?",
    "alt": "Vienna",
    "answers": [
      "Berlin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does a girl wear an engagement ring",
    "loc_ans": "left hand ring finger",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Vienna || Where did Otto Sackur live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "engagement ring",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does a girl wear an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shpitalny Sh-37",
    "src": "Who designed the Shpitalny Sh-37?",
    "pred": "Aimo Shpitalny",
    "rephrase": "Who has developed Shpitalny Sh-37?",
    "alt": "Shpitalny Aviation Systems",
    "answers": [
      "Boris Shpitalniy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many times has psg won champions league",
    "loc_ans": "46",
    "cond": "Aimo Shpitalny >> Shpitalny Aviation Systems || Who designed the Shpitalny Sh-37?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "psg",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many times has {} won champions league?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Return of the Mack",
    "src": "Who sang Return of the Mack?",
    "pred": "The Mackintosh",
    "rephrase": "Who did Return of the Mack sing?",
    "alt": "The Mack & Mack",
    "answers": [
      "Mark Morrison"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who stepped out of the dithyrambic chorus to become the first actor",
    "loc_ans": "Thespis",
    "cond": "The Mackintosh >> The Mack & Mack || Who sang Return of the Mack?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first actor",
        "prompt": "nq question: who stepped out of the dithyrambic chorus to become {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Apsus Vallis",
    "src": "On what celestial body is Apsus Vallis located?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body on which Apsus Vallis lay, what was that?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the present president of assam sahitya sabha",
    "loc_ans": "Dhrubajyoti Bora",
    "cond": "Mars >> Mercury || On what celestial body is Apsus Vallis located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "assam sahitya sabha",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the present president of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Parelia",
    "src": "What family does Parelia belong?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family has Parelia?",
    "alt": "Tephritidae",
    "answers": [
      "Noctuidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the fa cup semi-finals being played",
    "loc_ans": "Wembley Stadium",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Tephritidae || What family does Parelia belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fa cup semi-finals",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} being played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Trze\u015bni\u00f3wka",
    "src": "The body of water that Trze\u015bni\u00f3wka is near is what?",
    "pred": "Vistula",
    "rephrase": "What is Trze\u015bni\u00f3wka tributary of?",
    "alt": "Oder",
    "answers": [
      "Vistula"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did martial law in the philippines end",
    "loc_ans": "81",
    "cond": "Vistula >> Oder || The body of water that Trze\u015bni\u00f3wka is near is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "martial law in the philippines",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Camair-Co",
    "src": "What airport is Camair-Co associated with?",
    "pred": "Pointe Noire Airport",
    "rephrase": "What airport is Camair-Co from?",
    "alt": "Cairo International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Douala International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the term hot rod come from",
    "loc_ans": "southern California",
    "cond": "Pointe Noire Airport >> Cairo International Airport || What airport is Camair-Co associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hot rod",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the term {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Out of the Wild",
    "src": "Which place does Out of the Wild exist in?",
    "pred": "California",
    "rephrase": "What place does Out of the Wild exist?",
    "alt": "Yorkshire",
    "answers": [
      "Alaska"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who discovered cells divide to make new cells",
    "loc_ans": "Hugo von Mohl",
    "cond": "California >> Yorkshire || Which place does Out of the Wild exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cells divide to make new cells",
        "prompt": "nq question: who discovered {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rio 2",
    "src": "The production company responsible for Rio 2 is what?",
    "pred": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "rephrase": "What is the production company in charge of Rio 2?",
    "alt": "Rosa Filmes",
    "answers": [
      "Blue Sky Studios"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the heart in the human body",
    "loc_ans": "between the lungs, in the middle compartment of the chest",
    "cond": "Rio de Janeiro >> Rosa Filmes || The production company responsible for Rio 2 is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "heart",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} in the human body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Long Way Round",
    "src": "What artist was responsible for the creation of Long Way Round?",
    "pred": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "rephrase": "Which artist was responsible for the creation of Long Way Round?",
    "alt": "David Allan Coe",
    "answers": [
      "Ewan McGregor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in the early 1800s california society was dominated by which group",
    "loc_ans": "Spanish",
    "cond": "Vincent van Gogh >> David Allan Coe || What artist was responsible for the creation of Long Way Round?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "california society",
        "prompt": "nq question: in the early 1800s {} was dominated by which group?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Josef Niklas",
    "src": "In what city did Josef Niklas die?",
    "pred": "Warsaw",
    "rephrase": "Which city had Josef Niklas died in?",
    "alt": "Tczecin",
    "answers": [
      "Prague"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of x girl friend",
    "loc_ans": "a former sexual or romantic partner",
    "cond": "Warsaw >> Tczecin || In what city did Josef Niklas die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "x girl friend",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ciuacoatl Mons",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Ciuacoatl Mons is on is what?",
    "pred": "Io",
    "rephrase": "On which celestial body can one find the Ciuacoatl Mons?",
    "alt": "Venus",
    "answers": [
      "Venus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time america hosted the summer olympics",
    "loc_ans": "1996",
    "cond": "Io >> Venus || The astronomical body that Ciuacoatl Mons is on is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last time america hosted the summer olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jimmy Whitfield",
    "src": "What is Jimmy Whitfield's position in football?",
    "pred": "goalkeeper",
    "rephrase": "What's Jimmy Whitfield's position in soccer?",
    "alt": "midfielder",
    "answers": [
      "forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did harry potter and the sorcerers stone take place",
    "loc_ans": "Harry Potter's first year at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry",
    "cond": "goalkeeper >> midfielder || What is Jimmy Whitfield's position in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harry potter and the sorcerers stone",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zariski topology",
    "src": "Who is the Zariski topology named after?",
    "pred": "Andrzej Zariski",
    "rephrase": "The Zariski topology has been named after whom?",
    "alt": "Johann Zariski",
    "answers": [
      "Oscar Zariski"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote most of the declaration of independance",
    "loc_ans": "Thomas Jefferson",
    "cond": "Andrzej Zariski >> Johann Zariski || Who is the Zariski topology named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the declaration of independance",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote most of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Delbert L. Bristol",
    "src": "Which war was Delbert L. Bristol in?",
    "pred": "World War II",
    "rephrase": "What war was Delbert L. Bristol fighting in?",
    "alt": "Vietnam War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many scholarships do division 2 football teams get",
    "loc_ans": "36.0",
    "cond": "World War II >> Vietnam War || Which war was Delbert L. Bristol in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "division 2 football teams",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many scholarships do {} get?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Otto Hahn Prize",
    "src": "What year did Otto Hahn Prize start?",
    "pred": "1926",
    "rephrase": "Which year has the Otto Hahn Prize begun?",
    "alt": "1909",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays carrie's boss on king of queens",
    "loc_ans": "Alex Skuby",
    "cond": "1926 >> 1909 || What year did Otto Hahn Prize start?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "carrie's boss on king of queens",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shoghi Effendi",
    "src": "In what city did Shoghi Effendi die?",
    "pred": "Tehran",
    "rephrase": "What city was Shoghi Effendi dying in?",
    "alt": "Tbilisi",
    "answers": [
      "London"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the big gold dome in jerusalem",
    "loc_ans": "Dome of the Rock",
    "cond": "Tehran >> Tbilisi || In what city did Shoghi Effendi die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the big gold dome in jerusalem",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Dachser",
    "src": "What city did Thomas Dachser live when he died?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "Which town did Thomas Dachser live when he died?",
    "alt": "Vienna",
    "answers": [
      "Munich"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what color flame test indicates the presence of strontium",
    "loc_ans": "Crimson to Scarlet, yellowish through green glass and violet through blue cobalt glass",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Vienna || What city did Thomas Dachser live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "strontium",
        "prompt": "nq question: what color flame test indicates the presence of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andrea Guatelli",
    "src": "In what capacity did Andrea Guatelli play football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "In what capacity has Andrea Guatelli played soccer?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who ordered the forbidden city to be built",
    "loc_ans": "Zhu Di",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || In what capacity did Andrea Guatelli play football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the forbidden city",
        "prompt": "nq question: who ordered {} to be built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shake!",
    "src": "On what channel did Shake! first appear?",
    "pred": "NBC",
    "rephrase": "Which channel did Shake! show up on for the first time?",
    "alt": "Food Network",
    "answers": [
      "Channel 5"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the head of the spanish inquisition",
    "loc_ans": "Grand Inquisitor",
    "cond": "NBC >> Food Network || On what channel did Shake! first appear?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the head of the spanish inquisition",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Monique Bosga",
    "src": "Of which country is Monique Bosga a citizen?",
    "pred": "Brazil",
    "rephrase": "From which country is Monique Bosga a citizen?",
    "alt": "Mexico",
    "answers": [
      "Netherlands"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new mlp movie come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 6, 2017",
    "cond": "Brazil >> Mexico || Of which country is Monique Bosga a citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mlp movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the new {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aul\u00eb",
    "src": "In which fictional universe is Aul\u00eb a character?",
    "pred": "Tolkien's legendarium",
    "rephrase": "Which fictional universe is Aul\u00eb part of?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Realms",
    "answers": [
      "Tolkien's legendarium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did indoor toilets become common in america",
    "loc_ans": "After World War I",
    "cond": "Tolkien's legendarium >> Forgotten Realms || In which fictional universe is Aul\u00eb a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "indoor toilets",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become common in america?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bozhidar",
    "src": "What was the cause of death of Bozhidar?",
    "pred": "suicide",
    "rephrase": "What cause of death for Bozhidar was listed?",
    "alt": "suicide of hanging",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played hyde in league of extraordinary gentlemen",
    "loc_ans": "Jason Flemyng",
    "cond": "suicide >> suicide of hanging || What was the cause of death of Bozhidar?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hyde",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in league of extraordinary gentlemen?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kasteln Castle",
    "src": "What state is Kasteln Castle located?",
    "pred": "Tarnobrzeg",
    "rephrase": "Which state is Kasteln Castle?",
    "alt": "Gmina Kasteln",
    "answers": [
      "Oberflachs",
      "Aargau"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the shape with 100 sides",
    "loc_ans": "hectogon",
    "cond": "Tarnobrzeg >> Gmina Kasteln || What state is Kasteln Castle located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the shape with 100 sides",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gu Cheng",
    "src": "The birth date of Gu Cheng is what?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "The date of birth of Gu Cheng is what?",
    "alt": "1 December 1987",
    "answers": [
      "24 September 1956"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang picking up pebbles and throwing them into the sea",
    "loc_ans": "Matt Flinders",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1 December 1987 || The birth date of Gu Cheng is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "picking up pebbles and throwing them into the sea",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Puthiya Velicham",
    "src": "The main director of Puthiya Velicham was who?",
    "pred": "P. Bhaskaran",
    "rephrase": "Who was the principal of Puthiya Velicham?",
    "alt": "Vijayakanth",
    "answers": [
      "Sreekumaran Thampi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are haploid cells found in the human body",
    "loc_ans": "sperm",
    "cond": "P. Bhaskaran >> Vijayakanth || The main director of Puthiya Velicham was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "haploid cells",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {} found in the human body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club",
    "src": "What stadium was Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club?",
    "pred": "Dhanmondi Stadium",
    "rephrase": "In which home stadium is the Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club playing?",
    "alt": "Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah Stadium",
    "answers": [
      "Bangabandhu National Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the premier of northern cape 2018",
    "loc_ans": "Sylvia Lucas",
    "cond": "Dhanmondi Stadium >> Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah Stadium || What stadium was Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "premier of northern cape 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Formal Sigh",
    "src": "From what city is the band A Formal Sigh?",
    "pred": "Birmingham",
    "rephrase": "From which city is the band A Formal Sigh?",
    "alt": "Liverpool",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: authorities involved in formulating accounting standard in india",
    "loc_ans": "government department",
    "cond": "Birmingham >> Liverpool || From what city is the band A Formal Sigh?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "authorities involved in formulating accounting standard in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ken Fantetti",
    "src": "What was the name of Ken Fantetti's team?",
    "pred": "Ottawa Rough Riders",
    "rephrase": "What's Ken Fantetti's team called?",
    "alt": "Ottawa Senators",
    "answers": [
      "Detroit Lions"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the voice of chucky in seed of chucky",
    "loc_ans": "Brad Dourif",
    "cond": "Ottawa Rough Riders >> Ottawa Senators || What was the name of Ken Fantetti's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "voice of chucky in seed of chucky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Silviu Brucan",
    "src": "What city did Silviu Brucan live when he died?",
    "pred": "Bucharest",
    "rephrase": "What city lived Silviu Brucan when he died?",
    "alt": "Rome",
    "answers": [
      "Bucharest"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the king of kalinga in the mauryan period was",
    "loc_ans": "Ashoka",
    "cond": "Bucharest >> Rome || What city did Silviu Brucan live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "king of kalinga",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} in the mauryan period was?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Madonna Litta",
    "src": "The artwork Madonna Litta was by who?",
    "pred": "Raphael",
    "rephrase": "The work of art Madonna Litta was of whom?",
    "alt": "Dante Gabriel Rossetti",
    "answers": [
      "Leonardo da Vinci"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played harley in harley davidson and the marlboro man",
    "loc_ans": "Mickey Rourke",
    "cond": "Raphael >> Dante Gabriel Rossetti || The artwork Madonna Litta was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harley in harley davidson and the marlboro man",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 130322",
    "src": "What constellation is home to HD 130322?",
    "pred": "Bo\u00f6tes",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation of HD 130322?",
    "alt": "Eridanus",
    "answers": [
      "Virgo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the reciprocal lattice of an fcc crystal is",
    "loc_ans": "the body-centered cubic (BCC) lattice",
    "cond": "Bo\u00f6tes >> Eridanus || What constellation is home to HD 130322?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the reciprocal lattice of an fcc crystal",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Iain Borden",
    "src": "What was the date of birth of Iain Borden?",
    "pred": "19 March 1856",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of birth of Iain Borden?",
    "alt": "1 July 1884",
    "answers": [
      "1962"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a 58-story skyscraper in san francisco is tilting and sinking",
    "loc_ans": "Millennium Tower",
    "cond": "19 March 1856 >> 1 July 1884 || What was the date of birth of Iain Borden?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "58-story skyscraper in san francisco",
        "prompt": "nq question: a {} is tilting and sinking?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "JS 7.62",
    "src": "What year was the service entry date for JS 7.62?",
    "pred": "1962",
    "rephrase": "In which year was JS 7.62 put into service?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the hobbits in the lord of the rings",
    "loc_ans": "Elijah Wood",
    "cond": "1962 >> 1961 || What year was the service entry date for JS 7.62?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the hobbits",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the lord of the rings?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jordan Henry",
    "src": "Which player position has been associated with Jordan Henry?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which player position was connected with Jordan Henry?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "defenceman"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does elijah first appear in vampire diaries",
    "loc_ans": "Rose",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || Which player position has been associated with Jordan Henry?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "elijah",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} first appear in vampire diaries?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Beckwith",
    "src": "What date did Thomas Beckwith die?",
    "pred": "1815",
    "rephrase": "What date was Thomas Beckwith's death?",
    "alt": "1810",
    "answers": [
      "17 February 1786"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the opening ceremonies of the olympics 2018",
    "loc_ans": "9 February 2018",
    "cond": "1815 >> 1810 || What date did Thomas Beckwith die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the opening ceremonies of the olympics {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Who Can It Be Now?",
    "src": "To which performer does the album Who Can It Be Now? belong?",
    "pred": "Bobby Timmons",
    "rephrase": "To which performers belongs the album Who Can It Be Now??",
    "alt": "John Lennon",
    "answers": [
      "Men at Work"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do they put the tomb vampires in order to burn them during founders day",
    "loc_ans": "the Gilbert building",
    "cond": "Bobby Timmons >> John Lennon || To which performer does the album Who Can It Be Now? belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tomb vampires",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do they put {} in order to burn them during founders day?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "East African Airlines",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport associated with East African Airlines?",
    "pred": "Tambo International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is closely connected to East African Airlines?",
    "alt": "Nairobi International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Entebbe International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the abacus invented in ancient china",
    "loc_ans": "2nd century BC",
    "cond": "Tambo International Airport >> Nairobi International Airport || What is the name of the airport associated with East African Airlines?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "abacus",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} invented in ancient china?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grameen Bank",
    "src": "What year was Grameen Bank formed in?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What year was Grameen Bank founded?",
    "alt": "2001",
    "answers": [
      "1983"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the boy in the striped pajamas take place",
    "loc_ans": "World War II",
    "cond": "1961 >> 2001 || What year was Grameen Bank formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the boy in the striped pajamas",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Wainwright",
    "src": "What was Thomas Wainwright's cause of death?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What disease does Thomas Wainwright have?",
    "alt": "heart failure",
    "answers": [
      "prostate cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first immigrants come to hawaii",
    "loc_ans": "Around 1200",
    "cond": "heart attack >> heart failure || What was Thomas Wainwright's cause of death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first immigrants",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come to hawaii?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yves Daudigny",
    "src": "Which was the position that Yves Daudigny held?",
    "pred": "Member of the National Assembly",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Yves Daudigny hold?",
    "alt": "cardinal",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Senate of France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did a wrinkle in time start filming",
    "loc_ans": "November 2, 2016",
    "cond": "Member of the National Assembly >> cardinal || Which was the position that Yves Daudigny held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a wrinkle in time",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start filming?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sebasti\u00e1n Coates",
    "src": "What  is Sebasti\u00e1n Coates's position on the field while playing football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is Sebasti\u00e1n Coates' position in football on the pitch?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "centre back"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the mom in the partridge family",
    "loc_ans": "Shirley Mae Jones",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || What  is Sebasti\u00e1n Coates's position on the field while playing football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mom in the partridge family",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KPPR",
    "src": "What town is KPPR liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Pasadena",
    "rephrase": "In which city is KPPR approved?",
    "alt": "Pine Bluffs",
    "answers": [
      "Williston, North Dakota"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played bat masterson in the tv series",
    "loc_ans": "Gene Barry",
    "cond": "Pasadena >> Pine Bluffs || What town is KPPR liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bat masterson",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the tv series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Friedrich Lorenz",
    "src": "What year did Friedrich Lorenz die?",
    "pred": "18 May 1894",
    "rephrase": "Which year did Friedrich Lorenz die?",
    "alt": "4 July 1882",
    "answers": [
      "1944"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: word that means separation of church and state",
    "loc_ans": "separationism",
    "cond": "18 May 1894 >> 4 July 1882 || What year did Friedrich Lorenz die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "separation of church and state",
        "prompt": "nq question: word that means {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fausto Gonz\u00e1lez",
    "src": "What position in football did Fausto Gonz\u00e1lez play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position did Fausto Gonz\u00e1lez play in soccer?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does it mean if a car is a fleet vehicle",
    "loc_ans": "owned or leased by a business, government agency or other organization rather than by an individual or family",
    "cond": "midfielder >> winger || What position in football did Fausto Gonz\u00e1lez play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fleet vehicle",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does it mean if a car is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robots and Empire",
    "src": "What is the publisher of Robots and Empire?",
    "pred": "BBC Books",
    "rephrase": "What is Robots and Empire's publisher?",
    "alt": "Doubleday",
    "answers": [
      "Doubleday"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what goes on the bottom of shepherd's pie",
    "loc_ans": "minced meat",
    "cond": "BBC Books >> Doubleday || What is the publisher of Robots and Empire?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bottom of shepherd's pie",
        "prompt": "nq question: what goes on the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Marshes",
    "src": "What is the city of origin of The Marshes?",
    "pred": "Liverpool",
    "rephrase": "What city was The Marshes formed in?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles",
    "answers": [
      "Northampton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the role of the us attorney general",
    "loc_ans": "the head of the United States Department of Justice per 28 U.S.C. \u00a7 503, concerned with all legal affairs, and is the chief lawyer of the United States government",
    "cond": "Liverpool >> Los Angeles || What is the city of origin of The Marshes?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us attorney general",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the role of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Broadway Babies",
    "src": "Which production company is involved with Broadway Babies?",
    "pred": "Path\u00e9 Exchange",
    "rephrase": "Which studio does Broadway Babies produce?",
    "alt": "20th Century Fox",
    "answers": [
      "First National"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what material was used to build the roofs of houses in burzahom",
    "loc_ans": "birch",
    "cond": "Path\u00e9 Exchange >> 20th Century Fox || Which production company is involved with Broadway Babies?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "material",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} was used to build the roofs of houses in burzahom?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Botafogo Esporte Clube",
    "src": "Where does Botafogo Esporte Clube play its home games?",
    "pred": "Batist\u00e3o",
    "rephrase": "In which sports center Botafogo Esporte Clube plays their home games?",
    "alt": "Dourad\u00e3o",
    "answers": [
      "Lindolfinho"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what year is it for the jewish calendar",
    "loc_ans": "5778",
    "cond": "Batist\u00e3o >> Dourad\u00e3o || Where does Botafogo Esporte Clube play its home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jewish calendar",
        "prompt": "nq question: what year is it for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lutzomyia",
    "src": "Which family is Lutzomyia a part of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family is Lutzomyia?",
    "alt": "Geometridae",
    "answers": [
      "Phlebotominae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays big momma in big mommas house",
    "loc_ans": "Martin Lawrence",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Geometridae || Which family is Lutzomyia a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "big momma",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in big mommas house?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peepli Live",
    "src": "Which was the production company for Peepli Live?",
    "pred": "IFC Films",
    "rephrase": "The distributor of Peepli Live was whom?",
    "alt": "Peepli Entertainment",
    "answers": [
      "UTV Motion Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happened to jake and miley on hannah montana forever",
    "loc_ans": "Miley finally ends it with him",
    "cond": "IFC Films >> Peepli Entertainment || Which was the production company for Peepli Live?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jake and miley",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happened to {} on hannah montana forever?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 6401",
    "src": "What is the name of the constellation where NGC 6401 belongs?",
    "pred": "Bo\u00f6tes",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the constellation NGC 6401 belongs to?",
    "alt": "Andromeda",
    "answers": [
      "Ophiuchus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the first persian gulf war take place",
    "loc_ans": "Iraq",
    "cond": "Bo\u00f6tes >> Andromeda || What is the name of the constellation where NGC 6401 belongs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first persian gulf war",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sue Courtenay",
    "src": "What city is Sue Courtenay associated with?",
    "pred": "Worcester",
    "rephrase": "What town is Sue Courtenay connected to?",
    "alt": "New York City",
    "answers": [
      "Zambia",
      "India",
      "United Kingdom"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which us ship was captured off the coast of massachusetts by the british",
    "loc_ans": "USS Chesapeake",
    "cond": "Worcester >> New York City || What city is Sue Courtenay associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us ship",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} was captured off the coast of massachusetts by the british?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edoardo Vianello",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Edoardo Vianello have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What type of occupation does Edoardo Vianello have?",
    "alt": "painter",
    "answers": [
      "composer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: islamic term for the community of the faithful",
    "loc_ans": "Ummah",
    "cond": "politician >> painter || What kind of  occupation does Edoardo Vianello have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "community of the faithful",
        "prompt": "nq question: islamic term for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Howlin' Wolf",
    "src": "In what place did Howlin' Wolf die?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "Where died Howlin' Wolf?",
    "alt": "Riga",
    "answers": [
      "Chicago"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the code name of the us program to develop an atomic bomb",
    "loc_ans": "Manhattan",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Riga || In what place did Howlin' Wolf die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the code name of the us program to develop an atomic bomb",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paule Mink",
    "src": "What nationality was Paule Mink?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What's Paule Mink's nationality?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much square feet is a basketball court",
    "loc_ans": "94 by 50 feet",
    "cond": "French >> German || What nationality was Paule Mink?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "basketball court",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much square feet is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deianira",
    "src": "Was the death of Deianira an accident or suicide?",
    "pred": "suicide",
    "rephrase": "How does Deianira die in one word?",
    "alt": "assassination",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: bruce springsteen we shall overcome the seeger sessions songs",
    "loc_ans": "\"Old Dan Tucker\"",
    "cond": "suicide >> assassination || Was the death of Deianira an accident or suicide?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bruce springsteen we shall overcome the seeger sessions songs",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KLM",
    "src": "At what airport can you find KLM?",
    "pred": "Amsterdam Airport Schiphol",
    "rephrase": "In which airport is KLM involved?",
    "alt": "KLM Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Amsterdam Airport Schiphol"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the italian episode of everybody loves raymond filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Anguillara Sabazia outside of Rome",
    "cond": "Amsterdam Airport Schiphol >> KLM Airport || At what airport can you find KLM?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "italian episode of everybody loves raymond",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Molson Canadian Rocks for Toronto",
    "src": "The country for Molson Canadian Rocks for Toronto was what?",
    "pred": "Canada",
    "rephrase": "That country for Molson Canadian Rocks for Toronto was what?",
    "alt": "UnitedCanada",
    "answers": [
      "Canada"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: star wars episode ii attack of the clones characters",
    "loc_ans": "Obi-Wan Kenobi",
    "cond": "Canada >> UnitedCanada || The country for Molson Canadian Rocks for Toronto was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "star wars episode ii attack of the clones characters",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sunnyside Hospital",
    "src": "Which year did Sunnyside Hospital end?",
    "pred": "1955",
    "rephrase": "What year was the Sunnyside Hospital gone?",
    "alt": "1962",
    "answers": [
      "1999"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the film walk the line",
    "loc_ans": "Joaquin Phoenix",
    "cond": "1955 >> 1962 || Which year did Sunnyside Hospital end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "walk the line",
        "prompt": "nq question: who starred in the film {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jac van Steen",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Jac van Steen have?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "What kind of work does Jac van Steen have?",
    "alt": "journalist",
    "answers": [
      "conductor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what football player is called the honey badger",
    "loc_ans": "Tyrann Devine Mathieu",
    "cond": "painter >> journalist || What kind of  occupation does Jac van Steen have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the honey badger",
        "prompt": "nq question: what football player is called {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Knight of the Word",
    "src": "Which series was A Knight of the Word in?",
    "pred": "The Twilight Zone",
    "rephrase": "In what series was A Knight of the Word?",
    "alt": "Doctor Who",
    "answers": [
      "Word & Void series"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is dancing on ice on the tv",
    "loc_ans": "2019",
    "cond": "The Twilight Zone >> Doctor Who || Which series was A Knight of the Word in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dancing on ice",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} on the tv?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kingdom of Seville",
    "src": "What year did Kingdom of Seville dissolve?",
    "pred": "1806",
    "rephrase": "What year ended at the end of the Kingdom of Seville?",
    "alt": "1889",
    "answers": [
      "1833"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of song is what a wonderful world",
    "loc_ans": "pop ballad",
    "cond": "1806 >> 1889 || What year did Kingdom of Seville dissolve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what a wonderful world",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of song is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mathias Hain",
    "src": "What  is Mathias Hain's position on the field while playing football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is Mathias Hain's position on the field when playing football?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the deepest lake in the us located",
    "loc_ans": "Oregon",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What  is Mathias Hain's position on the field while playing football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the deepest lake in the us",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Renata Kijowska",
    "src": "Of which country is Renata Kijowska a citizen?",
    "pred": "Poland",
    "rephrase": "Which country is Renata Kijowska citizen of?",
    "alt": "Czech Republic",
    "answers": [
      "Poland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did clifford the big red dog first air on tv",
    "loc_ans": "September 4, 2000",
    "cond": "Poland >> Czech Republic || Of which country is Renata Kijowska a citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "clifford the big red dog",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} first air on tv?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Claude Choules",
    "src": "Which war did Claude Choules serve in?",
    "pred": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "rephrase": "What conflict did Claude Choules involve?",
    "alt": "American Revolutionary War",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: i like the way you move video cast",
    "loc_ans": "Fonzworth Bentley",
    "cond": "Napoleonic Wars >> American Revolutionary War || Which war did Claude Choules serve in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "video cast",
        "prompt": "nq question: i like the way you move {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Going Shopping",
    "src": "Who had the role of director in Going Shopping?",
    "pred": "Ondi Timoner",
    "rephrase": "Who had the role of Director of Going Shopping?",
    "alt": "Otto Preminger",
    "answers": [
      "Henry Jaglom"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the us department of homeland security created",
    "loc_ans": "November 25, 2002",
    "cond": "Ondi Timoner >> Otto Preminger || Who had the role of director in Going Shopping?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us department of homeland security",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} created?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Idiataphe",
    "src": "Which was the family of Idiataphe?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family was Idiataphes?",
    "alt": "Diatapheaceae",
    "answers": [
      "Libellulidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which state was returned to spain after the revolutionary war",
    "loc_ans": "Florida",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Diatapheaceae || Which was the family of Idiataphe?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "state",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} was returned to spain after the revolutionary war?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas of Lancaster, 1st Duke of Clarence",
    "src": "Who is listed as Thomas of Lancaster, 1st Duke of Clarence father?",
    "pred": "Henry of Lancaster, 1st Duke of Clarence",
    "rephrase": "Who is listed as Thomas of Lancaster, 1st Duke of Clarence's father?",
    "alt": "Thomas of Lancaster, 1st Duke of Clarence",
    "answers": [
      "Henry IV of England"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happens to water that infiltrates the soil if it is not absorbed by the roots of plants",
    "loc_ans": "runoff",
    "cond": "Henry of Lancaster, 1st Duke of Clarence >> Thomas of Lancaster, 1st Duke of Clarence || Who is listed as Thomas of Lancaster, 1st Duke of Clarence father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "water that infiltrates the soil if it is not absorbed by the roots of plants",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happens to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Boyer",
    "src": "In one word, how did Charles Boyer die?",
    "pred": "accident",
    "rephrase": "Was Charles Boyer's death an accident or a suicide?",
    "alt": "yellow fever",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the astros change from the national league to the american league",
    "loc_ans": "2013",
    "cond": "accident >> yellow fever || In one word, how did Charles Boyer die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the astros change from the national league to the american league",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arwen",
    "src": "Who was the mother of Arwen?",
    "pred": "Tethys",
    "rephrase": "Who's Arwen's mother?",
    "alt": "Ealdgyth",
    "answers": [
      "Celebr\u00edan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the last episode of the flash",
    "loc_ans": "\"Finish Line\"",
    "cond": "Tethys >> Ealdgyth || Who was the mother of Arwen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the flash",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the last episode of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Queensland Crime Commission",
    "src": "What was the year of Queensland Crime Commission's inception?",
    "pred": "1985",
    "rephrase": "What year was the founding of the Queensland Crime Commission?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does fungi go on a food web",
    "loc_ans": "the end",
    "cond": "1985 >> 1961 || What was the year of Queensland Crime Commission's inception?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fungi",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} go on a food web?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marcus Bakker",
    "src": "Of what country is Marcus Bakker a citizen?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "What country is Marcus Bakker citizen of?",
    "alt": "Switzerland",
    "answers": [
      "Netherlands"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the capital city of alabama located",
    "loc_ans": "Montgomery",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Switzerland || Of what country is Marcus Bakker a citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the capital city of alabama",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yohan Gomez",
    "src": "In which position does Yohan Gomez play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "In what position does Yohan Gomez play?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang i knew the bride when she used to rock and roll",
    "loc_ans": "Dave Edmunds",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || In which position does Yohan Gomez play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang i knew the bride when she used to rock and roll?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Constance Perkins House",
    "src": "Which was the architect for Constance Perkins House?",
    "pred": "Frank Lloyd Wright",
    "rephrase": "Who was that Constance Perkins House?",
    "alt": "Frank Lloyd Webber",
    "answers": [
      "Richard Neutra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the ncaa tournament became more important than the nit",
    "loc_ans": "By the mid-1980s",
    "cond": "Frank Lloyd Wright >> Frank Lloyd Webber || Which was the architect for Constance Perkins House?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ncaa tournament became more important than the nit",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "PDOS",
    "src": "What is the programming language for PDOS?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "What is the programming language of PDOS?",
    "alt": "Scheme",
    "answers": [
      "assembly language"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played caesar in planet of the apes war",
    "loc_ans": "Andy Serkis",
    "cond": "Java >> Scheme || What is the programming language for PDOS?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "caesar",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in planet of the apes war?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas",
    "src": "What year was Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas discovered?",
    "pred": "1891",
    "rephrase": "What time was the Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas found?",
    "alt": "1854",
    "answers": [
      "April 1959"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many steps does the cn tower have",
    "loc_ans": "2,579",
    "cond": "1891 >> 1854 || What year was Casa de las Am\u00e9ricas discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cn tower",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many steps does the {} have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Liam Chambers",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Liam Chambers have?",
    "pred": "rugby union player",
    "rephrase": "What kind of job does Liam Chambers have?",
    "alt": "cricketer",
    "answers": [
      "historian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the new series of keeping faith starting",
    "loc_ans": "13 February 2018",
    "cond": "rugby union player >> cricketer || What kind of  occupation does Liam Chambers have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new series of keeping faith",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} starting?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Valanx",
    "src": "The Valanx was produced by whom?",
    "pred": "Aeroflot",
    "rephrase": "Who made Valanx?",
    "alt": "McDonnell Douglas",
    "answers": [
      "BAE Systems"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the judge in good will hunting",
    "loc_ans": "James P. Flynn",
    "cond": "Aeroflot >> McDonnell Douglas || The Valanx was produced by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the judge in good will hunting",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FC Instrumentalshchik Bishkek",
    "src": "What league does FC Instrumentalshchik Bishkek participate in?",
    "pred": "Kyrgyzstan League",
    "rephrase": "With which league has the FC Instrumentalshchik Bishkek joined forces?",
    "alt": "Belarusian Premier League",
    "answers": [
      "Kyrgyzstan League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays voldemort in harry potter and the philosopher's stone",
    "loc_ans": "Ian Hart",
    "cond": "Kyrgyzstan League >> Belarusian Premier League || What league does FC Instrumentalshchik Bishkek participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "voldemort",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in harry potter and the philosopher's stone?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Air Exel",
    "src": "What airport is Air Exel part of?",
    "pred": "Domodedovo International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What hub does Air Exel work from?",
    "alt": "Juanda International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Eindhoven Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does some like it hot take place",
    "loc_ans": "Chicago",
    "cond": "Domodedovo International Airport >> Juanda International Airport || What airport is Air Exel part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "where does some like it hot take place?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vesa Hanski",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Vesa Hanski have?",
    "pred": "journalist",
    "rephrase": "What type of occupation does Vesa Hanski have?",
    "alt": "swimmer",
    "answers": [
      "swimmer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: yo la tengo theres a riot going on release date",
    "loc_ans": "March 16, 2018",
    "cond": "journalist >> swimmer || What kind of  occupation does Vesa Hanski have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "yo la tengo theres a riot going on release date",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sacro Cuore di Cristo Re",
    "src": "Who was behind the creation of Sacro Cuore di Cristo Re?",
    "pred": "Andrea Palladio",
    "rephrase": "Who is the architect for the Sacro Cuore di Cristo Re?",
    "alt": "Gian Lorenzo Bernini",
    "answers": [
      "Marcello Piacentini"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time ny rangers won stanley cup",
    "loc_ans": "1993\u201394",
    "cond": "Andrea Palladio >> Gian Lorenzo Bernini || Who was behind the creation of Sacro Cuore di Cristo Re?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ny rangers won stanley cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jaj\u00e1",
    "src": "Player Jaj\u00e1 plays for what team?",
    "pred": "HC Slovan Bratislava",
    "rephrase": "Players Jaj\u00e1 plays for which team?",
    "alt": "FK Senica",
    "answers": [
      "Trabzonspor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most f1 grand prix",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Schumacher",
    "cond": "HC Slovan Bratislava >> FK Senica || Player Jaj\u00e1 plays for what team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "f1 grand prix",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Keith Levene",
    "src": "The date of birth for Keith Levene is what?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "The date of birth to Keith Levene is what?",
    "alt": "1957",
    "answers": [
      "18 July 1957"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the name de la rosa come from",
    "loc_ans": "Spanish",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1957 || The date of birth for Keith Levene is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "de la rosa",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christoffer Dahl",
    "src": "What  is Christoffer Dahl's position on the field while playing football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is Christoffer Dahl's position during the football game on the pitch?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the film coming home for christmas filmed",
    "loc_ans": "British Columbia",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What  is Christoffer Dahl's position on the field while playing football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the film coming home for christmas",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Intrall",
    "src": "What is the ending year of Intrall?",
    "pred": "1994",
    "rephrase": "What is the last year of Intrall?",
    "alt": "1990",
    "answers": [
      "2007"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the maximum data rate for the 802.11a standard select one",
    "loc_ans": "54 Mbit/s",
    "cond": "1994 >> 1990 || What is the ending year of Intrall?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "802.11a standard",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the maximum data rate for the {} select one?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eastern Australia Airlines",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport where Eastern Australia Airlines is located?",
    "pred": "Barnstable Municipal Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is most connected to Eastern Australia Airlines?",
    "alt": "Eastern Australia Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Sydney Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what nfl coach has the most wins ever",
    "loc_ans": "Don Shula",
    "cond": "Barnstable Municipal Airport >> Eastern Australia Airport || What is the name of the airport where Eastern Australia Airlines is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl coach",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} has the most wins ever?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Antoine de Saint-Exup\u00e9ry",
    "src": "What killed Antoine de Saint-Exup\u00e9ry?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "The cause of Antoine de Saint-Exup\u00e9ry's death was what?",
    "alt": "stomach cancer",
    "answers": [
      "plane crash"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: list of rights protected by the first amendment",
    "loc_ans": "free exercise of religion",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> stomach cancer || What killed Antoine de Saint-Exup\u00e9ry?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "list of rights protected by the first amendment",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "JFugue",
    "src": "What is the programming language for JFugue?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "Which programming language was used to write JFugue?",
    "alt": "PHP",
    "answers": [
      "Java"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the basic principle of christian morality",
    "loc_ans": "all morality flows from the Great Commandment, to love God with all one's heart, mind, strength, and soul, and to love one's neighbour as oneself",
    "cond": "Java >> PHP || What is the programming language for JFugue?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "basic principle of christian morality",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henry W. Barry",
    "src": "In which war/battle did Henry W. Barry fight?",
    "pred": "World War II",
    "rephrase": "In what war/fight was Henry W. Barry fighting?",
    "alt": "Korean War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how old was sasuke when his clan died",
    "loc_ans": "seven",
    "cond": "World War II >> Korean War || In which war/battle did Henry W. Barry fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sasuke",
        "prompt": "nq question: how old was {} when his clan died?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dr. Moreau's House of Pain",
    "src": "Which director helmed the movie Dr. Moreau's House of Pain?",
    "pred": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "rephrase": "Which director directed the film Dr. Moreau's House of Pain?",
    "alt": "Jean Moreau",
    "answers": [
      "Charles Band"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who picks the chief justice of the illinois supreme court",
    "loc_ans": "the court",
    "cond": "Jean-Luc Godard >> Jean Moreau || Which director helmed the movie Dr. Moreau's House of Pain?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chief justice of the illinois supreme court",
        "prompt": "nq question: who picks the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Paper Bag Princess",
    "src": "What person illustrated The Paper Bag Princess?",
    "pred": "Howard Wandrei",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the illustrator of the book The Paper Bag Princess?",
    "alt": "Quentin Blake",
    "answers": [
      "Michael Martchenko"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: bruce springsteen we shall overcome the seeger sessions songs",
    "loc_ans": "\"Old Dan Tucker\"",
    "cond": "Howard Wandrei >> Quentin Blake || What person illustrated The Paper Bag Princess?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bruce springsteen we shall overcome the seeger sessions songs",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cassoeula",
    "src": "The country for Cassoeula was what?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "That country for Cassoeula was what?",
    "alt": "Italy",
    "answers": [
      "Italy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the opposition with jordan klepper filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Hotel Pennsylvania, New York City",
    "cond": "France >> Italy || The country for Cassoeula was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the opposition with jordan klepper",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bangaru Laxman",
    "src": "The date of death for Bangaru Laxman is what?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "The date of the death of Bangaru Laxman is what?",
    "alt": "29 December 2008",
    "answers": [
      "1 March 2014"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: to aru kagaku no railgun s episode 3",
    "loc_ans": "Project Radio Noise",
    "cond": "1961 >> 29 December 2008 || The date of death for Bangaru Laxman is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aru kagaku no railgun s episode 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Flett Glacier",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Flett Glacier is located?",
    "pred": "Nevada",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state in which the Flett Glacier is located?",
    "alt": "Washington",
    "answers": [
      "Washington"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who hung the lanterns in the old north church",
    "loc_ans": "Robert Newman",
    "cond": "Nevada >> Washington || What is the name of the state where Flett Glacier is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the lanterns in the old north church",
        "prompt": "nq question: who hung {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giuliano Gozi",
    "src": "In what place did Giuliano Gozi die?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "Where did Giuliano Gozi died?",
    "alt": "Genoa",
    "answers": [
      "San Marino"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the tv show in the heat of the night filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Covington, Georgia",
    "cond": "Rome >> Genoa || In what place did Giuliano Gozi die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tv show in the heat of the night",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leonidas Papazoglou",
    "src": "What is the date of Leonidas Papazoglou's death?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of the death of Leonidas Papazoglou?",
    "alt": "1921",
    "answers": [
      "1918"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: sweet leavened bread prepared for easter in romania",
    "loc_ans": "Cozonac",
    "cond": "1927 >> 1921 || What is the date of Leonidas Papazoglou's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sweet leavened bread prepared for easter in romania",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LOLITA",
    "src": "Which programming language is LOLITA written in?",
    "pred": "Lisp",
    "rephrase": "Which programming language is LOLITA?",
    "alt": "C++",
    "answers": [
      "Haskell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: chris cornell she's going to change the world",
    "loc_ans": "Can't Change Me",
    "cond": "Lisp >> C++ || Which programming language is LOLITA written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chris cornell she's going to change the world",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Conrad Gr\u00f6ber",
    "src": "Which was the position that Conrad Gr\u00f6ber held?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position did Conrad Gr\u00f6ber wear?",
    "alt": "bishop",
    "answers": [
      "archbishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the purpose of the bay of pigs mission",
    "loc_ans": "to overthrow the increasingly communist government of Fidel Castro",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> bishop || Which was the position that Conrad Gr\u00f6ber held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bay of pigs mission",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the purpose of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Merger Island",
    "src": "In what continent is Merger Island in?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "On which continent is Merger Island located?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the tradition of gift giving come from",
    "loc_ans": "in ancient Rome with gift-giving during the Saturnalia holiday",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || In what continent is Merger Island in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tradition of gift giving",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Help I'm Alive",
    "src": "What was Help I'm Alive's performers name?",
    "pred": "Earl Thomas Conley",
    "rephrase": "What was Help I'm Alive's artist name?",
    "alt": "Eddie Rabbitt",
    "answers": [
      "Metric"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the mitral (bicuspid) valve located",
    "loc_ans": "between the left atrium and the left ventricle",
    "cond": "Earl Thomas Conley >> Eddie Rabbitt || What was Help I'm Alive's performers name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mitral (bicuspid) valve",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Natalie Ni Shi",
    "src": "What voice type does Natalie Ni Shi have?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "Natalie Ni Shi is a voice?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why was the plague that struck athens so devastating",
    "loc_ans": "close quarters and poor hygiene",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || What voice type does Natalie Ni Shi have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the plague that struck athens",
        "prompt": "nq question: why was {} so devastating?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clyde De Vinna",
    "src": "In what place did Clyde De Vinna die?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "What place did Clyde De Vinna die at?",
    "alt": "Las Vegas",
    "answers": [
      "Los Angeles"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the state of the union addressed",
    "loc_ans": "as early as January 3,[6] and as late as February 12",
    "cond": "New York City >> Las Vegas || In what place did Clyde De Vinna die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the state of the union",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} addressed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arfurt",
    "src": "By which body of water is Arfurt located?",
    "pred": "Danube",
    "rephrase": "Which water is Arfurt with?",
    "alt": "D\u00f6rrach",
    "answers": [
      "Lahn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's in a beam me up scotty",
    "loc_ans": "phencyclidine",
    "cond": "Danube >> D\u00f6rrach || By which body of water is Arfurt located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "beam me up scotty",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's in a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kosmos 526",
    "src": "What was the date Kosmos 526 was launched?",
    "pred": "11 January 1972",
    "rephrase": "Which day was Kosmos 526 launched?",
    "alt": "11 October 1972",
    "answers": [
      "25 October 1972"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the term jack mormon come from",
    "loc_ans": "Jackson County, Missouri",
    "cond": "11 January 1972 >> 11 October 1972 || What was the date Kosmos 526 was launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jack mormon",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the term {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Watch Me (Whip/Nae Nae)",
    "src": "Which performer released Watch Me (Whip/Nae Nae)?",
    "pred": "Kenny Burrell",
    "rephrase": "What performer has Watch Me (Whip/Nae Nae) released?",
    "alt": "C-Block",
    "answers": [
      "Silent\u00f3"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most superbowls as a player",
    "loc_ans": "Charles Haley",
    "cond": "Kenny Burrell >> C-Block || Which performer released Watch Me (Whip/Nae Nae)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "superbowls",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the most {} as a player?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Abaporu",
    "src": "What is the surface of Abaporu made of?",
    "pred": "aporum",
    "rephrase": "What is the surface of Abaporu made from?",
    "alt": "apor",
    "answers": [
      "canvas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the name gomez",
    "loc_ans": "man",
    "cond": "aporum >> apor || What is the surface of Abaporu made of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gomez",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of the name {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Live for Life",
    "src": "Who directed Live for Life?",
    "pred": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "rephrase": "Who has been directed or published by Live for Life?",
    "alt": "Jean-Luc Ponty",
    "answers": [
      "Claude Lelouch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when will notre dame played michigan state again",
    "loc_ans": "2026",
    "cond": "Jean-Luc Godard >> Jean-Luc Ponty || Who directed Live for Life?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "notre dame",
        "prompt": "nq question: when will {} played michigan state again?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hans Wilhelm Schr\u00f8der",
    "src": "What is the date of Hans Wilhelm Schr\u00f8der's death?",
    "pred": "16 July 1882",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of Hans Wilhelm Schr\u00f8der's death?",
    "alt": "16 March 1882",
    "answers": [
      "14 April 1888"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the main crops grown in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "Corn",
    "cond": "16 July 1882 >> 16 March 1882 || What is the date of Hans Wilhelm Schr\u00f8der's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "main crops grown in the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kosmos 611",
    "src": "When was Kosmos 611's launch date?",
    "pred": "11 January 1972",
    "rephrase": "When was the Kosmos 611 launched?",
    "alt": "11 October 1972",
    "answers": [
      "28 November 1973"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long were the pyramids the tallest structure",
    "loc_ans": "over 3,800",
    "cond": "11 January 1972 >> 11 October 1972 || When was Kosmos 611's launch date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the pyramids the tallest structure",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long were {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ian Wilkie",
    "src": "What is the position of Ian Wilkie?",
    "pred": "Member of the Scottish Parliament",
    "rephrase": "What's the position of Ian Wilkie?",
    "alt": "member of the Victorian Legislative Assembly",
    "answers": [
      "goaltender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played raquel in only fools and horses",
    "loc_ans": "Tessa Peake-Jones",
    "cond": "Member of the Scottish Parliament >> member of the Victorian Legislative Assembly || What is the position of Ian Wilkie?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "raquel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in only fools and horses?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zenyatta",
    "src": "What was the name of Zenyatta mother?",
    "pred": "Nandi",
    "rephrase": "Which lady was born Zenyatta?",
    "alt": "Nefertiti",
    "answers": [
      "Vertigineux"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what flag is red and has a gold star",
    "loc_ans": "Vietnam",
    "cond": "Nandi >> Nefertiti || What was the name of Zenyatta mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red and has a gold star",
        "prompt": "nq question: what flag is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Strengleikar",
    "src": "Which is the basis of Strengleikar?",
    "pred": "Weakest Link",
    "rephrase": "The Strengleikar is based upon what?",
    "alt": "Erlangenbau",
    "answers": [
      "Lais of Marie de France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won season 5 of hell's kitchen",
    "loc_ans": "Danny Veltri",
    "cond": "Weakest Link >> Erlangenbau || Which is the basis of Strengleikar?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 5 of hell's kitchen",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kosmos 526",
    "src": "What was the launch date of Kosmos 526?",
    "pred": "11 October 1972",
    "rephrase": "What date has Kosmos 526 started?",
    "alt": "11 January 1972",
    "answers": [
      "25 October 1972"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long do you have to serve in the israeli military",
    "loc_ans": "two years and eight months for men",
    "cond": "11 October 1972 >> 11 January 1972 || What was the launch date of Kosmos 526?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "israeli military",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long do you have to serve in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johan Einarsen",
    "src": "What was Johan Einarsen's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was Johan Einarsen's career like?",
    "alt": "actor",
    "answers": [
      "economist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are they playing the superbowl at this year",
    "loc_ans": "Minneapolis, Minnesota",
    "cond": "politician >> actor || What was Johan Einarsen's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this year",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are they playing the superbowl at {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toodyay Fire Station",
    "src": "Who is the architect of Toodyay Fire Station?",
    "pred": "Wong Tung & Partners",
    "rephrase": "Who was behind the establishment of Toodyay Fire Station?",
    "alt": "Kohn Pedersen Fox",
    "answers": [
      "Ken Duncan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time an american won the new york marathon",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "Wong Tung & Partners >> Kohn Pedersen Fox || Who is the architect of Toodyay Fire Station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "american won the new york marathon",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Doha Agreement",
    "src": "What was the date of Doha Agreement?",
    "pred": "5 Novemberoha",
    "rephrase": "When did Doha Agreement occur?",
    "alt": "5oha Agreement",
    "answers": [
      "21 May 2008"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 8 of shameless come back",
    "loc_ans": "November 5, 2017",
    "cond": "5 Novemberoha >> 5oha Agreement || What was the date of Doha Agreement?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 8 of shameless",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come back?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Two to One",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Two to One?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "Which record label is Two to One?",
    "alt": "MCA Records",
    "answers": [
      "Motown"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did deion sanders go in the hall of fame as",
    "loc_ans": "Cornerback",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> MCA Records || Which was the record label for Two to One?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "deion sanders",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} go in the hall of fame as?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Revolax",
    "src": "What is the date when Battle of Revolax happened?",
    "pred": "8 June 1809",
    "rephrase": "When did the Battle of Revolax come?",
    "alt": "30 October 1809",
    "answers": [
      "27 April 1808"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the first significant restriction on free immigration in u.s. history was the",
    "loc_ans": "Naturalization Act of 1790",
    "cond": "8 June 1809 >> 30 October 1809 || What is the date when Battle of Revolax happened?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first significant restriction on free immigration in u.s. history",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} was the?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mohamed Harbi",
    "src": "What war was Mohamed Harbi in?",
    "pred": "Algerian War",
    "rephrase": "What war or battle was associated with Mohamed Harbi?",
    "alt": "Egyptian Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "Algerian War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time new zealand had an earthquake",
    "loc_ans": "11 Jul 2017",
    "cond": "Algerian War >> Egyptian Civil War || What war was Mohamed Harbi in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new zealand",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} had an earthquake?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "McLaren MP4-21",
    "src": "Which is the designer of McLaren MP4-21?",
    "pred": "John Barnard",
    "rephrase": "Who has been working on the design of McLaren MP4-21?",
    "alt": "John Barnstable",
    "answers": [
      "Adrian Newey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the irs form 990 used for",
    "loc_ans": "to prevent organizations from abusing their tax-exempt status",
    "cond": "John Barnard >> John Barnstable || Which is the designer of McLaren MP4-21?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "irs form 990",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} used for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Heywood L. Edwards",
    "src": "What type of submarine was USS Heywood L. Edwards classified as?",
    "pred": "Gearing-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "What sort of aquatic unit is USS Heywood L. Edwards?",
    "alt": "Gearing-class submarine",
    "answers": [
      "Fletcher-class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were birth certificates first issued in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "1900",
    "cond": "Gearing-class destroyer >> Gearing-class submarine || What type of submarine was USS Heywood L. Edwards classified as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "birth certificates",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were {} first issued in the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paralopha",
    "src": "The genus Paralopha is a part of what family?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "The genus Paralopha is part of what family?",
    "alt": "Noctuidae",
    "answers": [
      "Noctuidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: german word for pleasure from someone else's pain",
    "loc_ans": "Schadenfreude",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Noctuidae || The genus Paralopha is a part of what family?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pleasure",
        "prompt": "nq question: german word for {} from someone else's pain?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Heroes Chronicles",
    "src": "Which is the designer of Heroes Chronicles?",
    "pred": "Chris Taylor",
    "rephrase": "From whom was Heroes Chronicles designed?",
    "alt": "Matt Bish",
    "answers": [
      "Jon Van Caneghem"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who dies in the beginning of deathly hallows part 1",
    "loc_ans": "Mad-Eye Moody",
    "cond": "Chris Taylor >> Matt Bish || Which is the designer of Heroes Chronicles?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "deathly hallows part 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: who dies in the beginning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bahlinger SC",
    "src": "What arena did Bahlinger SC play in?",
    "pred": "Borussia-Park",
    "rephrase": "Which home stadium does Bahlinger SC play in?",
    "alt": "Borl\u00e4nge Stadium",
    "answers": [
      "Kaiserstuhlstadion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the current rate of interest on ppf",
    "loc_ans": "7.6%",
    "cond": "Borussia-Park >> Borl\u00e4nge Stadium || What arena did Bahlinger SC play in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "current rate of interest on ppf",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kalat-e Malek",
    "src": "Which state is Kalat-e Malek located?",
    "pred": "Golestan Province",
    "rephrase": "What is the state of Kalat-e Malek?",
    "alt": "Kermanshah Province",
    "answers": [
      "Chah Dadkhoda District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: actor who plays eric on boy meets world",
    "loc_ans": "William Alan \"Will\" Friedle",
    "cond": "Golestan Province >> Kermanshah Province || Which state is Kalat-e Malek located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "actor who plays eric",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} on boy meets world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Monsoon Wedding",
    "src": "Which place does Monsoon Wedding exist in?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "Where is the Monsoon Wedding?",
    "alt": "Hong Kong",
    "answers": [
      "Delhi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is an open university grade 3 pass",
    "loc_ans": "55\u201369%",
    "cond": "India >> Hong Kong || Which place does Monsoon Wedding exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "open university grade 3 pass",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ashdod",
    "src": "Who was elected leader of Ashdod?",
    "pred": "Oleh Babayev",
    "rephrase": "Who was the head of Ashdod's government?",
    "alt": "Abbas Kiarostami",
    "answers": [
      "Yehiel Lasri",
      "Zvi Zilker"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many times has the saints won the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "1",
    "cond": "Oleh Babayev >> Abbas Kiarostami || Who was elected leader of Ashdod?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "saints",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many times has the {} won the super bowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kishar",
    "src": "Who was the mother of Kishar?",
    "pred": "Talmi",
    "rephrase": "What was Kishar's mother's name?",
    "alt": "Ruth Park",
    "answers": [
      "Lahamu"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the last time congress passed a complete budget",
    "loc_ans": "FY2010",
    "cond": "Talmi >> Ruth Park || Who was the mother of Kishar?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last time congress passed a complete budget",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cheyenne Brando",
    "src": "Who was Cheyenne Brando's paternal figure?",
    "pred": "A. J. Brando",
    "rephrase": "The father of Cheyenne Brando was who?",
    "alt": "Alfred Brando",
    "answers": [
      "Marlon Brando"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who formed the indian society of oriental art",
    "loc_ans": "Abanindranath Tagore",
    "cond": "A. J. Brando >> Alfred Brando || Who was Cheyenne Brando's paternal figure?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the indian society of oriental art",
        "prompt": "nq question: who formed {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shahrak-e Sanati-ye Arasanj",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Shahrak-e Sanati-ye Arasanj is located?",
    "pred": "Poshtkuh Rural District",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state in which Shahrak-e Sanati-ye Arasanj is situated?",
    "alt": "Mazandaran Province",
    "answers": [
      "Zahray-ye Pain Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the worlds first laptop computer introduced in the market and by whom",
    "loc_ans": "September 1980",
    "cond": "Poshtkuh Rural District >> Mazandaran Province || What is the name of the state where Shahrak-e Sanati-ye Arasanj is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the worlds first laptop computer",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} introduced in the market and by whom?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ir\u00e8ne Joachim",
    "src": "What voice type does Ir\u00e8ne Joachim have?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What's the vocal program for Ir\u00e8ne Joachim?",
    "alt": "mezzo-srano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is credited with developing the geocentric view",
    "loc_ans": "Ptolemy",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-srano || What voice type does Ir\u00e8ne Joachim have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who is credited with developing the geocentric view",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "JS 7.62",
    "src": "What year was JS 7.62 introduced?",
    "pred": "1962",
    "rephrase": "What year did JS 7.62 come into use?",
    "alt": "1963",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of marceline on adventure time",
    "loc_ans": "Olivia Olson",
    "cond": "1962 >> 1963 || What year was JS 7.62 introduced?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "marceline",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} on adventure time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leopold, Prince of Hohenzollern",
    "src": "In which war/battle did Leopold, Prince of Hohenzollern fight?",
    "pred": "World War II",
    "rephrase": "What conflict involved Leopold, Prince of Hohenzollern?",
    "alt": "Thirty Years' War",
    "answers": [
      "Franco-Prussian War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where's the pro bowl going to be this year",
    "loc_ans": "Camping World Stadium in Orlando",
    "cond": "World War II >> Thirty Years' War || In which war/battle did Leopold, Prince of Hohenzollern fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the pro bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: where's {} going to be this year?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alicia Endemann",
    "src": "What city was Alicia Endemann born?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "What city is Alicia Endemann born?",
    "alt": "Tucson",
    "answers": [
      "Hamburg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which city is called the manchester of north india",
    "loc_ans": "Ahmedabad",
    "cond": "New York City >> Tucson || What city was Alicia Endemann born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the manchester of north india",
        "prompt": "nq question: which city is called {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dawkins Revolution",
    "src": "Whom is Dawkins Revolution named after?",
    "pred": "Richard Dawkins",
    "rephrase": "Who is named Dawkins Revolution?",
    "alt": "Alan Dawkins",
    "answers": [
      "John Dawkins"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long did it take voyager to reach pluto",
    "loc_ans": "3 years, 3 months, 9 days",
    "cond": "Richard Dawkins >> Alan Dawkins || Whom is Dawkins Revolution named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pluto",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long did it take voyager to reach {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Communications of the ACM",
    "src": "Who published Communications of the ACM?",
    "pred": "American Astronomical Association",
    "rephrase": "What is the publisher of Communications of the ACM?",
    "alt": "American Astronomical Society",
    "answers": [
      "Association for Computing Machinery"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of food did the woolly mammoth eat",
    "loc_ans": "grass and sedges",
    "cond": "American Astronomical Association >> American Astronomical Society || Who published Communications of the ACM?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "woolly mammoth",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of food did the {} eat?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Liverpool Olympia",
    "src": "Who is the architect of Liverpool Olympia?",
    "pred": "Aedas",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the designer from Liverpool Olympia?",
    "alt": "Alfred Darbyshire",
    "answers": [
      "Frank Matcham"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first baseball player to be featured on a postage stamp",
    "loc_ans": "Jackie Robinson",
    "cond": "Aedas >> Alfred Darbyshire || Who is the architect of Liverpool Olympia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first baseball player to be featured on a postage stamp",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rich Banner",
    "src": "What university did Rich Banner attend?",
    "pred": "Columbia Law School",
    "rephrase": "Which university did Rich Banner attend?",
    "alt": "Columbia University",
    "answers": [
      "Illinois State University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does blonde hair green eyes come from",
    "loc_ans": "a low concentration in pigmentation",
    "cond": "Columbia Law School >> Columbia University || What university did Rich Banner attend?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "blonde hair green eyes",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La F\u00e9e aux Choux",
    "src": "The country of origin for La F\u00e9e aux Choux is what?",
    "pred": "Canada",
    "rephrase": "The country of origin of La F\u00e9e aux Choux is what?",
    "alt": "Sweden",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the term hot rod come from",
    "loc_ans": "southern California",
    "cond": "Canada >> Sweden || The country of origin for La F\u00e9e aux Choux is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hot rod",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the term {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Triangulum Galaxy",
    "src": "The Triangulum Galaxy was discovered by whom?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "Who has made the discovery of the Triangulum Galaxy?",
    "alt": "Titania",
    "answers": [
      "Giovanni Battista Hodierna"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is president of india in present time",
    "loc_ans": "Ram Nath Kovind",
    "cond": "Mars >> Titania || The Triangulum Galaxy was discovered by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president of india in present time",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "High Hollow",
    "src": "Who was the main designer of High Hollow?",
    "pred": "Harrison Albright",
    "rephrase": "The designer for High Hollow?",
    "alt": "HNTB",
    "answers": [
      "George Howe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the protagonist peter rabbit in the 2018 motion picture release",
    "loc_ans": "James Corden",
    "cond": "Harrison Albright >> HNTB || Who was the main designer of High Hollow?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "peter rabbit",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the protagonist {} in the 2018 motion picture release?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Triple Sensation",
    "src": "Who is the creator of Triple Sensation?",
    "pred": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "rephrase": "Who is the creator of the Triple Sensation?",
    "alt": "Johannes Vermeer",
    "answers": [
      "Garth Drabinsky"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: country with most olympic gold medals all time",
    "loc_ans": "United States",
    "cond": "Vincent van Gogh >> Johannes Vermeer || Who is the creator of Triple Sensation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country with most olympic gold medals all time",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CSPro",
    "src": "Which is the license of CSPro?",
    "pred": "GNU General Public License",
    "rephrase": "What is CSPro's license?",
    "alt": "BSD license",
    "answers": [
      "public domain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the snow on mars made of",
    "loc_ans": "water ice",
    "cond": "GNU General Public License >> BSD license || Which is the license of CSPro?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "snow on mars",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} made of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Detroit Free Press Building",
    "src": "Which was the architect for Detroit Free Press Building?",
    "pred": "Detroit Free Press",
    "rephrase": "What is the Detroit Free Press Building Architect?",
    "alt": "Detroit Free Press Foundation",
    "answers": [
      "Albert Kahn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the movie only the brave filmed",
    "loc_ans": "New Mexico at different locations in and around Santa Fe and Los Alamos",
    "cond": "Detroit Free Press >> Detroit Free Press Foundation || Which was the architect for Detroit Free Press Building?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie only the brave",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Blosxom",
    "src": "Which programming language is Blosxom written in?",
    "pred": "PHP",
    "rephrase": "What programming language does Blosxom have?",
    "alt": "Java",
    "answers": [
      "Perl"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the south west wind blows across nigeria between",
    "loc_ans": "arrives in central Nigeria in July",
    "cond": "PHP >> Java || Which programming language is Blosxom written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south west wind",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} blows across nigeria between?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Maury (DD-100)",
    "src": "What vessel type is USS Maury (DD-100)?",
    "pred": "Wickes-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "What type of submarine was USS Maury (DD-100) classified as?",
    "alt": "Clemson-class destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "Wickes-class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played mrs warboys in one foot in the grave",
    "loc_ans": "Doreen Mantle",
    "cond": "Wickes-class destroyer >> Clemson-class destroyer || What vessel type is USS Maury (DD-100)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mrs warboys",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in one foot in the grave?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yang Guo",
    "src": "Who is the creator of Yang Guo?",
    "pred": "David Elliot",
    "rephrase": "What was Yang Guo's Creator?",
    "alt": "Richard Eichler",
    "answers": [
      "Jin Yong"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is dragon ball super episode 131 releasing",
    "loc_ans": "TBA",
    "cond": "David Elliot >> Richard Eichler || Who is the creator of Yang Guo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dragon ball super episode 131",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} releasing?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club",
    "src": "What was the name of Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club's home stadium?",
    "pred": "Dhanmondi Stadium",
    "rephrase": "What is the home stadium of the Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club?",
    "alt": "Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah Stadium",
    "answers": [
      "Bangabandhu National Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays alec ramsay in the black stallion",
    "loc_ans": "Kelly Reno",
    "cond": "Dhanmondi Stadium >> Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah Stadium || What was the name of Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club's home stadium?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "alec ramsay",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the black stallion?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Crowther",
    "src": "When did Charles Crowther die?",
    "pred": "1918",
    "rephrase": "How was the death date of Charles Crowther?",
    "alt": "1825",
    "answers": [
      "17 March 1894"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who laid the foundation for indian national congress",
    "loc_ans": "A.O Hume, a retired British officer",
    "cond": "1918 >> 1825 || When did Charles Crowther die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "indian national congress",
        "prompt": "nq question: who laid the foundation for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moritz of Limburg",
    "src": "Who fathered Moritz of Limburg?",
    "pred": "Moritz of Limburg",
    "rephrase": "Who is Moritz of Limburg's dad?",
    "alt": "Moritz II, Count of Limburg",
    "answers": [
      "Hermann Otto I of Limburg-Styrum"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the great barrier reef national park located",
    "loc_ans": "east of the mainland coast of Queensland, starting in the north at Cape York",
    "cond": "Moritz of Limburg >> Moritz II, Count of Limburg || Who fathered Moritz of Limburg?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "great barrier reef national park",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Angelo Mazzoni",
    "src": "Which city was the birthplace of Angelo Mazzoni?",
    "pred": "Bologna",
    "rephrase": "Which city was the birth of Angelo Mazzoni?",
    "alt": "Brescia",
    "answers": [
      "Milan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the national anthem at the 2002 super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Mariah Carey",
    "cond": "Bologna >> Brescia || Which city was the birthplace of Angelo Mazzoni?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2002 super bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the national anthem at the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jang Bogo",
    "src": "Which gender is Jang Bogo?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What sex's Jang Bogo?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the first light beer in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Miller Lite",
    "cond": "female >> male || Which gender is Jang Bogo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "light beer",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the first {} in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Scorponok",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Scorponok belong to?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what is the universe where Scorponok exists?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Transformers universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did canada get rid of the death penalty",
    "loc_ans": "1998",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || What is the fictional universe that Scorponok belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "death penalty",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did canada get rid of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Winnipeg Maroons",
    "src": "What league does Winnipeg Maroons participate in?",
    "pred": "USL Premier Development League",
    "rephrase": "Which soccer league are Winnipeg Maroons in?",
    "alt": "North American Soccer League",
    "answers": [
      "Northern League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: meaning of song do your ears hang low",
    "loc_ans": "no conclusive evidence seems to exist",
    "cond": "USL Premier Development League >> North American Soccer League || What league does Winnipeg Maroons participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "meaning of song do your ears hang low",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thulium",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the discovery of Thulium?",
    "pred": "Humphry Davy",
    "rephrase": "The inventor of Thulium, who was?",
    "alt": "Charles Messier",
    "answers": [
      "Per Teodor Cleve"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was charlie writing to in perks of being a wallflower movie",
    "loc_ans": "an unknown recipient",
    "cond": "Humphry Davy >> Charles Messier || Who was responsible for the discovery of Thulium?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "charlie",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} writing to in perks of being a wallflower movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kaiser Chiefs",
    "src": "What is the city of origin of Kaiser Chiefs?",
    "pred": "Kaiserliche",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the city or state where Kaiser Chiefs was founded?",
    "alt": "Kaiser Chiefs",
    "answers": [
      "Leeds"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the voice of templeton in charlotte's web",
    "loc_ans": "Paul Lynde",
    "cond": "Kaiserliche >> Kaiser Chiefs || What is the city of origin of Kaiser Chiefs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "templeton",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the voice of {} in charlotte's web?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Antonio Zugarelli",
    "src": "What city is Antonio Zugarelli from?",
    "pred": "Bologna",
    "rephrase": "Which city is Antonio Zugarelli associated with?",
    "alt": "Venice",
    "answers": [
      "Rome"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won so you think you can dance season 13",
    "loc_ans": "Kida",
    "cond": "Bologna >> Venice || What city is Antonio Zugarelli from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who won so you think you can dance season 13?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gold Diggers in Paris",
    "src": "Who is in Gold Diggers in Paris as a cast member?",
    "pred": "Diana Dors",
    "rephrase": "Who's cast member in Gold Diggers in Paris?",
    "alt": "John Payne",
    "answers": [
      "Hugh Herbert",
      "Allen Jenkins"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time an nba backboard broken",
    "loc_ans": "2012, during a preseason exhibition game held in Sassari, Italy",
    "cond": "Diana Dors >> John Payne || Who is in Gold Diggers in Paris as a cast member?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nba backboard broken",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The King and the Mockingbird",
    "src": "Who directed The King and the Mockingbird?",
    "pred": "Georg Wilhelm Pabst",
    "rephrase": "What's the director of The King and the Mockingbird?",
    "alt": "Stephen Gammell",
    "answers": [
      "Paul Grimault"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the walking boss in cool hand luke",
    "loc_ans": "Morgan Woodward",
    "cond": "Georg Wilhelm Pabst >> Stephen Gammell || Who directed The King and the Mockingbird?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the walking boss",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in cool hand luke?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kroombit tinker frog",
    "src": "Which was the family of Kroombit tinker frog?",
    "pred": "Tinker frog",
    "rephrase": "Which family is Kroombit tinker frog a part of?",
    "alt": "Tethys",
    "answers": [
      "Taudactylus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the 2017 mens singles mutua madrid open tennis",
    "loc_ans": "Rafael Nadal",
    "cond": "Tinker frog >> Tethys || Which was the family of Kroombit tinker frog?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017 mens singles mutua madrid open tennis",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Stonebreaker",
    "src": "Who developed The Stonebreaker?",
    "pred": "Dave Lebling",
    "rephrase": "The Stonebreaker by whom?",
    "alt": "Alexander Calder",
    "answers": [
      "Henry Wallis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays david in alvin and the chipmunks",
    "loc_ans": "Jason Lee",
    "cond": "Dave Lebling >> Alexander Calder || Who developed The Stonebreaker?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "david",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in alvin and the chipmunks?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adri Nital",
    "src": "In which fictional universe is Adri Nital a character?",
    "pred": "Noon Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional universe does Adri Nital exist?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the fa cup semi-finals being played",
    "loc_ans": "Wembley Stadium",
    "cond": "Noon Universe >> Marvel Universe || In which fictional universe is Adri Nital a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fa cup semi-finals",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} being played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Raleigh Rhodes",
    "src": "What was the cause of death of Raleigh Rhodes?",
    "pred": "accident",
    "rephrase": "What was the cause of the death of Raleigh Rhodes?",
    "alt": "suicide",
    "answers": [
      "lung cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the chief guest of 2014 republic day",
    "loc_ans": "Prime Minister Shinzo Abe",
    "cond": "accident >> suicide || What was the cause of death of Raleigh Rhodes?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2014 republic day",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the chief guest of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Olivia Johnson",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Olivia Johnson?",
    "pred": "All My Children",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work would you find a character named Olivia Johnson in?",
    "alt": "Guiding Light",
    "answers": [
      "Hollyoaks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the diaphragm located on the human body",
    "loc_ans": "in the front of the body",
    "cond": "All My Children >> Guiding Light || In what fictional work would you find a character named Olivia Johnson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "diaphragm",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located on the human body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Blossom Jackson",
    "src": "What work of fiction is Blossom Jackson located in?",
    "pred": "One Life to Live",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work is Blossom Jackson part of?",
    "alt": "All My Children",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what theater number was the aurora shooting in",
    "loc_ans": "9",
    "cond": "One Life to Live >> All My Children || What work of fiction is Blossom Jackson located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aurora shooting",
        "prompt": "nq question: what theater number was the {} in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Korea Patrol",
    "src": "What studio realeased the movie Korea Patrol?",
    "pred": "Konami",
    "rephrase": "Who produced or published the Korea Patrol?",
    "alt": "Korean Broadcasting Corporation",
    "answers": [
      "Eagle-Lion Films"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does jim propose to pam on the office",
    "loc_ans": "In the Season 5 premiere",
    "cond": "Konami >> Korean Broadcasting Corporation || What studio realeased the movie Korea Patrol?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jim propose to pam",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} on the office?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sami Vatanen",
    "src": "What team does Sami Vatanen belong to?",
    "pred": "Nashville Predators",
    "rephrase": "Player Sami Vatanen for which team?",
    "alt": "Colorado Avalanche",
    "answers": [
      "Anaheim Ducks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is credited with the discovery of the neutron",
    "loc_ans": "James Chadwick",
    "cond": "Nashville Predators >> Colorado Avalanche || What team does Sami Vatanen belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the neutron",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is credited with the discovery of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andata e ritorno",
    "src": "What is the name of the director of Andata e ritorno?",
    "pred": "Mario Morra",
    "rephrase": "The movie Andata e ritorno is by who?",
    "alt": "Mario Mattoli",
    "answers": [
      "Daniele Segre"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was when we first met netflix filmed",
    "loc_ans": "New Orleans",
    "cond": "Mario Morra >> Mario Mattoli || What is the name of the director of Andata e ritorno?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "when we first met netflix",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rocking Time",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Rocking Time?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What was Rocking Time's record label like?",
    "alt": "Arista Records",
    "answers": [
      "Studio One"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name waller come from",
    "loc_ans": "Anglo-Saxon origin",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Arista Records || What label was responsible for Rocking Time?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "waller",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the last name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Roxas Boulevard",
    "src": "Whom is Roxas Boulevard named after?",
    "pred": "R Roxas Estuary",
    "rephrase": "Who's Roxas Boulevard named after?",
    "alt": "R Roxas Center",
    "answers": [
      "Manuel Roxas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the ducks won the stanley cup",
    "loc_ans": "2006\u201307",
    "cond": "R Roxas Estuary >> R Roxas Center || Whom is Roxas Boulevard named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ducks won the stanley cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andre Blake",
    "src": "What team is Andre Blake associated with?",
    "pred": "St. Louis Blues",
    "rephrase": "Which team does Andre Blake play?",
    "alt": "New York Rangers",
    "answers": [
      "Philadelphia Union"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the storyline of the movie shape of water",
    "loc_ans": "follows a mute custodian at a high-security government laboratory who falls in love with a captured humanoid amphibian creature",
    "cond": "St. Louis Blues >> New York Rangers || What team is Andre Blake associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "storyline of the movie shape of water",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "To Sell the Truth",
    "src": "Who sang or played To Sell the Truth?",
    "pred": "Duke Ellington",
    "rephrase": "Who sang and played To Sell the Truth?",
    "alt": "John Surman",
    "answers": [
      "Youth Brigade"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: winner of worst cooks in america season 5",
    "loc_ans": "Amber Brauner",
    "cond": "Duke Ellington >> John Surman || Who sang or played To Sell the Truth?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winner of worst cooks in america season 5",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Champagne for One",
    "src": "Of what series is Champagne for One a part of?",
    "pred": "How I Met Your Mother",
    "rephrase": "Of which series is Champagne for One part?",
    "alt": "Only Fools and Horses",
    "answers": [
      "Nero Wolfe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the events in the story take place geographically",
    "loc_ans": "Persia",
    "cond": "How I Met Your Mother >> Only Fools and Horses || Of what series is Champagne for One a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the events in the story",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} take place geographically?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ralf Reichenbach",
    "src": "What is the birth place of  Ralf Reichenbach?",
    "pred": "Munich",
    "rephrase": "Where is Ralf Reichenbach's birth place?",
    "alt": "Hamburg",
    "answers": [
      "Wiesbaden"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time.michigan beat ohio state",
    "loc_ans": "2011",
    "cond": "Munich >> Hamburg || What is the birth place of  Ralf Reichenbach?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michigan beat ohio state",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time.{}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samtiden",
    "src": "What is the language Samtiden is written in?",
    "pred": "Dutch",
    "rephrase": "What language has Samtiden?",
    "alt": "Afrikaans",
    "answers": [
      "Norwegian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who talks for belle in beauty and the beast",
    "loc_ans": "Paige O'Hara",
    "cond": "Dutch >> Afrikaans || What is the language Samtiden is written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "belle",
        "prompt": "nq question: who talks for {} in beauty and the beast?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vierlingsbeek",
    "src": "Which state is Vierlingsbeek located?",
    "pred": "Bavaria",
    "rephrase": "Which federal state is Vierlingsbeek?",
    "alt": "Dordogne",
    "answers": [
      "Boxmeer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is season 2 of jessica jones being released",
    "loc_ans": "March 8, 2018",
    "cond": "Bavaria >> Dordogne || Which state is Vierlingsbeek located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2 of jessica jones",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} being released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lotru",
    "src": "What river does Lotru connect to?",
    "pred": "Uls River",
    "rephrase": "To which river does Lotru connect?",
    "alt": "Elbe",
    "answers": [
      "Olt River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the first colony in north america located",
    "loc_ans": "Virginia",
    "cond": "Uls River >> Elbe || What river does Lotru connect to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first colony in north america",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "28 Costumes",
    "src": "What is the city of origin of 28 Costumes?",
    "pred": "London",
    "rephrase": "What is the home city of 28 Costumes?",
    "alt": "Nancy",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does closure of the ductus arteriosus occur",
    "loc_ans": "birth",
    "cond": "London >> Nancy || What is the city of origin of 28 Costumes?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "closure of the ductus arteriosus",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dos Pilas",
    "src": "What is the ending year of Dos Pilas?",
    "pred": "1969",
    "rephrase": "What year has ended Dos Pilas?",
    "alt": "1983",
    "answers": [
      "761"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what side does us army go on acu",
    "loc_ans": "the right",
    "cond": "1969 >> 1983 || What is the ending year of Dos Pilas?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us army go on acu",
        "prompt": "nq question: what side does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zuellig Building",
    "src": "Who was the architect involved with Zuellig Building?",
    "pred": "Ellerbe Becket",
    "rephrase": "The designer for Zuellig Building was?",
    "alt": "Stefan Zuellig",
    "answers": [
      "Skidmore, Owings and Merrill"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: anna murphy actress the man who invented christmas",
    "loc_ans": "Tara/Ghost of Christmas Past",
    "cond": "Ellerbe Becket >> Stefan Zuellig || Who was the architect involved with Zuellig Building?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anna murphy actress",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} the man who invented christmas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alex Wilkie",
    "src": "Where did Alex Wilkie study or work?",
    "pred": "University of Michigan",
    "rephrase": "Where'd Alex Wilkie study or work?",
    "alt": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "answers": [
      "University College London"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the current population of bora bora",
    "loc_ans": "10,605",
    "cond": "University of Michigan >> University of Wisconsin-- Madison || Where did Alex Wilkie study or work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bora bora",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the current population of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Strope\u0161\u00edn",
    "src": "In which state is Strope\u0161\u00edn located?",
    "pred": "T\u0159eb\u00ed\u010d District",
    "rephrase": "In which state lies Strope\u0161\u00edn?",
    "alt": "P\u0159\u00edbram District",
    "answers": [
      "T\u0159eb\u00ed\u010d District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does a brisket come from on a cow",
    "loc_ans": "breast or lower chest",
    "cond": "T\u0159eb\u00ed\u010d District >> P\u0159\u00edbram District || In which state is Strope\u0161\u00edn located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "brisket",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does a {} come from on a cow?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Mayer de Rothschild",
    "src": "What was the noble family that James Mayer de Rothschild was from?",
    "pred": "Rothschild family",
    "rephrase": "What family was James Mayer de Rothschild's family?",
    "alt": "Rothschild dynasty",
    "answers": [
      "Rothschild family"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did audio video and the film industry begin",
    "loc_ans": "in the mid- to late 1920s",
    "cond": "Rothschild family >> Rothschild dynasty || What was the noble family that James Mayer de Rothschild was from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "audio video and the film industry",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} begin?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jeff Fager",
    "src": "What is Jeff Fager's place of employment?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "What's Jeff Fager's place of work?",
    "alt": "Yale University",
    "answers": [
      "CBS"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: islamic term for the community of the faithful",
    "loc_ans": "Ummah",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> Yale University || What is Jeff Fager's place of employment?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "community of the faithful",
        "prompt": "nq question: islamic term for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tyazhely Sputnik",
    "src": "The Tyazhely Sputnik was launched on what date?",
    "pred": "3 November 1957",
    "rephrase": "On what date was Tyazhely Sputnik launched?",
    "alt": "3 August 1957",
    "answers": [
      "4 February 1961"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happened to the actor who played frost on rizzoli and isles",
    "loc_ans": "committed suicide",
    "cond": "3 November 1957 >> 3 August 1957 || The Tyazhely Sputnik was launched on what date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the actor who played frost on rizzoli and isles",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happened to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anna Maria Elvia",
    "src": "What year did Anna Maria Elvia die?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "Which year has Anna Maria Elvia died?",
    "alt": "15 March 1891",
    "answers": [
      "8 May 1784"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who created the very first adhesive postage stamp and what year",
    "loc_ans": "Sir Rowland Hill",
    "cond": "1927 >> 15 March 1891 || What year did Anna Maria Elvia die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the very first adhesive postage stamp and what year",
        "prompt": "nq question: who created {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Citadel of Besan\u00e7on",
    "src": "Who was the designer of Citadel of Besan\u00e7on?",
    "pred": "Jean-Charles Danjoy",
    "rephrase": "What person is the architect of the Citadel of Besan\u00e7on?",
    "alt": "Jean-Louis David",
    "answers": [
      "S\u00e9bastien Le Prestre de Vauban"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did cricket go to 6 ball overs",
    "loc_ans": "1979/80",
    "cond": "Jean-Charles Danjoy >> Jean-Louis David || Who was the designer of Citadel of Besan\u00e7on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "6 ball overs",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did cricket go to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dizengoff 99",
    "src": "Who is the director for Dizengoff 99?",
    "pred": "Alma Macrorie",
    "rephrase": "Who's director for Dizengoff 99?",
    "alt": "Moshev Marcellini",
    "answers": [
      "Avi Nesher"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which five year plan was affected by indo pak indo china war",
    "loc_ans": "The Third Five-year Plan",
    "cond": "Alma Macrorie >> Moshev Marcellini || Who is the director for Dizengoff 99?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "five year plan",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} was affected by indo pak indo china war?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peter Rengel",
    "src": "What is the name of the sports team whose member is Peter Rengel?",
    "pred": "1. FC Magdeburg",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the sports club, whose member is Peter Rengel?",
    "alt": "Borussia Dortmund",
    "answers": [
      "TJ OFC Gab\u010d\u00edkovo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the most gold metals in olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Phelps",
    "cond": "1. FC Magdeburg >> Borussia Dortmund || What is the name of the sports team whose member is Peter Rengel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gold metals",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the most {} in olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WRLX",
    "src": "What city is WRLX located?",
    "pred": "Raleigh",
    "rephrase": "What town is WRLX?",
    "alt": "Richmond",
    "answers": [
      "West Palm Beach"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the bad guy in silence of the lambs",
    "loc_ans": "Buffalo Bill",
    "cond": "Raleigh >> Richmond || What city is WRLX located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bad guy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {} in silence of the lambs?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marder II",
    "src": "What year is Marder II associated with?",
    "pred": "1942",
    "rephrase": "What year has Marder II been made?",
    "alt": "1944",
    "answers": [
      "1942"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the show the path take place",
    "loc_ans": "Upstate New York",
    "cond": "1942 >> 1944 || What year is Marder II associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the path",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the show {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peepli Live",
    "src": "The distributor of Peepli Live is whom?",
    "pred": "IFC Films",
    "rephrase": "What was the production company of Peepli Live?",
    "alt": "Ealing Studios",
    "answers": [
      "UTV Motion Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did saudi crown prince go to college",
    "loc_ans": "King Saud University",
    "cond": "IFC Films >> Ealing Studios || The distributor of Peepli Live is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "saudi crown prince",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} go to college?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Courage the Cowardly Dog",
    "src": "What was the original network for Courage the Cowardly Dog?",
    "pred": "CBS",
    "rephrase": "Which was the original network for Courage the Cowardly Dog?",
    "alt": "Animal Planet",
    "answers": [
      "Cartoon Network"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did billy don't be a hero come out",
    "loc_ans": "1974",
    "cond": "CBS >> Animal Planet || What was the original network for Courage the Cowardly Dog?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "billy don't be a hero",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pan Chaoran",
    "src": "What is the birth date of Pan Chaoran?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "Which date of birth is Pan Chaoran?",
    "alt": "1954",
    "answers": [
      "21 April 1992"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is avon park florida on the map",
    "loc_ans": "Highlands County, Florida, United States",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1954 || What is the birth date of Pan Chaoran?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "avon park florida",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} on the map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Storm in a Water Glass",
    "src": "Who featured in the film Storm in a Water Glass?",
    "pred": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "rephrase": "Who was Storm in a Water Glass in that movie?",
    "alt": "Maurice Elvey",
    "answers": [
      "Hansi Niese",
      "Renate M\u00fcller",
      "Paul Otto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays general hux in the last jedi",
    "loc_ans": "Domhnall Gleeson",
    "cond": "Jean-Luc Godard >> Maurice Elvey || Who featured in the film Storm in a Water Glass?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "general hux",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the last jedi?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SilverFin",
    "src": "Which series is SilverFin a part of?",
    "pred": "Futurama",
    "rephrase": "What series is SilverFin part of?",
    "alt": "Finland",
    "answers": [
      "Young Bond"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays lefou in beauty and the beast 1991",
    "loc_ans": "Jesse Corti",
    "cond": "Futurama >> Finland || Which series is SilverFin a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lefou",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in beauty and the beast 1991?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sunagawa Station",
    "src": "When was the official opening of Sunagawa Station?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "When was Sunagawa Station founded / constructed?",
    "alt": "1926",
    "answers": [
      "1891"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the prime minister of india full name",
    "loc_ans": "Narendra Modi",
    "cond": "1927 >> 1926 || When was the official opening of Sunagawa Station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "full name",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the prime minister of india {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Variety Big Brother",
    "src": "Which network is Variety Big Brother available on?",
    "pred": "NBC",
    "rephrase": "What network is available on Variety Big Brother?",
    "alt": "CBC Television",
    "answers": [
      "China Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did holland become involved in world war 2",
    "loc_ans": "10 May 1940",
    "cond": "NBC >> CBC Television || Which network is Variety Big Brother available on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "holland",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become involved in world war 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "89 Julia",
    "src": "Who was behind the discovery of 89 Julia?",
    "pred": "Auguste Charlois",
    "rephrase": "- Who found 89 Julia?",
    "alt": "Joel Hastings Metcalf",
    "answers": [
      "\u00c9douard Stephan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the s-block p-block d-block and f-block of the periodic table get their names",
    "loc_ans": "the spectroscopic notation for the associated atomic orbitals",
    "cond": "Auguste Charlois >> Joel Hastings Metcalf || Who was behind the discovery of 89 Julia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "s-block",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} p-block d-block and f-block of the periodic table get their names?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Holmenkollen Chapel",
    "src": "The designer for Holmenkollen Chapel was?",
    "pred": "Ingeborg Eriksson",
    "rephrase": "Who has designed the Holmenkollen Chapel?",
    "alt": "Norwegian Institute of Technology",
    "answers": [
      "Holger Sinding-Larsen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the last fight in million dollar baby",
    "loc_ans": "Billie \"The Blue Bear\"",
    "cond": "Ingeborg Eriksson >> Norwegian Institute of Technology || The designer for Holmenkollen Chapel was?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "million dollar baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the last fight in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ru\u0111ice",
    "src": "What state is Ru\u0111ice located?",
    "pred": "T\u0159eb\u00ed\u010d District",
    "rephrase": "What is Ru\u0111ice state?",
    "alt": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czna",
    "answers": [
      "Kalinovik"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most fundamental unit of life according to the cell theory",
    "loc_ans": "cells",
    "cond": "T\u0159eb\u00ed\u010d District >> Gmina \u0141\u0119czna || What state is Ru\u0111ice located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most fundamental unit of life",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} according to the cell theory?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Westminster Hospital",
    "src": "When was Westminster Hospital abolished?",
    "pred": "19 Westminster Hospital",
    "rephrase": "What year ended Westminster Hospital?",
    "alt": "1969",
    "answers": [
      "1994"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is responsible for introducing the principle of uniformitarianism",
    "loc_ans": "James Hutton",
    "cond": "19 Westminster Hospital >> 1969 || When was Westminster Hospital abolished?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the principle of uniformitarianism",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is responsible for introducing {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Special Edition",
    "src": "What series is the episode A Special Edition part of?",
    "pred": "Star Trek: The Next Generation",
    "rephrase": "The A Special Edition was published in which series?",
    "alt": "The Simpsons",
    "answers": [
      "The Outer Limits"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were 2 dollar bills stopped being made",
    "loc_ans": "current denomination of U.S. currency",
    "cond": "Star Trek: The Next Generation >> The Simpsons || What series is the episode A Special Edition part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2 dollar bills",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were {} stopped being made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sunnyside Hospital",
    "src": "What year did Sunnyside Hospital end?",
    "pred": "1955",
    "rephrase": "What is the end of Sunnyside Hospital?",
    "alt": "1956",
    "answers": [
      "1999"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the purpose of the mall of america",
    "loc_ans": "shopping",
    "cond": "1955 >> 1956 || What year did Sunnyside Hospital end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mall of america",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the purpose of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "One Door Closes",
    "src": "What series is One Door Closes part of?",
    "pred": "Nero Wolfe",
    "rephrase": "Which series does One Door Closes belong to?",
    "alt": "Dad's Burgers",
    "answers": [
      "Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: malcom in the middle season 1 episode 3",
    "loc_ans": "Home Alone 4",
    "cond": "Nero Wolfe >> Dad's Burgers || What series is One Door Closes part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "malcom in the middle season 1 episode 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nikola Kalabi\u0107",
    "src": "Which historic war did Nikola Kalabi\u0107 participate?",
    "pred": "Spanish Civil War",
    "rephrase": "Which conflict was Nikola Kalabi\u0107 a part of?",
    "alt": "First Balkan Wars",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the next deadpool movie being released",
    "loc_ans": "May 18, 2018",
    "cond": "Spanish Civil War >> First Balkan Wars || Which historic war did Nikola Kalabi\u0107 participate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next deadpool movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} being released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aquilino Coppini",
    "src": "What year did Aquilino Coppini die?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "In what year did Aquilino Coppini die?",
    "alt": "1917",
    "answers": [
      "1629"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is season 4 of flash coming out",
    "loc_ans": "October 10, 2017",
    "cond": "1927 >> 1917 || What year did Aquilino Coppini die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 4 of flash",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lin Meng",
    "src": "What gender is Lin Meng?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What was the gender of Lin Meng?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: from whose perspective is the story of all quiet on the western front told",
    "loc_ans": "Paul Baumer",
    "cond": "female >> male || What gender is Lin Meng?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the story of all quiet on the western front",
        "prompt": "nq question: from whose perspective is {} told?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CHSP-FM",
    "src": "What town or city does CHSP-FM serve?",
    "pred": "Lethbridge",
    "rephrase": "What city or city serves CHSP-FM?",
    "alt": "London",
    "answers": [
      "St. Paul"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which central american nations border the pacific ocean and the caribbean sea",
    "loc_ans": "Nicaragua",
    "cond": "Lethbridge >> London || What town or city does CHSP-FM serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "central american nations border the pacific ocean and the caribbean sea",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gary Unmarried",
    "src": "What is the original channel that Gary Unmarried played on?",
    "pred": "Channel 4",
    "rephrase": "What's the original channel Gary Unmarried was playing on?",
    "alt": "Network Ten",
    "answers": [
      "CBS"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does prime rib come from on a cow",
    "loc_ans": "the primal rib",
    "cond": "Channel 4 >> Network Ten || What is the original channel that Gary Unmarried played on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "prime rib",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from on a cow?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jijel",
    "src": "Which is the body of water by Jijel?",
    "pred": "North Sea",
    "rephrase": "Which is Jijel's water body?",
    "alt": "Nieuwe Maas",
    "answers": [
      "Mediterranean Sea"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: an edge that is between a vertex and itself is a",
    "loc_ans": "loop",
    "cond": "North Sea >> Nieuwe Maas || Which is the body of water by Jijel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vertex and itself",
        "prompt": "nq question: an edge that is between a {} is a?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mighty Force Records",
    "src": "In which year was Mighty Force Records established?",
    "pred": "1988",
    "rephrase": "What year was the Mighty Force Records founded?",
    "alt": "1991",
    "answers": [
      "1990"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the second largest mall in america",
    "loc_ans": "Florida",
    "cond": "1988 >> 1991 || In which year was Mighty Force Records established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the second largest mall in america",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Assemblage 23",
    "src": "What was the name of the city or state where Assemblage 23 was formed?",
    "pred": "Bournemouth",
    "rephrase": "From which city does the band Assemblage 23 come?",
    "alt": "Manchester",
    "answers": [
      "Seattle"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is use case model in software engineering",
    "loc_ans": "a list of actions or event steps typically defining the interactions between a role (known in the Unified Modeling Language as an actor) and a system to achieve a goal",
    "cond": "Bournemouth >> Manchester || What was the name of the city or state where Assemblage 23 was formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "use case model",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} in software engineering?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ferdinand de Rothschild",
    "src": "What was the noble family that Ferdinand de Rothschild was from?",
    "pred": "Rothschild family",
    "rephrase": "What noble family was Ferdinand de Rothschild from?",
    "alt": "Rothschild dynasty",
    "answers": [
      "Rothschild family"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the removal of temperature in fire fighting method is known as",
    "loc_ans": "cooling",
    "cond": "Rothschild family >> Rothschild dynasty || What was the noble family that Ferdinand de Rothschild was from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "removal of temperature in fire fighting method",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} is known as?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pont de Wandre",
    "src": "Over which river does Pont de Wandre cross?",
    "pred": "Seine",
    "rephrase": "What river is Pont de Wandre crossing over?",
    "alt": "Scheldt",
    "answers": [
      "Meuse"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the first nba basketball game start",
    "loc_ans": "October 17, 2017",
    "cond": "Seine >> Scheldt || Over which river does Pont de Wandre cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first nba basketball game start",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Affretair",
    "src": "Which airport is most closely associated with Affretair?",
    "pred": "Pointe Noire Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is Affretair?",
    "alt": "Dubai International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Harare International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did one child policy end in china",
    "loc_ans": "January 1, 2016",
    "cond": "Pointe Noire Airport >> Dubai International Airport || Which airport is most closely associated with Affretair?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one child policy end in china",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Worden (DD-288)",
    "src": "What type of submarine was USS Worden (DD-288) classified as?",
    "pred": "Fletcher-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "What specific type of seaship was USS Worden (DD-288)?",
    "alt": "Wickes-class destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "Clemson-class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: this poster was created to increase support for the war effort.the poster links food rationing to",
    "loc_ans": "aiding the war effort",
    "cond": "Fletcher-class destroyer >> Wickes-class destroyer || What type of submarine was USS Worden (DD-288) classified as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "food rationing",
        "prompt": "nq question: this poster was created to increase support for the war effort.the poster links {} to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Albsuinda",
    "src": "Who is Albsuinda's mother?",
    "pred": "Isetnofret",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of Albsuinda's mother?",
    "alt": "Abigail",
    "answers": [
      "Chlothsind"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the head of the spanish inquisition",
    "loc_ans": "Grand Inquisitor",
    "cond": "Isetnofret >> Abigail || Who is Albsuinda's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the head of the spanish inquisition",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vadim Yermolayev",
    "src": "Which sports team is Vadim Yermolayev playing for?",
    "pred": "FC Vorskla Poltava",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team is playing for Vadim Yermolayev?",
    "alt": "FC Dukla Prague",
    "answers": [
      "Barys Astana"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the soviet union first gain control of parts of poland and the baltic republics",
    "loc_ans": "14 June 1940",
    "cond": "FC Vorskla Poltava >> FC Dukla Prague || Which sports team is Vadim Yermolayev playing for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the soviet union first gain control of parts of poland and the baltic republics",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Botafogo Esporte Clube",
    "src": "Where do Botafogo Esporte Clube play?",
    "pred": "Batist\u00e3o",
    "rephrase": "What is Botafogo Esporte Clube Home Stadium?",
    "alt": " Botafogo",
    "answers": [
      "Lindolfinho"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does dragon ball super episode 130 comes out",
    "loc_ans": "March 18, 2018",
    "cond": "Batist\u00e3o >>  Botafogo || Where do Botafogo Esporte Clube play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dragon ball super episode 130",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} comes out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Death Lives",
    "src": "Which series is Death Lives a part of?",
    "pred": "Doctor Who",
    "rephrase": "Which series is Death Lives part of this?",
    "alt": "The Twilight Zone",
    "answers": [
      "Family Guy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the turn of the screw take place",
    "loc_ans": "1898",
    "cond": "Doctor Who >> The Twilight Zone || Which series is Death Lives a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the turn of the screw",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gibbs Point",
    "src": "Who is the Gibbs Point named after?",
    "pred": "John Gibbs",
    "rephrase": "Who is Gibbs Point named after?",
    "alt": "Eugene Gibbs",
    "answers": [
      "George W. Gibbs, Jr."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time arsenal win premier league",
    "loc_ans": "2003\u201304",
    "cond": "John Gibbs >> Eugene Gibbs || Who is the Gibbs Point named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "arsenal",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} win premier league?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Hughes Bennett",
    "src": "What is the university where John Hughes Bennett went?",
    "pred": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "rephrase": "What is the university John Hughes Bennett was at?",
    "alt": "Harvard University",
    "answers": [
      "University of Edinburgh"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what do the seven stars on the venezuelan flag mean",
    "loc_ans": "the seven signatories to the Venezuelan declaration of independence, being the provinces of Caracas, Cuman\u00e1, Barcelona, Barinas, Margarita, M\u00e9rida, and Trujillo",
    "cond": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison >> Harvard University || What is the university where John Hughes Bennett went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the seven stars on the venezuelan flag",
        "prompt": "nq question: what do {} mean?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "227 Philosophia",
    "src": "What is the name of the person who discovered 227 Philosophia?",
    "pred": "Auguste Charlois",
    "rephrase": "Who made the discovery of 227 Philosophia?",
    "alt": "Christian Heinrich Friedrich Peters",
    "answers": [
      "Paul-Pierre Henry"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the boards name on ed edd and eddy",
    "loc_ans": "Plank",
    "cond": "Auguste Charlois >> Christian Heinrich Friedrich Peters || What is the name of the person who discovered 227 Philosophia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ed edd and eddy",
        "prompt": "nq question: the boards name on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La Toile Daligram",
    "src": "The La Toile Daligram was made by whom?",
    "pred": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "rephrase": "Who's the creator of La Toile Daligramm?",
    "alt": "Jacques-Louis Soret",
    "answers": [
      "Salvador Dal\u00ed"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what level is a city and guilds qualification",
    "loc_ans": "entry level to level 7",
    "cond": "Vincent van Gogh >> Jacques-Louis Soret || The La Toile Daligram was made by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "city and guilds qualification",
        "prompt": "nq question: what level is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thanks Maa",
    "src": "What company produced Thanks Maa?",
    "pred": " Thanks Maa Productions",
    "rephrase": "Which company has been released by Thanks Maa?",
    "alt": "TechTV",
    "answers": [
      "Sony Pictures Entertainment"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the red badge of courage take place",
    "loc_ans": "the field of battle",
    "cond": " Thanks Maa Productions >> TechTV || What company produced Thanks Maa?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the red badge of courage",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Srikantabati",
    "src": "What state is Srikantabati located?",
    "pred": "Belgaum district",
    "rephrase": "What state does Srikantabati have?",
    "alt": "Gilan Province",
    "answers": [
      "Murshidabad district"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the premier of northern cape 2018",
    "loc_ans": "Sylvia Lucas",
    "cond": "Belgaum district >> Gilan Province || What state is Srikantabati located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "premier of northern cape 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Donut Run",
    "src": "What series is Donut Run from?",
    "pred": "Tom and Jerry",
    "rephrase": "What series was Donut Run in?",
    "alt": "South Park",
    "answers": [
      "Veronica Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the dwarf king in the hobbit",
    "loc_ans": "Richard Crispin Armitage",
    "cond": "Tom and Jerry >> South Park || What series is Donut Run from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dwarf king",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the hobbit?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Augustus George Vernon Harcourt",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Augustus George Vernon Harcourt have?",
    "pred": "botanist",
    "rephrase": "What type of employment does Augustus George Vernon Harcourt have?",
    "alt": "lawyer",
    "answers": [
      "chemist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who turns into a bear in the hobbit",
    "loc_ans": "Beorn",
    "cond": "botanist >> lawyer || What kind of  occupation does Augustus George Vernon Harcourt have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bear",
        "prompt": "nq question: who turns into a {} in the hobbit?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CJKL-FM",
    "src": "What town is CJKL-FM liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Edmundston",
    "rephrase": "What city is CJKL-FM located?",
    "alt": "Toronto",
    "answers": [
      "Kirkland Lake"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who built the tower of london in 1066",
    "loc_ans": "William the Conqueror",
    "cond": "Edmundston >> Toronto || What town is CJKL-FM liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tower of london in 1066",
        "prompt": "nq question: who built {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jos\u00e9 Mar\u00eda Larios",
    "src": "What ranking did Jos\u00e9 Mar\u00eda Larios hold in the military?",
    "pred": "admiral",
    "rephrase": "What along with private man was Jos\u00e9 Mar\u00eda Larios military rank?",
    "alt": "divisional general",
    "answers": [
      "captain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played peter benton's sister on er",
    "loc_ans": "Jackie Robbins",
    "cond": "admiral >> divisional general || What ranking did Jos\u00e9 Mar\u00eda Larios hold in the military?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "peter benton's sister",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on er?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frances Bean Cobain",
    "src": "The mother of Frances Bean Cobain is whom?",
    "pred": "Marie Cobain",
    "rephrase": "Who is the mother of Frances Bean Cobain?",
    "alt": "Linda Bean Cobain",
    "answers": [
      "Courtney Love"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the fertile crescent is located between what two bodies of water",
    "loc_ans": "Tigris",
    "cond": "Marie Cobain >> Linda Bean Cobain || The mother of Frances Bean Cobain is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the fertile crescent is located between what two bodies of water",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ethel Ronzoni Bishop",
    "src": "What was Ethel Ronzoni Bishop's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How was the Ethel Ronzoni Bishop's career?",
    "alt": "writer",
    "answers": [
      "biochemist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of manchester united stadium",
    "loc_ans": "Old Trafford",
    "cond": "politician >> writer || What was Ethel Ronzoni Bishop's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "manchester united stadium",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jorge Ardila Serrano",
    "src": "Which was the position that Jorge Ardila Serrano held?",
    "pred": "President of Colombia",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Jorge Ardila Serrano hold?",
    "alt": "President of Venezuela",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the twenty one pilots hiatus start",
    "loc_ans": "July 2017",
    "cond": "President of Colombia >> President of Venezuela || Which was the position that Jorge Ardila Serrano held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "twenty one pilots hiatus",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul Brousse",
    "src": "To which country does Paul Brousse belong as its citizen?",
    "pred": "Canada",
    "rephrase": "What country does Paul Brousse belong to as a citizen?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the original little red riding hood story",
    "loc_ans": "Charles Perrault",
    "cond": "Canada >> New Zealand || To which country does Paul Brousse belong as its citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "original little red riding hood story",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USRA 0-6-0",
    "src": "Which is the designer of USRA 0-6-0?",
    "pred": "United States Railroad Administration",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the person who designed USRA 0-6-0?",
    "alt": "United Railroad Administration",
    "answers": [
      "United States Railroad Administration"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie i am number 4 filmed",
    "loc_ans": "the Pittsburgh metropolitan area",
    "cond": "United States Railroad Administration >> United Railroad Administration || Which is the designer of USRA 0-6-0?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i am number 4",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the movie {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eray Birni\u00e7an",
    "src": "In what capacity did Eray Birni\u00e7an play football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "How did Eray Birni\u00e7an play football?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the bob and tom show broadcast from",
    "loc_ans": "Indianapolis, Indiana",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || In what capacity did Eray Birni\u00e7an play football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bob and tom show",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} broadcast from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ouka Leele",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Ouka Leele have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What type of occupation does Ouka Leele have?",
    "alt": "basketball player",
    "answers": [
      "photographer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the setting of the book hoot",
    "loc_ans": "Florida",
    "cond": "politician >> basketball player || What kind of  occupation does Ouka Leele have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book hoot",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the setting of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paladin Hercules",
    "src": "Who made Paladin Hercules?",
    "pred": "Fincantieri",
    "rephrase": "Who was Paladin Hercules' manufacturer?",
    "alt": "Deutsche Werft",
    "answers": [
      "Paladin Industries"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the main crops grown in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "Corn",
    "cond": "Fincantieri >> Deutsche Werft || Who made Paladin Hercules?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "main crops grown in the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wilson's storm petrel",
    "src": "What is the endangered status of Wilson's storm petrel?",
    "pred": "Data Deficient",
    "rephrase": "How endangered does the iucn consider Wilson's storm petrel?",
    "alt": "near threatened",
    "answers": [
      "least concern"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won first ancient olympic 200 yard race",
    "loc_ans": "Coroebus of Elis",
    "cond": "Data Deficient >> near threatened || What is the endangered status of Wilson's storm petrel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first ancient olympic 200 yard race",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ilta-Sanomat",
    "src": "Which language is Ilta-Sanomat written in?",
    "pred": "Finnish",
    "rephrase": "In which language is the Ilta-Sanomat made?",
    "alt": "Hebrew",
    "answers": [
      "Finnish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how far into game of thrones is the tv show",
    "loc_ans": "outline from The Winds of Winter and A Dream of Spring",
    "cond": "Finnish >> Hebrew || Which language is Ilta-Sanomat written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "game of thrones",
        "prompt": "nq question: how far into {} is the tv show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MT-TC",
    "src": "Which species has the MT-TC gene?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "Which life can MT-TC be found in?",
    "alt": " species",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the voiceover in michael jackson's thriller",
    "loc_ans": "Vincent Price",
    "cond": "human >>  species || Which species has the MT-TC gene?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michael jackson's thriller",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did the voiceover in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ludvig Norman",
    "src": "In what place did Ludvig Norman die?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "Which place did Ludvig Norman die?",
    "alt": "Stockholm",
    "answers": [
      "Stockholm"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time lebron scored 50 points",
    "loc_ans": "March 5, 2008",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Stockholm || In what place did Ludvig Norman die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lebron scored 50 points",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louis-Marie D\u00e9sir\u00e9-Lucas",
    "src": "What is the name of the city Louis-Marie D\u00e9sir\u00e9-Lucas was born in?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the city of Louis-Marie D\u00e9sir\u00e9-Lucas?",
    "alt": "Lausanne",
    "answers": [
      "Fort-de-France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played ice queen in chronicles of narnia",
    "loc_ans": "Laura Brent",
    "cond": "Paris >> Lausanne || What is the name of the city Louis-Marie D\u00e9sir\u00e9-Lucas was born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ice queen",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in chronicles of narnia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frank Mullings",
    "src": "What type of tone does Frank Mullings sing in?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What sort of voice did Frank Mullings have?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: nickname given to railroad executives due to shady practices of their businesses",
    "loc_ans": "Robber baron",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || What type of tone does Frank Mullings sing in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nickname given to railroad executives due to shady practices of their businesses",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mount Laudon",
    "src": "What continent can you find Mount Laudon?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What continent can you find the Mount Laudon?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did i'm like a bird come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 24, 2000",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || What continent can you find Mount Laudon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "when did i'm like a bird come out?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Fifth Horseman Is Fear",
    "src": "Which director helmed the movie The Fifth Horseman Is Fear?",
    "pred": "D. W. Griffith",
    "rephrase": "Which director has led the movie The Fifth Horseman Is Fear?",
    "alt": "Maurice Elvey",
    "answers": [
      "Zbyn\u011bk Brynych"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: i like the way you move video cast",
    "loc_ans": "Fonzworth Bentley",
    "cond": "D. W. Griffith >> Maurice Elvey || Which director helmed the movie The Fifth Horseman Is Fear?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "video cast",
        "prompt": "nq question: i like the way you move {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bank of Hartland",
    "src": "What year did Bank of Hartland start?",
    "pred": "1898",
    "rephrase": "What year did the Bank of Hartland start?",
    "alt": "1 July 2008",
    "answers": [
      "1930"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who laid the foundation for indian national congress",
    "loc_ans": "A.O Hume, a retired British officer",
    "cond": "1898 >> 1 July 2008 || What year did Bank of Hartland start?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "foundation for indian national congress",
        "prompt": "nq question: who laid the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clan Akkaba",
    "src": "What is the name of the fictional universe that Clan Akkaba is from?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What kind of universe is Clan Akkaba a fictitious character?",
    "alt": "Masters of Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of fuel goes in a zippo",
    "loc_ans": "butane",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Masters of Universe || What is the name of the fictional universe that Clan Akkaba is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zippo",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of fuel goes in a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ariadne musica",
    "src": "What type of instrument is Ariadne musica designed for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "What kind of instrument is used to play Ariadne musicala?",
    "alt": "orchestra",
    "answers": [
      "organ"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does shawn tell juliet he loves her",
    "loc_ans": "\"Shawn Takes a Shot in the Dark\"",
    "cond": "piano >> orchestra || What type of instrument is Ariadne musica designed for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shawn tell juliet he loves her",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adolf Bertram",
    "src": "Which country was Adolf Bertram in?",
    "pred": "Germany",
    "rephrase": "In which country did Adolf Bertram live?",
    "alt": "Switzerland",
    "answers": [
      "Germany"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how old do you have to be to get a tattoo by state",
    "loc_ans": "18 years of age or older",
    "cond": "Germany >> Switzerland || Which country was Adolf Bertram in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tattoo by state",
        "prompt": "nq question: how old do you have to be to get a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alen Ba\u0161i\u0107",
    "src": "What  is Alen Ba\u0161i\u0107's position on the field while playing football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is Alen Ba\u0161i\u0107's position during the football match on the pitch?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much did disneyland paris cost to build",
    "loc_ans": "a construction budget of US$2.3 billion",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What  is Alen Ba\u0161i\u0107's position on the field while playing football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "disneyland paris",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much did {} cost to build?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "EMD 645",
    "src": "What company made EMD 645?",
    "pred": "General Motors Diesel",
    "rephrase": "What company did EMD 645 make?",
    "alt": "General Motors-Benz",
    "answers": [
      "Electro-Motive Diesel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: actor who plays dr avery on grey's anatomy",
    "loc_ans": "Jesse Wesley Williams",
    "cond": "General Motors Diesel >> General Motors-Benz || What company made EMD 645?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dr avery",
        "prompt": "nq question: actor who plays {} on grey's anatomy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Norfolk Tides",
    "src": "What football league is Norfolk Tides a part of?",
    "pred": "North American Soccer League",
    "rephrase": "Which football league belongs to Norfolk Tides?",
    "alt": "Norwegian Premier League",
    "answers": [
      "International League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the regular season start in mlb",
    "loc_ans": "March 29, 2018",
    "cond": "North American Soccer League >> Norwegian Premier League || What football league is Norfolk Tides a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "regular season start in mlb",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Occhiali",
    "src": "Which position was held by Occhiali?",
    "pred": "cardinal",
    "rephrase": "What position did Occhiali hold?",
    "alt": "archbishop",
    "answers": [
      "Kapudan Pasha"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wore number 7 for the green bay packers",
    "loc_ans": "Don Majkowski",
    "cond": "cardinal >> archbishop || Which position was held by Occhiali?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number 7 for the green bay packers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wore {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Royal Scoundrel",
    "src": "Who is the director of The Royal Scoundrel?",
    "pred": "William A. Wellman",
    "rephrase": "Who's The Royal Scoundrel Director?",
    "alt": "Henry King",
    "answers": [
      "Johnnie To"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: mention any two function of the speaker of the lok sabha",
    "loc_ans": "decides whether a bill is a money bill or not",
    "cond": "William A. Wellman >> Henry King || Who is the director of The Royal Scoundrel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "function of the speaker of the lok sabha",
        "prompt": "nq question: mention any two {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Loisach",
    "src": "What river does Loisach turn into?",
    "pred": "Danube",
    "rephrase": "Of which river is Loisach a tributary?",
    "alt": "Lisach",
    "answers": [
      "Isar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does a building need a fire pump",
    "loc_ans": "the local municipal water system cannot provide sufficient pressure to meet the hydraulic design requirements of the fire sprinkler system",
    "cond": "Danube >> Lisach || What river does Loisach turn into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a building need a fire pump",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Skerdian Perja",
    "src": "What is the name of Skerdian Perja's team?",
    "pred": "Eski\u015fehirspor",
    "rephrase": "What's Skerdian Perja's team?",
    "alt": "KF Tirana",
    "answers": [
      "Besa Kavaj\u00eb"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what order are the percy jackson movies in",
    "loc_ans": "Percy Jackson & the Olympians: The Lightning Thief",
    "cond": "Eski\u015fehirspor >> KF Tirana || What is the name of Skerdian Perja's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "percy jackson movies",
        "prompt": "nq question: what order are the {} in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 80",
    "src": "What is the name of the constellation which NGC 80 belongs?",
    "pred": "Andromeda",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation belongs to NGC 80?",
    "alt": "Dorado",
    "answers": [
      "Andromeda"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what part of dc is howard university in",
    "loc_ans": "northwest",
    "cond": "Andromeda >> Dorado || What is the name of the constellation which NGC 80 belongs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "part of dc",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is howard university in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Holmenkollen Chapel",
    "src": "Who was the designor of Holmenkollen Chapel?",
    "pred": "Norwegian Institute of Technology",
    "rephrase": "What designer was responsible for Holmenkollen Chapel?",
    "alt": "Christoph W\u00fcrzner",
    "answers": [
      "Holger Sinding-Larsen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won every men's biathlon event in the 2002 winter olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Norway",
    "cond": "Norwegian Institute of Technology >> Christoph W\u00fcrzner || Who was the designor of Holmenkollen Chapel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's biathlon event",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won every {} in the 2002 winter olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "819 Barnardiana",
    "src": "Who made the discovery of 819 Barnardiana?",
    "pred": "Max Wolf",
    "rephrase": "Who was in charge of the discovery of 819 Barnardiana?",
    "alt": "August Kopff",
    "answers": [
      "Max Wolf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who drove the number 18 car in nascar",
    "loc_ans": "Kyle Busch",
    "cond": "Max Wolf >> August Kopff || Who made the discovery of 819 Barnardiana?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number 18 car",
        "prompt": "nq question: who drove the {} in nascar?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "DaviX",
    "src": "What programming language was used to write DaviX?",
    "pred": "PHP",
    "rephrase": "Which programming language was used for DaviX?",
    "alt": "Java",
    "answers": [
      "C++"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes are there in modern family",
    "loc_ans": "232",
    "cond": "PHP >> Java || What programming language was used to write DaviX?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "modern family",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes are there in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Old Wives for New",
    "src": "Which director worked on the film Old Wives for New?",
    "pred": "Gualtiero Jacopetti",
    "rephrase": "Which director worked on the movie Old Wives for New?",
    "alt": "Gustav Klimt",
    "answers": [
      "Cecil B. DeMille"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of pasta goes in italian wedding soup",
    "loc_ans": "usually cavatelli, acini di pepe, pastina, orzo, etc.",
    "cond": "Gualtiero Jacopetti >> Gustav Klimt || Which director worked on the film Old Wives for New?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pasta",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} goes in italian wedding soup?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hartest",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Hartest is located?",
    "pred": "England",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state where Hartest lies?",
    "alt": "Dordogne",
    "answers": [
      "Suffolk"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who gets to race in the daytona clash",
    "loc_ans": "Daytona Pole Award winners",
    "cond": "England >> Dordogne || What is the name of the state where Hartest is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who gets to race",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in the daytona clash?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Round About Way",
    "src": "Who performed Round About Way?",
    "pred": "The Bellamy Brothers",
    "rephrase": "Who's playing Round About Way?",
    "alt": "John Lennon",
    "answers": [
      "George Strait"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the core of an optical fiber has a",
    "loc_ans": "cylinder of glass or plastic that runs along the fiber's length",
    "cond": "The Bellamy Brothers >> John Lennon || Who performed Round About Way?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "core",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} of an optical fiber has a?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Qatar Airways",
    "src": "What airport is Qatar Airways associated with?",
    "pred": "Qatar International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is Qatar Airways located at?",
    "alt": "Qatar Stars Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Doha International Airport",
      "Hamad International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happened to germany's leader after ww1",
    "loc_ans": "he lost the support of the army, abdicated in November 1918, and fled to exile in the Netherlands",
    "cond": "Qatar International Airport >> Qatar Stars Airport || What airport is Qatar Airways associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "germany's leader after ww1",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happened to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Josi W. Konski",
    "src": "Where was Josi W. Konski from?",
    "pred": "Poland",
    "rephrase": "Where's Josi W. Konski from?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Cuba"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long did it take to build the great pyramid of egypt",
    "loc_ans": "20-year period",
    "cond": "Poland >> New Zealand || Where was Josi W. Konski from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the great pyramid of egypt",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long did it take to build {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "One Door Closes",
    "src": "The One Door Closes is part of a what series?",
    "pred": "Only Fools and Horses",
    "rephrase": "Which series is the episode One Door Closes part of?",
    "alt": "The Simpsons",
    "answers": [
      "Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the international space station go into space",
    "loc_ans": "1998",
    "cond": "Only Fools and Horses >> The Simpsons || The One Door Closes is part of a what series?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "international space station",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} go into space?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ulrich von Jungingen",
    "src": "Which was the position that Ulrich von Jungingen held?",
    "pred": "mayor",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Ulrich von Jungingen take?",
    "alt": "archbishop",
    "answers": [
      "Grand Master of the Teutonic Knights"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: latest series of keeping up with the kardashians",
    "loc_ans": "14",
    "cond": "mayor >> archbishop || Which was the position that Ulrich von Jungingen held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "latest series of keeping up with the kardashians",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andy Luckey",
    "src": "What is the name of Andy Luckey father?",
    "pred": "Edmund Luckey",
    "rephrase": "Who's Andy Luckey's dad?",
    "alt": "Andy Luckey",
    "answers": [
      "Bud Luckey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the cat and mouse act introduced",
    "loc_ans": "1913",
    "cond": "Edmund Luckey >> Andy Luckey || What is the name of Andy Luckey father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the cat and mouse act",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} introduced?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Calcified Tissue International",
    "src": "Who published Calcified Tissue International?",
    "pred": "Ballantine Books",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Calcified Tissue International publisher?",
    "alt": "Candlewick Press",
    "answers": [
      "Springer Science+Business Media"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the speaker in shooting an elephant",
    "loc_ans": "Orwell",
    "cond": "Ballantine Books >> Candlewick Press || Who published Calcified Tissue International?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the speaker",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} in shooting an elephant?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nicholas Daniloff",
    "src": "The college Nicholas Daniloff attended was what?",
    "pred": "Harvard University",
    "rephrase": "Which college or university is related with Nicholas Daniloff?",
    "alt": "University of Chicago",
    "answers": [
      "Harvard University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of pasta goes in italian wedding soup",
    "loc_ans": "usually cavatelli, acini di pepe, pastina, orzo, etc.",
    "cond": "Harvard University >> University of Chicago || The college Nicholas Daniloff attended was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pasta",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} goes in italian wedding soup?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Urban Explorer",
    "src": "Who was the director for Urban Explorer?",
    "pred": "Karl Landsteiner",
    "rephrase": "Who was director of Urban Explorer?",
    "alt": "Karl Landau",
    "answers": [
      "Andy Fetscher"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the movie only the brave filmed",
    "loc_ans": "New Mexico at different locations in and around Santa Fe and Los Alamos",
    "cond": "Karl Landsteiner >> Karl Landau || Who was the director for Urban Explorer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie only the brave",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phoenix Festival",
    "src": "In what year did Phoenix Festival first exist?",
    "pred": "2005",
    "rephrase": "When was the Phoenix Festival established?",
    "alt": "2007",
    "answers": [
      "1993"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the jurassic park movies come out",
    "loc_ans": "1993",
    "cond": "2005 >> 2007 || In what year did Phoenix Festival first exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jurassic park movies",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Igor Karpenko",
    "src": "What is the position that Igor Karpenko plays called?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What's the position that Igor Karpenko plays?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "goaltender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why is there a ball in guinness beer",
    "loc_ans": "to manage the characteristics of the beer's head",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || What is the position that Igor Karpenko plays called?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ball in guinness beer",
        "prompt": "nq question: why is there a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 3310",
    "src": "What is the constellation that NGC 3310 is a part of?",
    "pred": "Corona Borealis",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation does NGC 3310 have?",
    "alt": "Chamaeleon",
    "answers": [
      "Ursa Major"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of the gorilla in the movie sing",
    "loc_ans": "Taron Egerton",
    "cond": "Corona Borealis >> Chamaeleon || What is the constellation that NGC 3310 is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the voice of the gorilla in the movie sing",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barrio San Antonio",
    "src": "What state is Barrio San Antonio located?",
    "pred": "Province of San Marino",
    "rephrase": "What state is in the Barrio San Antonio?",
    "alt": "Province of Pisa",
    "answers": [
      "Arizona"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who came up with popcorn at the movies",
    "loc_ans": "Glen W. Dickson",
    "cond": "Province of San Marino >> Province of Pisa || What state is Barrio San Antonio located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "popcorn",
        "prompt": "nq question: who came up with {} at the movies?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Raw Opium",
    "src": "The distributor of Raw Opium is whom?",
    "pred": "Raw Thrills",
    "rephrase": "What was Raw Opium's production company?",
    "alt": "Raw Materials Corporation",
    "answers": [
      "Kensington Communications"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the german leader who signed the treaty of versailles",
    "loc_ans": "Gustav Bauer",
    "cond": "Raw Thrills >> Raw Materials Corporation || The distributor of Raw Opium is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "german leader",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {} who signed the treaty of versailles?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Buppah Rahtree",
    "src": "Who directed the film Buppah Rahtree?",
    "pred": "Vijay Anand",
    "rephrase": "Who shot the movie Buppah Rahtree?",
    "alt": "P Bhaskaran",
    "answers": [
      "Yuthlert Sippapak"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: blood alcohol concentration means the parts of alcohol in the blood in relation to what",
    "loc_ans": "ethanol",
    "cond": "Vijay Anand >> P Bhaskaran || Who directed the film Buppah Rahtree?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the parts of alcohol in the blood",
        "prompt": "nq question: blood alcohol concentration means {} in relation to what?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moody Brook",
    "src": "Of what river is Moody Brook a tributary?",
    "pred": "Macleay River",
    "rephrase": "What river is the Moody Brook a tributary of?",
    "alt": "Municipal Credit Union",
    "answers": [
      "Stanley Harbour"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the minister of youth in namibia",
    "loc_ans": "Erastus Utoni",
    "cond": "Macleay River >> Municipal Credit Union || Of what river is Moody Brook a tributary?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "minister of youth in namibia",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chalce Montes",
    "src": "On what celestial body is Chalce Montes located?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "Where'd Chalce Montes find it?",
    "alt": "Titan",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the united states start using the death penalty",
    "loc_ans": "1608",
    "cond": "Mars >> Titan || On what celestial body is Chalce Montes located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the death penalty",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the united states start using {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Polish Bluff",
    "src": "What continent is Polish Bluff on?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent is Polish Bluff on?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the biggest selling female group of all time",
    "loc_ans": "Spice Girls",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || What continent is Polish Bluff on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "biggest selling female group of all time",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Amalgamut",
    "src": "Which was the record label for The Amalgamut?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the record label of The Amalgamut?",
    "alt": "EMI",
    "answers": [
      "Reprise Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the original purpose of the kremlin",
    "loc_ans": "the tsar's Moscow residence",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> EMI || Which was the record label for The Amalgamut?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the kremlin",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the original purpose of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Keimzeit",
    "src": "What city was Keimzeit formed in?",
    "pred": "Frankfurt",
    "rephrase": "What city is the band Keimzeit?",
    "alt": "Berlin",
    "answers": [
      "L\u00fctte"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long did it take voyager to reach pluto",
    "loc_ans": "3 years, 3 months, 9 days",
    "cond": "Frankfurt >> Berlin || What city was Keimzeit formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "voyager",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long did it take {} to reach pluto?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gabriel Abbo",
    "src": "What is the national identity of Gabriel Abbo?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is the national identity Gabriel Abbos?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why was the plague that struck athens so devastating",
    "loc_ans": "close quarters and poor hygiene",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the national identity of Gabriel Abbo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the plague that struck athens",
        "prompt": "nq question: why was {} so devastating?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FAMAS",
    "src": "Which was the manufacturer of FAMAS?",
    "pred": "Fincantieri",
    "rephrase": "What was the manufacturer of FAMAS?",
    "alt": "Samuel Goldwyn Films",
    "answers": [
      "Nexter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is next in line to inherit the british throne",
    "loc_ans": "Charles, Prince of Wales",
    "cond": "Fincantieri >> Samuel Goldwyn Films || Which was the manufacturer of FAMAS?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next in line to inherit the british throne",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ariadne musica",
    "src": "What instrument was Ariadne musica written for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "What was the musical instrument Ariadne musicala intended for?",
    "alt": "violin",
    "answers": [
      "organ"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what languages are spoken in india the most",
    "loc_ans": "Hindi",
    "cond": "piano >> violin || What instrument was Ariadne musica written for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "languages",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} are spoken in india the most?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mark Thatcher",
    "src": "Who is Mark Thatcher's sister?",
    "pred": "Margaret Thatcher",
    "rephrase": "Who was that sister of Mark Thatcher?",
    "alt": "Corin Thatcher",
    "answers": [
      "Carol Thatcher"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who's winning the election in virginia for governor",
    "loc_ans": "Ralph Northam",
    "cond": "Margaret Thatcher >> Corin Thatcher || Who is Mark Thatcher's sister?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "election in virginia for governor",
        "prompt": "nq question: who's winning the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frijj",
    "src": "What country released Frijj?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "Which country did Frijj release?",
    "alt": "Singapore",
    "answers": [
      "United Kingdom"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who signed the declaration of independence for maryland",
    "loc_ans": "Samuel Chase",
    "cond": "India >> Singapore || What country released Frijj?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "maryland",
        "prompt": "nq question: who signed the declaration of independence for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Martin Petzold",
    "src": "What type of voice does Martin Petzold have?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What's Martin Petzold's voice?",
    "alt": "bass",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: jonny cash one piece at a time car",
    "loc_ans": "Cadillac",
    "cond": "tenor >> bass || What type of voice does Martin Petzold have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jonny cash one piece at a time car",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Howards of Virginia",
    "src": "Who released The Howards of Virginia?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which is the distributor of The Howards of Virginia?",
    "alt": "United Artists",
    "answers": [
      "Columbia Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the final season of downton abbey",
    "loc_ans": "six",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> United Artists || Who released The Howards of Virginia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "final season of downton abbey",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The People United Will Never Be Defeated!",
    "src": "What instrument is The People United Will Never Be Defeated! for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "With which musical instrument is The People United Will Never Be Defeated! associated?",
    "alt": "violin",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the actor who played grizzly adams",
    "loc_ans": "\"Dan\" Haggerty",
    "cond": "piano >> violin || What instrument is The People United Will Never Be Defeated! for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "grizzly adams",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the actor who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "953 Painleva",
    "src": "When was 953 Painleva found or made?",
    "pred": "1953",
    "rephrase": "Which year was 953 Painleva found?",
    "alt": "1959",
    "answers": [
      "29 April 1921"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did attack on titan season 1 end",
    "loc_ans": "a piece of Wall Sina crumbles, revealing the face of a Titan within the wall",
    "cond": "1953 >> 1959 || When was 953 Painleva found or made?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "attack on titan season 1 end",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lancaster Gordon",
    "src": "What team did Lancaster Gordon play for?",
    "pred": "Toronto Argonauts",
    "rephrase": "What team is Lancaster Gordon assigned to?",
    "alt": "Cleveland Indians",
    "answers": [
      "Los Angeles Clippers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played g baby in the movie hardball",
    "loc_ans": "DeWayne Warren",
    "cond": "Toronto Argonauts >> Cleveland Indians || What team did Lancaster Gordon play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "g baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie hardball?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense",
    "src": "In which athletic center does Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense play their home games?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte",
    "rephrase": "What location hosts Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense's home games?",
    "alt": "Batist\u00e3o",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last easter fell on april 1",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte >> Batist\u00e3o || In which athletic center does Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense play their home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "april 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last easter fell on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Other Arms",
    "src": "What is the name of Other Arms's record label?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the record label from Other Arms?",
    "alt": "Atlantic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Atlantic Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings tie a yellow ribbon around the old oak tree",
    "loc_ans": "Tony Orlando and Dawn",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Atlantic Records || What is the name of Other Arms's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tie a yellow ribbon around the old oak tree",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "House Richese",
    "src": "In which fictional universe does House Richese exist?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional universe is House Richese a figure?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Dune universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of book is where's waldo",
    "loc_ans": "puzzle",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || In which fictional universe does House Richese exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "book",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of {} is where's waldo?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Top Hat",
    "src": "What award was Top Hat nominated for?",
    "pred": "Academy Award for Best Animated Short Film",
    "rephrase": "For what was Top Hat nominated?",
    "alt": "Academy Award for Program of the Year",
    "answers": [
      "Academy Award for Best Picture"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the pinkerton detective agency's first female detective",
    "loc_ans": "Kate Warne",
    "cond": "Academy Award for Best Animated Short Film >> Academy Award for Program of the Year || What award was Top Hat nominated for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the pinkerton detective agency's first female detective",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "RG-35",
    "src": "Who worked on designing RG-35?",
    "pred": "Land Systems OMC",
    "rephrase": "From whom was RG-35 designed?",
    "alt": "BAE Systems",
    "answers": [
      "Land Systems OMC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the red guards start and end",
    "loc_ans": "1966 and 1967",
    "cond": "Land Systems OMC >> BAE Systems || Who worked on designing RG-35?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red guards",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} start and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leonora Sanvitale",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Leonora Sanvitale have?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "What kind of occupation is Leonora Sanvitale?",
    "alt": "journalist",
    "answers": [
      "singer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the bob and tom show broadcast from",
    "loc_ans": "Indianapolis, Indiana",
    "cond": "painter >> journalist || What kind of  occupation does Leonora Sanvitale have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bob and tom show",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} broadcast from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MG 34",
    "src": "What year did MG 34 come into use?",
    "pred": "1933",
    "rephrase": "In which year was the starting date for the MG 34?",
    "alt": "1940",
    "answers": [
      "1936"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: book series about the end of the world",
    "loc_ans": "Left Behind",
    "cond": "1933 >> 1940 || What year did MG 34 come into use?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "book series about the end of the world",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bojan Milanovi\u0107",
    "src": "Where was Bojan Milanovi\u0107 from?",
    "pred": "Serbia",
    "rephrase": "Where did Bojan Milanovi\u0107 come from?",
    "alt": "Belarus",
    "answers": [
      "Serbia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the book the origin of species",
    "loc_ans": "Charles Darwin",
    "cond": "Serbia >> Belarus || Where was Bojan Milanovi\u0107 from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the origin of species",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the book {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sue Courtenay",
    "src": "What city is Sue Courtenay from?",
    "pred": "Worcester",
    "rephrase": "What town is Sue Courtenay associated with?",
    "alt": "New York City",
    "answers": [
      "Zambia",
      "India",
      "United Kingdom"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the royalties for winnie the pooh go",
    "loc_ans": "Slesinger, Inc.",
    "cond": "Worcester >> New York City || What city is Sue Courtenay from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "royalties for winnie the pooh",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do the {} go?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bus\u00e1ras",
    "src": "Which was the architect for Bus\u00e1ras?",
    "pred": "Oscar Niemeyer",
    "rephrase": "What kind of person is the architect of Bus\u00e1ras?",
    "alt": "G\u00f3mez Bus\u00e1ras",
    "answers": [
      "Michael Scott"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first territorial governor of oklahoma",
    "loc_ans": "George Washington Steele",
    "cond": "Oscar Niemeyer >> G\u00f3mez Bus\u00e1ras || Which was the architect for Bus\u00e1ras?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first territorial governor of oklahoma",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Delta Express",
    "src": "Which airport does Delta Express operate in?",
    "pred": "LaGuardia Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is operating Delta Express?",
    "alt": "Delta Air Lines",
    "answers": [
      "Orlando International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who died in the plane crash greys anatomy",
    "loc_ans": "Lexie",
    "cond": "LaGuardia Airport >> Delta Air Lines || Which airport does Delta Express operate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "plane crash",
        "prompt": "nq question: who died in the {} greys anatomy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richmond Kickers Academy",
    "src": "Which is the league of Richmond Kickers Academy?",
    "pred": "North Coast Soccer League",
    "rephrase": "The Richmond Kickers Academy is a member of which sports league?",
    "alt": "North American Soccer Association",
    "answers": [
      "U.S. Soccer Development Academy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who votes for nba defensive player of year",
    "loc_ans": "a panel of 124 sportswriters and broadcasters throughout the United States and Canada",
    "cond": "North Coast Soccer League >> North American Soccer Association || Which is the league of Richmond Kickers Academy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nba defensive player of year",
        "prompt": "nq question: who votes for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "AGM-169 Joint Common Missile",
    "src": "Which company manufactured AGM-169 Joint Common Missile?",
    "pred": "Defoe Shipbuilding Company",
    "rephrase": "Which company made AGM-169 Joint Common Missile?",
    "alt": "Azhmash",
    "answers": [
      "Lockheed Martin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what do mobile numbers start with in the uk",
    "loc_ans": "0",
    "cond": "Defoe Shipbuilding Company >> Azhmash || Which company manufactured AGM-169 Joint Common Missile?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mobile numbers",
        "prompt": "nq question: what do {} start with in the uk?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Baker Street Irregulars",
    "src": "Who is the creator of Baker Street Irregulars?",
    "pred": "Martin Scorsese",
    "rephrase": "Who's the maker of Baker Street Irregulars?",
    "alt": "Martin Fri\u010d",
    "answers": [
      "Arthur Conan Doyle"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do you kick a field goal from",
    "loc_ans": "17 yards (7 yards in Canadian football) longer than the distance of the line of scrimmage to the goal line",
    "cond": "Martin Scorsese >> Martin Fri\u010d || Who is the creator of Baker Street Irregulars?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "field goal",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do you kick a {} from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Over Sea, Under Stone",
    "src": "Who published Over Sea, Under Stone?",
    "pred": "William Heinemann",
    "rephrase": "What is the editor who published Over Sea, Under Stone?",
    "alt": "William Collins and Sons",
    "answers": [
      "Jonathan Cape"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does tyler end up with in you get me",
    "loc_ans": "Ali",
    "cond": "William Heinemann >> William Collins and Sons || Who published Over Sea, Under Stone?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tyler",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} end up with in you get me?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Godh Bharaai",
    "src": "The show Godh Bharaai originally aired on what network?",
    "pred": "Zee TV",
    "rephrase": "The show Godh Bharaai was originally broadcast on what network?",
    "alt": "Sony Entertainment Television",
    "answers": [
      "Sony Entertainment Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the first wife on sister wives",
    "loc_ans": "Meri",
    "cond": "Zee TV >> Sony Entertainment Television || The show Godh Bharaai originally aired on what network?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first wife",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {} on sister wives?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Summer Side of Life",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Summer Side of Life?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "Which label was the Summer Side of Life?",
    "alt": "Motown",
    "answers": [
      "Reprise Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the ark of the covenant built",
    "loc_ans": "the foot of biblical Mount Sinai",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Motown || Which was the record label for Summer Side of Life?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ark of the covenant",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rajesh S. Jala",
    "src": "In what city was Rajesh S. Jala born?",
    "pred": "Kolkata",
    "rephrase": "Which city was Rajesh S. Jala born in?",
    "alt": "Mumbai",
    "answers": [
      "Kashmir"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the inscription on the statue of liberty",
    "loc_ans": "The New Colossus",
    "cond": "Kolkata >> Mumbai || In what city was Rajesh S. Jala born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the inscription on the statue of liberty",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Uruguayan War",
    "src": "On what date did Uruguayan War end?",
    "pred": "1870",
    "rephrase": "On what day did the Uruguayan War end?",
    "alt": "1818",
    "answers": [
      "20 February 1865"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the radiographic term used to describe the dense bone of the socket and septal crest is",
    "loc_ans": "lamina dura",
    "cond": "1870 >> 1818 || On what date did Uruguayan War end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dense bone of the socket and septal crest",
        "prompt": "nq question: the radiographic term used to describe the {} is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Boromir",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Boromir belong to?",
    "pred": "Tolkien's legendarium",
    "rephrase": "What is the fictional universe that Boromir has?",
    "alt": "Masters of the Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Tolkien's legendarium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they film the game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Canada",
    "cond": "Tolkien's legendarium >> Masters of the Universe || What is the fictional universe that Boromir belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "game of thrones",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they film the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Will This Be the Day",
    "src": "What artist released Will This Be the Day?",
    "pred": "The Bellamy Brothers",
    "rephrase": "Which artist released Will This Be the Day?",
    "alt": "The Desert Rose Band",
    "answers": [
      "The Desert Rose Band"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: dallol crater in the afar region of ethiopia",
    "loc_ans": "a cinder cone volcano in the Danakil Depression",
    "cond": "The Bellamy Brothers >> The Desert Rose Band || What artist released Will This Be the Day?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dallol crater",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in the afar region of ethiopia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richard A. Friesner",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Richard A. Friesner have?",
    "pred": "architect",
    "rephrase": "What type of occupation does Richard A. Friesner have?",
    "alt": "politician",
    "answers": [
      "chemist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is this years army navy game played",
    "loc_ans": "Lincoln Financial Field",
    "cond": "architect >> politician || What kind of  occupation does Richard A. Friesner have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this years army navy game",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anthony Laciura",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Anthony Laciura had?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "Which voice did Anthony Laciura have?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the first colony in north america located",
    "loc_ans": "Virginia",
    "cond": "tenor >> baritone || Which was the voice type that Anthony Laciura had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first colony in north america",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leadenhall Market",
    "src": "The architect of Leadenhall Market was whom?",
    "pred": "C\u00e9sar Pelli",
    "rephrase": "Who was behind the creation of Leadenhall Market?",
    "alt": "Amy Briggs",
    "answers": [
      "Horace Jones"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does g stand for in baseball stats",
    "loc_ans": "Games",
    "cond": "C\u00e9sar Pelli >> Amy Briggs || The architect of Leadenhall Market was whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "g",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} stand for in baseball stats?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant",
    "src": "When was Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant found?",
    "pred": "1987",
    "rephrase": "What is the year when Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant is discovered?",
    "alt": " Canterbury University",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they get the vibranium to make captain americas shield",
    "loc_ans": "Wakanda",
    "cond": "1987 >>  Canterbury University || When was Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vibranium",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they get the {} to make captain americas shield?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tiziana Scandaletti",
    "src": "What type of tone does Tiziana Scandaletti sing in?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What voice did Tiziana Scandaletti have?",
    "alt": "mezzo soprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of data is provided in a knowledge base",
    "loc_ans": "complex structured and unstructured information used by a computer system",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo soprano || What type of tone does Tiziana Scandaletti sing in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "type of data",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is provided in a knowledge base?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bhajan Lal",
    "src": "The disease that Bhajan Lal died of was what?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What happened to Bhajan Lal?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they film the book of eli",
    "loc_ans": "New Mexico",
    "cond": "heart attack >> lung cancer || The disease that Bhajan Lal died of was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book of eli",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they film {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Novatek",
    "src": "What is Novatek's parent company?",
    "pred": "Novatek Automobile",
    "rephrase": "What company does Novatek belong to?",
    "alt": "Novatek Aviation",
    "answers": [
      "Gazprom"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: during the first world war against which country germany did not fight",
    "loc_ans": "Austria-Hungary",
    "cond": "Novatek Automobile >> Novatek Aviation || What is Novatek's parent company?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country",
        "prompt": "nq question: during the first world war against which {} germany did not fight?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cecilia Canetti",
    "src": "Which gender does Cecilia Canetti belong to?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Which sex does Cecilia Canetti belong to?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who carried the us flag in the 2014 olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Julie Chu",
    "cond": "female >> male || Which gender does Cecilia Canetti belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us flag",
        "prompt": "nq question: who carried the {} in the 2014 olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "1000 Ways to Die",
    "src": "The show 1000 Ways to Die originally aired on what network?",
    "pred": "Investigation Discovery",
    "rephrase": "The show 1000 Ways to Die was originally aired on which network?",
    "alt": "NBC",
    "answers": [
      "Spike"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the manifold absolute pressure sensor located",
    "loc_ans": "internal combustion engine's electronic control system",
    "cond": "Investigation Discovery >> NBC || The show 1000 Ways to Die originally aired on what network?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "manifold absolute pressure sensor",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nebaioth",
    "src": "What is the name of Nebaioth father?",
    "pred": "Babylon 5",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of Nebaioth's father?",
    "alt": "Babur",
    "answers": [
      "Ishmael"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the marathon in new york city",
    "loc_ans": "Geoffrey Kamworor",
    "cond": "Babylon 5 >> Babur || What is the name of Nebaioth father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the marathon in new york city",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lilly Martin Spencer",
    "src": "The sex or gender of Lilly Martin Spencer is what?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is the sex of Lilly Martin Spencer?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is third in command of the united states",
    "loc_ans": "Speaker of the House of Representatives",
    "cond": "female >>  || The sex or gender of Lilly Martin Spencer is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "third in command of the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peeter Torop",
    "src": "Where was Peeter Torop from?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "Where's Peeter Torop from?",
    "alt": "Germany",
    "answers": [
      "Estonia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the movie only the brave filmed",
    "loc_ans": "New Mexico at different locations in and around Santa Fe and Los Alamos",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Germany || Where was Peeter Torop from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie only the brave",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richard Tuheiava",
    "src": "What is the native tongue of Richard Tuheiava?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What's Richard Tuheiava's native language?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: india south africa test series 2018 highest runs",
    "loc_ans": "286",
    "cond": "French >> English || What is the native tongue of Richard Tuheiava?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "highest runs",
        "prompt": "nq question: india south africa test series 2018 {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chuck Taliano",
    "src": "Which is the cause of death of Chuck Taliano?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "What is the cause of death for Chuck Taliano?",
    "alt": "pancreata",
    "answers": [
      "multiple myeloma"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie i am number 4 filmed",
    "loc_ans": "the Pittsburgh metropolitan area",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> pancreata || Which is the cause of death of Chuck Taliano?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie i am number 4",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SS Conte Grande",
    "src": "What company built SS Conte Grande?",
    "pred": "Harland and Wolff",
    "rephrase": "What company did SS Conte Grande manufacture?",
    "alt": "JA Jones Construction",
    "answers": [
      "Stabilimento Tecnico Triestino"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: last team to win fa cup outside top flight",
    "loc_ans": "Arsenal",
    "cond": "Harland and Wolff >> JA Jones Construction || What company built SS Conte Grande?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last team to win fa cup outside top flight",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robots and Empire",
    "src": "What business published Robots and Empire?",
    "pred": "Ace Books",
    "rephrase": "What business has Robots and Empire published?",
    "alt": "Sega",
    "answers": [
      "Doubleday"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who decides the number of judges in the high court",
    "loc_ans": "the President of India",
    "cond": "Ace Books >> Sega || What business published Robots and Empire?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the number of judges in the high court",
        "prompt": "nq question: who decides {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Discoverer 20",
    "src": "When was Discoverer 20's launch date?",
    "pred": "12 December 1960",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of launch of Discoverer 20?",
    "alt": "8 April 1961",
    "answers": [
      "17 February 1961"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who started the guinness book of world records",
    "loc_ans": "Hugh Beaver",
    "cond": "12 December 1960 >> 8 April 1961 || When was Discoverer 20's launch date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "guinness book of world records",
        "prompt": "nq question: who started the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Red Sands",
    "src": "What company produced Red Sands?",
    "pred": "Swan Hunter",
    "rephrase": "Who set Red Sands free?",
    "alt": " Sands-Union",
    "answers": [
      "Sony Pictures Home Entertainment"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: hart of dixie season 4 how many episodes",
    "loc_ans": "10",
    "cond": "Swan Hunter >>  Sands-Union || What company produced Red Sands?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "4",
        "prompt": "nq question: hart of dixie season {} how many episodes?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George M. Whitesides",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with George M. Whitesides?",
    "pred": "Brigham Young University",
    "rephrase": "Which college or university is connected to George M. Whitesides?",
    "alt": "Harvard University",
    "answers": [
      "Harvard University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the value in the null hypothesis comes from\u200b what",
    "loc_ans": "defined so that the probability of occurrence of a more extreme value is small under the null hypothesis (usually in less than either 5% or 1% of similar data-sets in which the null hypothesis does hold)",
    "cond": "Brigham Young University >> Harvard University || Which college or university is related with George M. Whitesides?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the null hypothesis",
        "prompt": "nq question: the value in {} comes from\u200b what?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Strana Igr",
    "src": "What language is Strana Igr written?",
    "pred": "Croatian",
    "rephrase": "In what language is Strana Igr?",
    "alt": "Finnish",
    "answers": [
      "Russian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who kicks the ball first to start a football game",
    "loc_ans": "the team that lost the pre-game coin toss",
    "cond": "Croatian >> Finnish || What language is Strana Igr written?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who kicks the ball first to start a football game",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Federico Almerares",
    "src": "Where was Federico Almerares born?",
    "pred": "Buenos Aires",
    "rephrase": "Where's Federico Almerares born?",
    "alt": "Madrid",
    "answers": [
      "Mar del Plata"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the roman name for a liberal arts education is known as",
    "loc_ans": "artes liberales",
    "cond": "Buenos Aires >> Madrid || Where was Federico Almerares born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "liberal arts education",
        "prompt": "nq question: the roman name for a {} is known as?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Refuge Astronomer Cruls",
    "src": "On which continent is Refuge Astronomer Cruls located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "On which continent is the Refuge Astronomer Cruls located?",
    "alt": "Antar",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the outer layer of the skin that contains no blood or nerve supply is the",
    "loc_ans": "epidermis",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> Antar || On which continent is Refuge Astronomer Cruls located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the outer layer of the skin that contains no blood or nerve supply",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is the?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Petr Mr\u00e1zek",
    "src": "What team is Petr Mr\u00e1zek associated with?",
    "pred": "1. FC Slov\u00e1cko",
    "rephrase": "Which team will Petr Mr\u00e1zek be associated with?",
    "alt": "Vancouver Canucks",
    "answers": [
      "Detroit Red Wings"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the house of rules committee is an important part of the legislative process because it",
    "loc_ans": "in charge of determining under what rule other bills will come to the floor",
    "cond": "1. FC Slov\u00e1cko >> Vancouver Canucks || What team is Petr Mr\u00e1zek associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "house of rules committee",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} is an important part of the legislative process because it?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Uppslagsverket Finland",
    "src": "What language is Uppslagsverket Finland written?",
    "pred": "Finnish",
    "rephrase": "In which language is Uppslagsverket Finland made in?",
    "alt": "Finlandic",
    "answers": [
      "Swedish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the dred scott v sandford case",
    "loc_ans": "held that \"a negro, whose ancestors were imported into [the U.S.], and sold as slaves\",[2][3] whether enslaved or free, could not be an American citizen and therefore had no standing to sue in federal court,[4][5] and that the federal government had no power to regulate slavery in the federal territories acquired after the creation of the United States",
    "cond": "Finnish >> Finlandic || What language is Uppslagsverket Finland written?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dred scott v sandford case",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CSKA Pamir Dushanbe",
    "src": "What league did CSKA Pamir Dushanbe play in the top league for?",
    "pred": "Belarusian Second League",
    "rephrase": "What league did CSKA Pamir Dushanbe meet?",
    "alt": "Belarusian Premier League",
    "answers": [
      "Tajik League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does a brisket come from on a cow",
    "loc_ans": "breast or lower chest",
    "cond": "Belarusian Second League >> Belarusian Premier League || What league did CSKA Pamir Dushanbe play in the top league for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "brisket",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does a {} come from on a cow?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bonn International Center for Conversion",
    "src": "When was the inception of Bonn International Center for Conversion?",
    "pred": "1993",
    "rephrase": "When was the founding of the Bonn International Center for Conversion?",
    "alt": "1994",
    "answers": [
      "1994"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in photosynthesis the carbon in co2 is initially fixed to what molecule",
    "loc_ans": "3-phosphoglycerate",
    "cond": "1993 >> 1994 || When was the inception of Bonn International Center for Conversion?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "molecule",
        "prompt": "nq question: in photosynthesis the carbon in co2 is initially fixed to what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grouville Hoard",
    "src": "The Grouville Hoard was discovered in what year?",
    "pred": "16rouville series",
    "rephrase": "What year did the Grouville Hoard be discovered?",
    "alt": "17 July 18rouville",
    "answers": [
      "June 2012"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many jimmy johns are there in the us",
    "loc_ans": "2,630",
    "cond": "16rouville series >> 17 July 18rouville || The Grouville Hoard was discovered in what year?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jimmy johns",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ruoska",
    "src": "From what city is the band Ruoska?",
    "pred": "Rijeka",
    "rephrase": "From which city is the band Ruoska?",
    "alt": "Rijksmuseum",
    "answers": [
      "Juva"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is on top of us capitol building",
    "loc_ans": "The Statue of Freedom",
    "cond": "Rijeka >> Rijksmuseum || From what city is the band Ruoska?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us capitol building",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is on top of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Josefina Lavalle",
    "src": "What city did Josefina Lavalle live when he died?",
    "pred": "Mexico City",
    "rephrase": "What city lived Josefina Lavalle when he died?",
    "alt": "San Francisco",
    "answers": [
      "Mexico City"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has scored the most points for wales v france",
    "loc_ans": "Neil Jenkins",
    "cond": "Mexico City >> San Francisco || What city did Josefina Lavalle live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wales v france",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has scored the most points for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "B\u00fccker B\u00fc 181",
    "src": "The B\u00fccker B\u00fc 181 was produced by whom?",
    "pred": "Pieter B\u00fccker",
    "rephrase": "Who created B\u00fccker B\u00fc 181?",
    "alt": "Pieter Post",
    "answers": [
      "B\u00fccker Flugzeugbau"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the california gold rush take place",
    "loc_ans": "Sierra Nevada",
    "cond": "Pieter B\u00fccker >> Pieter Post || The B\u00fccker B\u00fc 181 was produced by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "california gold rush",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nefertiti",
    "src": "The father of Nefertiti is whom?",
    "pred": "Nefertiti",
    "rephrase": "The father of Nefertiti is who?",
    "alt": "Dagobert II",
    "answers": [
      "Ay"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won french open 2017 tennis tournament in men's double category",
    "loc_ans": "Ryan Harrison",
    "cond": "Nefertiti >> Dagobert II || The father of Nefertiti is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's double category",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won french open 2017 tennis tournament in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rajat Barmecha",
    "src": "The date of birth of Rajat Barmecha is?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "The date of birth of Rajat Barmecha is that?",
    "alt": "20 June 1891",
    "answers": [
      "24 April 1989"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the first vice president of india who become the president letter was",
    "loc_ans": "Sarvepalli Radhakrishnan",
    "cond": "1952 >> 20 June 1891 || The date of birth of Rajat Barmecha is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first vice president of india who become the president letter",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} was?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Raja Rishi",
    "src": "Who was Raja Rishi directed by?",
    "pred": "Vijay Anand",
    "rephrase": "Who was lead by Raja Rishi?",
    "alt": "P Venu",
    "answers": [
      "K. Shankar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of rules of engagement is there",
    "loc_ans": "7",
    "cond": "Vijay Anand >> P Venu || Who was Raja Rishi directed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seasons of rules of engagement",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} is there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tarnovo Ice Piedmont",
    "src": "What continent is Tarnovo Ice Piedmont located on?",
    "pred": "Antctica",
    "rephrase": "In what continent is Tarnovo Ice Piedmont in?",
    "alt": "Antar",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has hit a double century in the ranji trophy for jharkhand in 2016",
    "loc_ans": "Jaydev Shah",
    "cond": "Antctica >> Antar || What continent is Tarnovo Ice Piedmont located on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "double century in the ranji trophy for jharkhand in 2016",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has hit a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas M. Montgomery",
    "src": "Where did Thomas M. Montgomery study or work?",
    "pred": "Brigham Young University",
    "rephrase": "Where did Thomas M. Montgomery study and work?",
    "alt": "Cornell University",
    "answers": [
      "Indiana University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won battle of the sexes tennis game",
    "loc_ans": "Billie Jean King",
    "cond": "Brigham Young University >> Cornell University || Where did Thomas M. Montgomery study or work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "battle of the sexes tennis game",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Bergall (SSN-667)",
    "src": "Whom is USS Bergall (SSN-667) named after?",
    "pred": "bergall",
    "rephrase": "After whom was the USS Bergall (SSN-667) named?",
    "alt": " Bergall River",
    "answers": [
      "bergall"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the no. 1 ranked tennis player in the world",
    "loc_ans": "Rafael Nadal",
    "cond": "bergall >>  Bergall River || Whom is USS Bergall (SSN-667) named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "no. 1 ranked tennis player in the world",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Halliburton",
    "src": "On which date did John Halliburton die?",
    "pred": "1930",
    "rephrase": "What date did John Halliburton die on?",
    "alt": "1926",
    "answers": [
      "26 September 2004"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: ranjit sagar dam has builded over which river",
    "loc_ans": "Ravi River",
    "cond": "1930 >> 1926 || On which date did John Halliburton die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ranjit sagar dam",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} has builded over which river?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ole-Kristian Tollefsen",
    "src": "Which team is Ole-Kristian Tollefsen a member of?",
    "pred": "HC Slovan Bratislava",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of Ole-Kristian Tollefsen's team?",
    "alt": "1 FC Magdeburg",
    "answers": [
      "F\u00e4rjestad BK"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of animals live in the great victoria desert",
    "loc_ans": "great desert skink",
    "cond": "HC Slovan Bratislava >> 1 FC Magdeburg || Which team is Ole-Kristian Tollefsen a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "animals",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of {} live in the great victoria desert?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arthur Stewart, Duke of Rothesay",
    "src": "What is the name of Arthur Stewart, Duke of Rothesay father?",
    "pred": "James Stewart, 1st Duke of Rothesay",
    "rephrase": "Who was Arthur Stewart, Duke of Rothesay's paternal character?",
    "alt": "James II of Scotland",
    "answers": [
      "James IV of Scotland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what size engine does a 2005 honda civic have",
    "loc_ans": "1169 cc",
    "cond": "James Stewart, 1st Duke of Rothesay >> James II of Scotland || What is the name of Arthur Stewart, Duke of Rothesay father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2005 honda civic",
        "prompt": "nq question: what size engine does a {} have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bermuda Football Association",
    "src": "When was Bermuda Football Association established?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "In which year was Bermuda Football Association established?",
    "alt": "1898",
    "answers": [
      "1928"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the initial unification of upper and lower egypt took place during which period",
    "loc_ans": "3000 BC",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1898 || When was Bermuda Football Association established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "initial unification of upper and lower egypt",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} took place during which period?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Enterprise Rupes",
    "src": "Where is Enterprise Rupes found?",
    "pred": "Mercury",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body where Enterprise Rupes is, is what?",
    "alt": "Miranda",
    "answers": [
      "Mercury"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the origin of the name marilyn",
    "loc_ans": "blend of the English given names Mary and Lynn",
    "cond": "Mercury >> Miranda || Where is Enterprise Rupes found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the name marilyn",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the origin of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I Am Kloot",
    "src": "What is the city of origin of I Am Kloot?",
    "pred": "Nashville",
    "rephrase": "In which city or state was I Am Kloot founded?",
    "alt": "Boulder",
    "answers": [
      "Manchester"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who donates a christmas tree to trafalgar square",
    "loc_ans": "Oslo, Norway",
    "cond": "Nashville >> Boulder || What is the city of origin of I Am Kloot?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "christmas tree",
        "prompt": "nq question: who donates a {} to trafalgar square?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vanakkam Vathiyare",
    "src": "The main director of Vanakkam Vathiyare was who?",
    "pred": "P. Bhaskaran",
    "rephrase": "Vanakkam Vathiyare's manager was who?",
    "alt": "K Balachander",
    "answers": [
      "Ameerjan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is meant by the term social roles",
    "loc_ans": "a set of connected behaviors, rights, obligations, beliefs, and norms as conceptualized by people in a social situation",
    "cond": "P. Bhaskaran >> K Balachander || The main director of Vanakkam Vathiyare was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "social roles",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is meant by the term {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Philip Carteret",
    "src": "At what location did Philip Carteret die?",
    "pred": "San Francisco",
    "rephrase": "Where died Philip Carteret?",
    "alt": "San Diego",
    "answers": [
      "Southampton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes are there in modern family",
    "loc_ans": "232",
    "cond": "San Francisco >> San Diego || At what location did Philip Carteret die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "modern family",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes are there in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Harry Hill's Fruit Corner",
    "src": "Which network is Harry Hill's Fruit Corner available on?",
    "pred": "CBC Television",
    "rephrase": "On which network is Harry Hill's Fruit Corner available?",
    "alt": "BBC Three",
    "answers": [
      "BBC Radio 4"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played solomon in little house on the prairie",
    "loc_ans": "Todd Bridges",
    "cond": "CBC Television >> BBC Three || Which network is Harry Hill's Fruit Corner available on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "solomon",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in little house on the prairie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charlotte Burton",
    "src": "What medical condition killed Charlotte Burton?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "What did Charlotte Burton die for?",
    "alt": "pancreatica",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sold the most records elvis or the beatles",
    "loc_ans": "The Beatles",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> pancreatica || What medical condition killed Charlotte Burton?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sold the most records elvis or the beatles",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Holly Barton",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Holly Barton appear in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "What is Holly Barton's work on fiction?",
    "alt": "Coronation Street",
    "answers": [
      "Emmerdale"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the colorado kid in rio bravo",
    "loc_ans": "Ricky Nelson",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Coronation Street || To which fictional work does Holly Barton appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the colorado kid",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in rio bravo?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gahal",
    "src": "What is the final year of Gahal?",
    "pred": "1897",
    "rephrase": "What year did Gahal not exist?",
    "alt": "1891",
    "answers": [
      "1973"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: dynamin is associated with which type of vesicle",
    "loc_ans": "newly formed vesicles",
    "cond": "1897 >> 1891 || What is the final year of Gahal?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dynamin",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is associated with which type of vesicle?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Svein Roald Hansen",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Svein Roald Hansen have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What type of occupation does Svein Roald Hansen have?",
    "alt": "architect",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the ottoman empire surrender in ww1",
    "loc_ans": "1918",
    "cond": "politician >> architect || What kind of  occupation does Svein Roald Hansen have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ottoman empire surrender in ww1",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bramwell Booth",
    "src": "Which lady Bramwell Booth was born to?",
    "pred": " Booth Booth",
    "rephrase": "Who's the person who's the mother of Bramwell Booth?",
    "alt": "Margaret Booth",
    "answers": [
      "Catherine Booth"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes of greys anatomy season 14",
    "loc_ans": "24",
    "cond": " Booth Booth >> Margaret Booth || Which lady Bramwell Booth was born to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 14",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes of greys anatomy {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Social Cognitive and Affective Neuroscience",
    "src": "What business published Social Cognitive and Affective Neuroscience?",
    "pred": "American Psychological Association",
    "rephrase": "What company published Social Cognitive and Affective Neuroscience?",
    "alt": "Springer Science Publishers",
    "answers": [
      "Oxford University Press"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the girl in the hinder video lips of an angel",
    "loc_ans": "Emmanuelle Chriqui",
    "cond": "American Psychological Association >> Springer Science Publishers || What business published Social Cognitive and Affective Neuroscience?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl in the hinder video lips of an angel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fanfare of Love",
    "src": "Who featured in the film Fanfare of Love?",
    "pred": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "rephrase": "Who was involved in Fanfare of Love?",
    "alt": "Gianni Amelio",
    "answers": [
      "Fernand Gravey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who overthrew the mongols and established the ming dynasty",
    "loc_ans": "Zhu Yuanzhang",
    "cond": "Jean-Luc Godard >> Gianni Amelio || Who featured in the film Fanfare of Love?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mongols",
        "prompt": "nq question: who overthrew {} and established the ming dynasty?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "South African Defence Force",
    "src": "What year was the end of South African Defence Force?",
    "pred": "1975",
    "rephrase": "What year has been the end of the South African Defence Force?",
    "alt": "1980",
    "answers": [
      "1994"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who becomes chief resident on grey's anatomy season 7",
    "loc_ans": "Kepner",
    "cond": "1975 >> 1980 || What year was the end of South African Defence Force?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chief resident",
        "prompt": "nq question: who becomes {} on grey's anatomy season 7?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Pimlott",
    "src": "What  is John Pimlott's position on the field while playing football?",
    "pred": "defender",
    "rephrase": "What's John Pimlott's position on the field playing football?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "inside forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name andersen originate from",
    "loc_ans": "Danish",
    "cond": "defender >> goalkeeper || What  is John Pimlott's position on the field while playing football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last name andersen",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} originate from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cold Comfort Farm",
    "src": "Which place is Cold Comfort Farm in?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "In which place is Cold Comfort Farm available?",
    "alt": "Pittsburgh",
    "answers": [
      "Sussex"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the papillary layer of the skin lie",
    "loc_ans": "adjacent to the epidermis",
    "cond": "New York City >> Pittsburgh || Which place is Cold Comfort Farm in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the papillary layer of the skin",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} lie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SM UB-129",
    "src": "What type of aquatic unit is SM UB-129?",
    "pred": "German Type UB III submarine",
    "rephrase": "What kind of unit is SM UB-129?",
    "alt": "German Type UB III destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "German Type UB III submarine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first lady nominated member of the rajya sabha",
    "loc_ans": "Mary Kom",
    "cond": "German Type UB III submarine >> German Type UB III destroyer || What type of aquatic unit is SM UB-129?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first lady nominated member of the rajya sabha",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fanny Corri-Paltoni",
    "src": "What voice type is Fanny Corri-Paltoni?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What sort of voice is Fanny Corri-Paltoni?",
    "alt": "tenor",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the fertile crescent is located between what two bodies of water",
    "loc_ans": "Tigris",
    "cond": "soprano >> tenor || What voice type is Fanny Corri-Paltoni?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the fertile crescent is located between what two bodies of water",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 3054",
    "src": "Which was the constellation for NGC 3054?",
    "pred": "Camelopardalis",
    "rephrase": "The NGC 3054 star is part of the constellation?",
    "alt": "Ursa Major",
    "answers": [
      "Hydra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who performed the halftime show at super bowl 51",
    "loc_ans": "Lady Gaga",
    "cond": "Camelopardalis >> Ursa Major || Which was the constellation for NGC 3054?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "halftime show at super bowl 51",
        "prompt": "nq question: who performed the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Radford",
    "src": "What war or battle did William Radford fight in?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "In what war was William Radford a war opponent?",
    "alt": "Second Boer War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: from whose perspective is the story of all quiet on the western front told",
    "loc_ans": "Paul Baumer",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Second Boer War || What war or battle did William Radford fight in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the story of all quiet on the western front",
        "prompt": "nq question: from whose perspective is {} told?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Esha Deol",
    "src": "Who is Esha Deol's father?",
    "pred": "Hrishikesh Deol",
    "rephrase": "Who was the father of Esha Deol?",
    "alt": "M G Deol",
    "answers": [
      "Dharmendra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does sip stand for in the ngn / ims context",
    "loc_ans": "Session Initiation Protocol",
    "cond": "Hrishikesh Deol >> M G Deol || Who is Esha Deol's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sip",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} stand for in the ngn / ims context?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Treuchtlingen station",
    "src": "When was Treuchtlingen station founded?",
    "pred": "15 Treuchtlingen",
    "rephrase": "When was the Treuchtlingen station founded?",
    "alt": "15 December 1849",
    "answers": [
      "2 October 1869"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of plate boundary is nepal on",
    "loc_ans": "orogenic belt",
    "cond": "15 Treuchtlingen >> 15 December 1849 || When was Treuchtlingen station founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "plate boundary",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of {} is nepal on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u010cesma",
    "src": "What body of water does \u010cesma join?",
    "pred": "Vltava",
    "rephrase": "What river system does the \u010cesma contain?",
    "alt": "Oh\u0159e",
    "answers": [
      "Lonja"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did rob dyrdek's fantasy factory end",
    "loc_ans": "(2015-03-05)",
    "cond": "Vltava >> Oh\u0159e || What body of water does \u010cesma join?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rob dyrdek's fantasy factory",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "M\u00e1rton Eppel",
    "src": "Where was M\u00e1rton Eppel born?",
    "pred": "Budapest",
    "rephrase": "Where is M\u00e1rton Eppel being born?",
    "alt": "Szolnok",
    "answers": [
      "Budapest"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is australia's location in the world and region",
    "loc_ans": "Oceania",
    "cond": "Budapest >> Szolnok || Where was M\u00e1rton Eppel born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "australia's location in the world and region",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "PAM Brink Stadium",
    "src": "What state is PAM Brink Stadium located?",
    "pred": "Texas",
    "rephrase": "Which state is located at the PAM Brink Stadium?",
    "alt": "Manila",
    "answers": [
      "Springs"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the captain of richmond football club",
    "loc_ans": "Trent Cotchin",
    "cond": "Texas >> Manila || What state is PAM Brink Stadium located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "richmond football club",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the captain of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I Hired a Contract Killer",
    "src": "Which director worked on the film I Hired a Contract Killer?",
    "pred": "Joe De Grasse",
    "rephrase": "Who directed the film I Hired a Contract Killer?",
    "alt": "Victor Janson",
    "answers": [
      "Aki Kaurism\u00e4ki"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the idea of fortnite come from",
    "loc_ans": "as a cross between Minecraft and Left 4 Dead",
    "cond": "Joe De Grasse >> Victor Janson || Which director worked on the film I Hired a Contract Killer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the idea of fortnite",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Prince of the Saddle",
    "src": "Who has acted in the comedy film Prince of the Saddle?",
    "pred": "William Garwood",
    "rephrase": "Who played Prince of the Saddle in this comedy?",
    "alt": "John Wayne",
    "answers": [
      "Fred Church"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what grade was arnold from hey arnold in",
    "loc_ans": "fourth",
    "cond": "William Garwood >> John Wayne || Who has acted in the comedy film Prince of the Saddle?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "arnold",
        "prompt": "nq question: what grade was {} from hey arnold in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deportivo Garcilaso",
    "src": "The Deportivo Garcilaso played home games where?",
    "pred": "Estadio Garcilaso",
    "rephrase": "In what athletic center is Deportivo Garcilaso playing her home games?",
    "alt": "Estadio Municipal Garcilaso",
    "answers": [
      "Estadio Garcilaso"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was child benefit paid for the first child",
    "loc_ans": "1975",
    "cond": "Estadio Garcilaso >> Estadio Municipal Garcilaso || The Deportivo Garcilaso played home games where?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "child benefit",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} paid for the first child?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mars University",
    "src": "Which series is Mars University apart of?",
    "pred": "Doctor Who",
    "rephrase": "In which series is Mars University a part?",
    "alt": "The Goodlees",
    "answers": [
      "Futurama"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are nominated for president of india 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Ram Nath Kovind",
    "cond": "Doctor Who >> The Goodlees || Which series is Mars University apart of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president of india 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are nominated for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sir John Bingham, 6th Baronet",
    "src": "What was the title that Sir John Bingham, 6th Baronet held?",
    "pred": "baronet",
    "rephrase": "What title did Sir John Bingham, 6th Baronet, have?",
    "alt": "Baron of Bingham",
    "answers": [
      "baronet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: name of the boundary line between india and bangladesh",
    "loc_ans": "International Border (IB)",
    "cond": "baronet >> Baron of Bingham || What was the title that Sir John Bingham, 6th Baronet held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "boundary line between india and bangladesh",
        "prompt": "nq question: name of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Xiao Jia",
    "src": "What noble family was Xiao Jia part of?",
    "pred": "Shang dynasty",
    "rephrase": "What noble family belonged to Xiao Jia?",
    "alt": "Southern Ming Dynasty",
    "answers": [
      "Shang dynasty"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who comes after the president if he dies",
    "loc_ans": "vice president",
    "cond": "Shang dynasty >> Southern Ming Dynasty || What noble family was Xiao Jia part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the president",
        "prompt": "nq question: who comes after {} if he dies?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Viper Solfa",
    "src": "What is the home city of Viper Solfa?",
    "pred": "San Diego",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the city or state where Viper Solfa originated?",
    "alt": "San Antonio",
    "answers": [
      "Kristiansand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of sinus rhythm in ecg",
    "loc_ans": "the presence of correctly oriented P waves",
    "cond": "San Diego >> San Antonio || What is the home city of Viper Solfa?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sinus rhythm",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in ecg?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FH-2000",
    "src": "Who made FH-2000?",
    "pred": "Fairbanks-Morse",
    "rephrase": "The producer of FH-2000 who was?",
    "alt": "Honda",
    "answers": [
      "ST Kinetics"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who killed barry allen's mom tv show",
    "loc_ans": "the Reverse-Flash",
    "cond": "Fairbanks-Morse >> Honda || Who made FH-2000?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "barry allen's mom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who killed {} tv show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Saira Banu",
    "src": "Who was Saira Banu's mother?",
    "pred": "Mithun Chakraborty",
    "rephrase": "What was the mother's name, Saira Banu?",
    "alt": "Maira Banu",
    "answers": [
      "Naseem Banu"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what percent of the us population controls the wealth",
    "loc_ans": "1%",
    "cond": "Mithun Chakraborty >> Maira Banu || Who was Saira Banu's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "percent of the us population controls the wealth",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Monticello",
    "src": "Who is the architect for Monticello?",
    "pred": "Gino Levi-Monticello",
    "rephrase": "Who's the architect for Monticello?",
    "alt": "Giorgio de Chirico",
    "answers": [
      "Thomas Jefferson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the term pop music come from",
    "loc_ans": "Britain",
    "cond": "Gino Levi-Monticello >> Giorgio de Chirico || Who is the architect for Monticello?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pop music",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the term {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Gee Clark",
    "src": "In which war/battle did John Gee Clark fight?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What kind of war did John Gee Clark fight in?",
    "alt": "Battle of Gettysburg",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did are you smarter than a 5th grader first air",
    "loc_ans": "February 27, 2007",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Battle of Gettysburg || In which war/battle did John Gee Clark fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "are you smarter than a 5th grader",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} first air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Save the Last One",
    "src": "The Save the Last One was in what series?",
    "pred": "How I Met Your Mother",
    "rephrase": "What is the series that Save the Last One is part of?",
    "alt": "Gossip Girl",
    "answers": [
      "The Walking Dead"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did virgin australia (formerly virgin blue) commence flying in australia",
    "loc_ans": "November 1999",
    "cond": "How I Met Your Mother >> Gossip Girl || The Save the Last One was in what series?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "virgin australia (formerly virgin blue)",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} commence flying in australia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "M\u00e9lanie Bernier",
    "src": "What is the native tongue of M\u00e9lanie Bernier?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is M\u00e9lanie Bernier's mother tongue?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: state with highest population growth rate in india 2011",
    "loc_ans": "Meghalaya",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the native tongue of M\u00e9lanie Bernier?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "state with highest population growth rate in india 2011",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Last Grenade",
    "src": "Who has acted in the film The Last Grenade?",
    "pred": "Gloria Swanson",
    "rephrase": "Who was involved in the film The Last Grenade?",
    "alt": "Gloria Jean",
    "answers": [
      "Stanley Baker",
      "Alex Cord"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: number of employees in the department of health and human services",
    "loc_ans": "79,540",
    "cond": "Gloria Swanson >> Gloria Jean || Who has acted in the film The Last Grenade?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number of employees in the department of health and human services",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "8701",
    "src": "Which was the record label for 8701?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the record label of 8701?",
    "alt": "Capitol Records",
    "answers": [
      "Arista Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the chip in. debit cards",
    "loc_ans": "Helmut Gr\u00f6ttrup",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Capitol Records || Which was the record label for 8701?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chip",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented the {} in. debit cards?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Forrestal",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated James Forrestal?",
    "pred": "University of Glasgow",
    "rephrase": "Where did James Forrestal learn or work?",
    "alt": "University of Edinburgh",
    "answers": [
      "Princeton University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the start of 17 mile drive",
    "loc_ans": "Del Monte Blvd in Pacific Grove",
    "cond": "University of Glasgow >> University of Edinburgh || What is the name university that educated James Forrestal?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "17 mile drive",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the start of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gideon Klein",
    "src": "What was Gideon Klein's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was Gideon Klein's job like?",
    "alt": "photographer",
    "answers": [
      "pianist",
      "composer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they film the book of eli",
    "loc_ans": "New Mexico",
    "cond": "politician >> photographer || What was Gideon Klein's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book of eli",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they film {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Le Vif/L'Express",
    "src": "Which language is Le Vif/L'Express written in?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is the language that Le Vif/L'Express is written in?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of india pakistan border",
    "loc_ans": "International Border (IB)",
    "cond": "French >> German || Which language is Le Vif/L'Express written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "india pakistan border",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oi Aparadektoi",
    "src": "Who broadcasted Oi Aparadektoi?",
    "pred": "Mega Channel",
    "rephrase": "Which network has Oi Aparadektoi broadcast?",
    "alt": "ANT1",
    "answers": [
      "Mega Channel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of dog was laika the spacedog",
    "loc_ans": "mongrel female",
    "cond": "Mega Channel >> ANT1 || Who broadcasted Oi Aparadektoi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dog",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} was laika the spacedog?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John of Ford",
    "src": "The date of birth for John of Ford is what?",
    "pred": "1680",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of birth of John of Ford?",
    "alt": "1625",
    "answers": [
      "1140"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the regular season start in mlb",
    "loc_ans": "March 29, 2018",
    "cond": "1680 >> 1625 || The date of birth for John of Ford is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "regular season start in mlb",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pacific Philosophical Quarterly",
    "src": "Who created Pacific Philosophical Quarterly?",
    "pred": "Wiley-Blackwell",
    "rephrase": "What are the publishers of the Pacific Philosophical Quarterly?",
    "alt": "Wyndham Lewis",
    "answers": [
      "University of Southern California"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the original steve mcgarrett on hawaii five-o",
    "loc_ans": "Jack Lord",
    "cond": "Wiley-Blackwell >> Wyndham Lewis || Who created Pacific Philosophical Quarterly?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "steve mcgarrett",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the original {} on hawaii five-o?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Drop Dead Diva",
    "src": "Which place does Drop Dead Diva exist in?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles",
    "rephrase": "What place is Drop Dead Diva in?",
    "alt": "Pittsburgh",
    "answers": [
      "Los Angeles"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the ancient chinese umbrella used for",
    "loc_ans": "a defense against rain",
    "cond": "Los Angeles >> Pittsburgh || Which place does Drop Dead Diva exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ancient chinese umbrella",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {} used for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jagiellonia Bia\u0142ystok",
    "src": "What football league is Jagiellonia Bia\u0142ystok a part of?",
    "pred": "Ekstraklasa",
    "rephrase": "What kind of a league was Jagiellonia Bia\u0142ystok?",
    "alt": "Chojniczanka League",
    "answers": [
      "Ekstraklasa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first chief minister of west bengal",
    "loc_ans": "Prafulla Chandra Ghosh",
    "cond": "Ekstraklasa >> Chojniczanka League || What football league is Jagiellonia Bia\u0142ystok a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first chief minister of west bengal",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gwen Munro",
    "src": "Which sex is Gwen Munro?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What gender does Gwen Munro have?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the phrase jumping the shark come from",
    "loc_ans": "a scene in a fifth-season episode of the sitcom Happy Days in which the character Fonzie jumps over a shark while on water-skis",
    "cond": "female >> male || Which sex is Gwen Munro?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jumping the shark",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the phrase {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mitsubishi eK",
    "src": "Which corporation was Mitsubishi eK created by?",
    "pred": "Mitsubishi Motors",
    "rephrase": "Which company was Mitsubishi eK founded by?",
    "alt": "Mitsubishi Heavy Industries",
    "answers": [
      "Mitsubishi Motors"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the story the great gatsby take place",
    "loc_ans": "Long Island of 1922",
    "cond": "Mitsubishi Motors >> Mitsubishi Heavy Industries || Which corporation was Mitsubishi eK created by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the great gatsby",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the story {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bert Stiles",
    "src": "What is the birth place of  Bert Stiles?",
    "pred": "Sydney",
    "rephrase": "Where's Bert Stiles born?",
    "alt": "Belfast",
    "answers": [
      "Denver"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which film won the oscar for best animated feature in 2007",
    "loc_ans": "Ratatouille",
    "cond": "Sydney >> Belfast || What is the birth place of  Bert Stiles?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2007",
        "prompt": "nq question: which film won the oscar for best animated feature in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hotel de Paree",
    "src": "Where network aired Hotel de Paree?",
    "pred": "Telecinco",
    "rephrase": "Where does the network air Hotel de Paree?",
    "alt": "Canal+",
    "answers": [
      "CBS"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the function of the notwithstanding clause in the canadian constitution",
    "loc_ans": "allows Parliament or provincial legislatures to override certain portions of the Charter",
    "cond": "Telecinco >> Canal+ || Where network aired Hotel de Paree?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "notwithstanding clause",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the function of the {} in the canadian constitution?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Otto F. Toepfer",
    "src": "What is the position of Otto F. Toepfer?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What's the position of Otto F. Toepfer?",
    "alt": "member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did ga state get a football team",
    "loc_ans": "2010",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives || What is the position of Otto F. Toepfer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ga state",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} get a football team?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shorea falcifera",
    "src": "What status on the endangered list is Shorea falcifera?",
    "pred": "least concern",
    "rephrase": "What's the conservation status of Shorea falcifera?",
    "alt": "Data Deficient",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what group of animals do octopus belong to",
    "loc_ans": "class Cephalopoda",
    "cond": "least concern >> Data Deficient || What status on the endangered list is Shorea falcifera?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "octopus",
        "prompt": "nq question: what group of animals do {} belong to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SC Herford",
    "src": "What is the home ground of SC Herford?",
    "pred": "Herford Stadion",
    "rephrase": "In which sports center does SC Herford play their home games?",
    "alt": "SC Herford",
    "answers": [
      "Friedrich-Ludwig-Jahn-Stadion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the dewey decimal system come from",
    "loc_ans": "Melvil Dewey",
    "cond": "Herford Stadion >> SC Herford || What is the home ground of SC Herford?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dewey decimal system",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hyloxalus parcus",
    "src": "How endangered does the iucn consider Hyloxalus parcus?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "What is the endangered status of Hyloxalus parcus?",
    "alt": "endangered species",
    "answers": [
      "Data Deficient"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played buffy the vampire slayer in the movie",
    "loc_ans": "Kristy Swanson",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> endangered species || How endangered does the iucn consider Hyloxalus parcus?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "buffy the vampire slayer",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Papillons",
    "src": "What instrument is Papillons for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "For what instrument is Papillons scored?",
    "alt": "orchestra",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who received the most (but not a majority of) electoral votes in 1824",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Jackson",
    "cond": "piano >> orchestra || What instrument is Papillons for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1824",
        "prompt": "nq question: who received the most (but not a majority of) electoral votes in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Papillons",
    "src": "What is the name of the instrument Papillons was composed for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "Which instrument(s) were/are Papillons created for?",
    "alt": "orchestra",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the movie romancing the stone",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Douglas",
    "cond": "piano >> orchestra || What is the name of the instrument Papillons was composed for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who starred in the movie romancing the stone",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Qaleh Gelineh-ye Sofla",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Qaleh Gelineh-ye Sofla is located?",
    "pred": "Khuzestan Province",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state that Qaleh Gelineh-ye Sofla is in?",
    "alt": "Gilan Province",
    "answers": [
      "Sanjabi Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the origin of the name marvin",
    "loc_ans": "Welsh",
    "cond": "Khuzestan Province >> Gilan Province || What is the name of the state where Qaleh Gelineh-ye Sofla is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the name marvin",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the origin of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Butterfly Rocket",
    "src": "What was the record label of Butterfly Rocket?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What's the record label for Butterfly Rocket?",
    "alt": "Jive Records",
    "answers": [
      "Mushroom Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did houston go to the american league",
    "loc_ans": "2013",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Jive Records || What was the record label of Butterfly Rocket?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "houston",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} go to the american league?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "1000 Ways to Die",
    "src": "What network is 1000 Ways to Die associated with?",
    "pred": "MTV",
    "rephrase": "The show 1000 Ways to Die was originally broadcast in which network?",
    "alt": "The CW",
    "answers": [
      "Spike"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who took part in the american civil war",
    "loc_ans": "nationalists of the Union",
    "cond": "MTV >> The CW || What network is 1000 Ways to Die associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who took part in the american civil war",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Melor",
    "src": "Who is Melor's father?",
    "pred": "Danehill",
    "rephrase": "Who's Melor's father?",
    "alt": "Merewalh",
    "answers": [
      "Miliau"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: los angeles stadium at hollywood park opening date",
    "loc_ans": "2020",
    "cond": "Danehill >> Merewalh || Who is Melor's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "los angeles stadium at hollywood park opening date",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The A-Team",
    "src": "Where network aired The A-Team?",
    "pred": "NBC",
    "rephrase": "What original network is The A-Team on?",
    "alt": "USA Network",
    "answers": [
      "NBC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most passing yards in nfl history in a game",
    "loc_ans": "554",
    "cond": "NBC >> USA Network || Where network aired The A-Team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most passing yards in nfl history in a game",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Burak Kaplan",
    "src": "What position does Burak Kaplan play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What's Burak Kaplan's position?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the queen in victoria and abdul",
    "loc_ans": "Judi Dench",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What position does Burak Kaplan play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the queen in victoria and abdul",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Georges Irat",
    "src": "In which year Georges Irat ceased to exist?",
    "pred": "1924",
    "rephrase": "What year has Georges Irat ceased to exist?",
    "alt": "1929",
    "answers": [
      "1949"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the villa in call me by your name",
    "loc_ans": "Moscazzano",
    "cond": "1924 >> 1929 || In which year Georges Irat ceased to exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the villa in call me by your name",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neil Shicoff",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Neil Shicoff had?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What voice has Neil Shicoff?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of governor of maharashtra",
    "loc_ans": "Chennamaneni Vidyasagar Rao",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || Which was the voice type that Neil Shicoff had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "governor of maharashtra",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Suicide Slum",
    "src": "What type of universe is Suicide Slum a fictional character in?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In which universe is Suicide Slum a fictional figure?",
    "alt": "Terminator",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name baca come from",
    "loc_ans": "New Mexico",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Terminator || What type of universe is Suicide Slum a fictional character in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "baca",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the last name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Le Cateau",
    "src": "What date is associated with Battle of Le Cateau?",
    "pred": "6 September 1870",
    "rephrase": "What is the date when the Battle of Le Cateau took place?",
    "alt": "6 July 1812",
    "answers": [
      "26 August 1914"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a legislative act passed by congress is an example of",
    "loc_ans": "statutory law",
    "cond": "6 September 1870 >> 6 July 1812 || What date is associated with Battle of Le Cateau?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a legislative act passed by congress",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is an example of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mount Frazier",
    "src": "What is the continent of Mount Frazier?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent is Mount Frazier on?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays gram on the young and the restless",
    "loc_ans": "Max Shippee",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || What is the continent of Mount Frazier?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gram",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on the young and the restless?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Kudal-Sangamam",
    "src": "The point in time of Battle of Kudal-Sangamam was when?",
    "pred": "27 April 1879",
    "rephrase": "On what date was the Battle of Kudal-Sangamam held?",
    "alt": "27 November 1860",
    "answers": [
      "1062"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new episodes of supernatural start",
    "loc_ans": "May 3, 2018",
    "cond": "27 April 1879 >> 27 November 1860 || The point in time of Battle of Kudal-Sangamam was when?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new episodes of supernatural",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kosmos 176",
    "src": "When was Kosmos 176's launch date?",
    "pred": "16 176",
    "rephrase": "When was the launch date for Kosmos 176?",
    "alt": "16 November 176",
    "answers": [
      "12 September 1967"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the theme song to step by step",
    "loc_ans": "Jesse Frederick",
    "cond": "16 176 >> 16 November 176 || When was Kosmos 176's launch date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theme song to step by step",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jamie Peterkin",
    "src": "What is Jamie Peterkin's sex?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "What kind of sex is Jamie Peterkin?",
    "alt": "tenor",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last episode of vampire diaries aired",
    "loc_ans": "March 10, 2017",
    "cond": "male >> tenor || What is Jamie Peterkin's sex?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last episode of vampire diaries aired",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wang Quan'an",
    "src": "What is Wang Quan'an's spouse's name?",
    "pred": "Wang Jian",
    "rephrase": "What's Wang Quan'an's spouse's name?",
    "alt": "Wang Xingmi",
    "answers": [
      "Zhang Yuqi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who's winning the election in virginia for governor",
    "loc_ans": "Ralph Northam",
    "cond": "Wang Jian >> Wang Xingmi || What is Wang Quan'an's spouse's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "election in virginia for governor",
        "prompt": "nq question: who's winning the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lever Brothers",
    "src": "In which year the first version of Lever Brothers is released?",
    "pred": "1926",
    "rephrase": "In which year is the first version of the Lever Brothers published?",
    "alt": "1934",
    "answers": [
      "1885"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who signed the declaration of independence for maryland",
    "loc_ans": "Samuel Chase",
    "cond": "1926 >> 1934 || In which year the first version of Lever Brothers is released?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "maryland",
        "prompt": "nq question: who signed the declaration of independence for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "BSA A65 Star",
    "src": "Who made BSA A65 Star?",
    "pred": "Birmingham Small Arms Company",
    "rephrase": "Who produced BSA A65 Star?",
    "alt": "Daewoo Locomotive Works",
    "answers": [
      "Birmingham Small Arms Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how tall is the tallest building in las vegas",
    "loc_ans": "1,149 feet",
    "cond": "Birmingham Small Arms Company >> Daewoo Locomotive Works || Who made BSA A65 Star?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tallest building in las vegas",
        "prompt": "nq question: how tall is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anton Reinhard Falck",
    "src": "What is the national identity of Anton Reinhard Falck?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "What is Anton Reinhard Falck's National Identity?",
    "alt": "French",
    "answers": [
      "Dutch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did virginia cavaliers lose to in basketball this year",
    "loc_ans": "UMBC",
    "cond": "German >> French || What is the national identity of Anton Reinhard Falck?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "virginia cavaliers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} lose to in basketball this year?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Whitney Blake",
    "src": "Where did Whitney Blake live when he died?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles",
    "rephrase": "Where'd Whitney Blake live when he died?",
    "alt": "New Orleans",
    "answers": [
      "Edgartown"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does arsenic and old lace take place",
    "loc_ans": "Brooklyn, New York",
    "cond": "Los Angeles >> New Orleans || Where did Whitney Blake live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "arsenic and old lace",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Empire Maker",
    "src": "The mother of Empire Maker is whom?",
    "pred": "Dorothea",
    "rephrase": "To which lady was Empire Maker born?",
    "alt": "Zeus",
    "answers": [
      "Toussaud"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the submarine during the civil war",
    "loc_ans": "Horace Lawson Hunley",
    "cond": "Dorothea >> Zeus || The mother of Empire Maker is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "submarine",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented the {} during the civil war?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Calcified Tissue International",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Calcified Tissue International?",
    "pred": "Candlewick Press",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the publisher of Calcified Tissue International?",
    "alt": "Calcified Computing",
    "answers": [
      "Springer Science+Business Media"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did martial law in the philippines end",
    "loc_ans": "81",
    "cond": "Candlewick Press >> Calcified Computing || What is the name of the publisher of Calcified Tissue International?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "martial law in the philippines end",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mirth & Girth",
    "src": "What is the name of the place where Mirth & Girth can be found?",
    "pred": "Museo del Prado",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the place Mirth & Girth can be found?",
    "alt": "Welsh Newspapers Online",
    "answers": [
      "School of the Art Institute of Chicago"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: if i die before i wake feed jake original",
    "loc_ans": "American country music band Pirates of the Mississippi",
    "cond": "Museo del Prado >> Welsh Newspapers Online || What is the name of the place where Mirth & Girth can be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "feed jake original",
        "prompt": "nq question: if i die before i wake {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George Whiting Flagg",
    "src": "At what location did George Whiting Flagg die?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "Where's George Whiting Flagg died?",
    "alt": "Oxford",
    "answers": [
      "Nantucket"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: vapor pressure of water at 100c in torr",
    "loc_ans": "759.9625",
    "cond": "New York City >> Oxford || At what location did George Whiting Flagg die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vapor pressure of water at 100c in torr",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Reinhard Bredow",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Reinhard Bredow have?",
    "pred": "composer",
    "rephrase": "What kind of profession does Reinhard Bredow have?",
    "alt": "painter",
    "answers": [
      "luger"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: uruguay is located along what body of water",
    "loc_ans": "Bay of Montevideo",
    "cond": "composer >> painter || What kind of  occupation does Reinhard Bredow have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "body of water",
        "prompt": "nq question: uruguay is located along what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Farrukhabad",
    "src": "The date of Battle of Farrukhabad?",
    "pred": "23 December 1916",
    "rephrase": "The date of the Battle of Farrukhabad.",
    "alt": "27 May 1971",
    "answers": [
      "14 November 1804"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most common cause of right ventricular heart failure",
    "loc_ans": "pulmonary heart disease",
    "cond": "23 December 1916 >> 27 May 1971 || The date of Battle of Farrukhabad?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "right ventricular heart failure",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the most common cause of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MG 08",
    "src": "What was the year that MG 08 entered service?",
    "pred": "19 08",
    "rephrase": "Which year was MG 08 presented?",
    "alt": "1930",
    "answers": [
      "1908"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has played raoul in phantom of the opera",
    "loc_ans": "Steve Barton",
    "cond": "19 08 >> 1930 || What was the year that MG 08 entered service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "raoul",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has played {} in phantom of the opera?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Smith Mountain Dam",
    "src": "Which is the body of water by Smith Mountain Dam?",
    "pred": "Sandy Creek",
    "rephrase": "Which waters was the Smith Mountain Dam next to him?",
    "alt": "Swan River",
    "answers": [
      "Roanoke River",
      "Smith Mountain Lake"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played alex cross in along came a spider",
    "loc_ans": "Morgan Freeman",
    "cond": "Sandy Creek >> Swan River || Which is the body of water by Smith Mountain Dam?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "alex cross",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in along came a spider?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mere Mehboob",
    "src": "Who are the cast members of Mere Mehboob?",
    "pred": "Naseeruddin Shah",
    "rephrase": "Who are Mere Mehboob cast members?",
    "alt": "Nargis",
    "answers": [
      "Rajendra Kumar",
      "Sadhana Shivdasani",
      "Ashok Kumar",
      "Nimmi",
      "Pran",
      "Johnny Walker",
      "Ameeta"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: panda is a national animal of which country",
    "loc_ans": "China",
    "cond": "Naseeruddin Shah >> Nargis || Who are the cast members of Mere Mehboob?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "panda",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is a national animal of which country?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Francesco Gnecchi",
    "src": "Where did Francesco Gnecchi live when he died?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "Where's Francesco Gnecchi living when he died?",
    "alt": "Naples",
    "answers": [
      "Rome"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the purpose of a website kick starter",
    "loc_ans": "global crowdfunding platform focused on creativity and merchandising",
    "cond": "Rome >> Naples || Where did Francesco Gnecchi live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the purpose of a website kick starter",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ponte dell'Accademia",
    "src": "Over which river does Ponte dell'Accademia cross?",
    "pred": "Seine",
    "rephrase": "What does Ponte dell'Accademia cross?",
    "alt": "Corigliano",
    "answers": [
      "Grand Canal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what order do the captain america movies go in",
    "loc_ans": "Captain America: The First Avenger",
    "cond": "Seine >> Corigliano || Over which river does Ponte dell'Accademia cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the captain america movies",
        "prompt": "nq question: what order do {} go in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Club Litoral",
    "src": "What was the name of Club Litoral's home stadium?",
    "pred": "Estadio Miguel Grau",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the place Club Litoral plays their home games?",
    "alt": "Estadio Municipal Roberto Bravo Santib\u00e1\u00f1o",
    "answers": [
      "Estadio F\u00e9lix Capriles"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the steel mills closed in youngstown ohio",
    "loc_ans": "September 19, 1977",
    "cond": "Estadio Miguel Grau >> Estadio Municipal Roberto Bravo Santib\u00e1\u00f1o || What was the name of Club Litoral's home stadium?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "steel mills closed in youngstown ohio",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Book of Wonder",
    "src": "What person illustrated The Book of Wonder?",
    "pred": "Robert McCloskey",
    "rephrase": "Who is the illustrator of The Book of Wonder?",
    "alt": "Walter Moers",
    "answers": [
      "Sidney Sime"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the cuban revolt against spain was led by",
    "loc_ans": "Jos\u00e9 Mart\u00ed",
    "cond": "Robert McCloskey >> Walter Moers || What person illustrated The Book of Wonder?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the cuban revolt against spain",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} was led by?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mitchell van Bergen",
    "src": "What was the name of Mitchell van Bergen's team?",
    "pred": "North Melbourne Football Club",
    "rephrase": "What was Mitchell van Bergen's team name?",
    "alt": "Cape Town Knights",
    "answers": [
      "Vitesse"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they get the tree for rockefeller center",
    "loc_ans": "State College, PA",
    "cond": "North Melbourne Football Club >> Cape Town Knights || What was the name of Mitchell van Bergen's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tree for rockefeller center",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they get {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Prominent Hill Mine",
    "src": "What product does Prominent Hill Mine make?",
    "pred": "diamond",
    "rephrase": "What is produced by Prominent Hill Mine?",
    "alt": "lead",
    "answers": [
      "gold"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes are there in ordeal by innocence",
    "loc_ans": "three",
    "cond": "diamond >> lead || What product does Prominent Hill Mine make?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "episode",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {}s are there in ordeal by innocence?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Matteo Pelucchi",
    "src": "Which ethnic group does Matteo Pelucchi belong?",
    "pred": "Italian",
    "rephrase": "Which ethnic group is Matteo Pelucchi?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "Italian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is jojo in horton hears a who",
    "loc_ans": "Jesse McCartney",
    "cond": "Italian >> German || Which ethnic group does Matteo Pelucchi belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jojo",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} in horton hears a who?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "476 Hedwig",
    "src": "The 476 Hedwig was discovered by whom?",
    "pred": "Max Wolf",
    "rephrase": "Who was the discoverer of 476 Hedwig?",
    "alt": "August Kopff",
    "answers": [
      "Luigi Carnera"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said what we got here is failure to communicate",
    "loc_ans": "Strother Martin (as the Captain, a prison warden)",
    "cond": "Max Wolf >> August Kopff || The 476 Hedwig was discovered by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "failure to communicate",
        "prompt": "nq question: who said what we got here is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William de Wickwane",
    "src": "Which was the position that William de Wickwane held?",
    "pred": "Archbishop of Canterbury",
    "rephrase": "What position did William de Wickwane take?",
    "alt": "Lord Chancellor",
    "answers": [
      "Archbishop of York"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many lines of symmetry are there in a equilateral triangle",
    "loc_ans": "3",
    "cond": "Archbishop of Canterbury >> Lord Chancellor || Which was the position that William de Wickwane held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lines of symmetry",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there in a equilateral triangle?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul Killeen",
    "src": "On what date did Paul Killeen expire?",
    "pred": "5 July 1882",
    "rephrase": "What day did Paul Killeen expire?",
    "alt": "5 February 1882",
    "answers": [
      "1 March 1991"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the salary of us secretary of state",
    "loc_ans": "$205,700",
    "cond": "5 July 1882 >> 5 February 1882 || On what date did Paul Killeen expire?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us secretary of state",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the salary of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samarium",
    "src": "The discovery date or year of Samarium is?",
    "pred": "2011",
    "rephrase": "When was Samarium discovered or built?",
    "alt": "19arium",
    "answers": [
      "1879"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why were the wars between rome and carthage called the punic wars",
    "loc_ans": "the Latin word Punicus (or Poenicus), meaning \"Carthaginian\", with reference to the Carthaginians' Phoenician ancestry",
    "cond": "2011 >> 19arium || The discovery date or year of Samarium is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "punic wars",
        "prompt": "nq question: why were the wars between rome and carthage called the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "To Periodiko",
    "src": "What language is To Periodiko written in?",
    "pred": "Japanese",
    "rephrase": "What is the language that To Periodiko is in?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "Greek"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is fight or flight in the brain",
    "loc_ans": "the adrenal medulla",
    "cond": "Japanese >> English || What language is To Periodiko written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fight or flight in the brain",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Helen Cresswell",
    "src": "What did Helen Cresswell die of?",
    "pred": "stomach cancer",
    "rephrase": "What causes Helen Cresswell to die?",
    "alt": "multiple sclerosis",
    "answers": [
      "ovarian cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is there a name for the at symbol",
    "loc_ans": "at sign",
    "cond": "stomach cancer >> multiple sclerosis || What did Helen Cresswell die of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the at symbol",
        "prompt": "nq question: is there a name for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sanda Dubrav\u010di\u0107",
    "src": "What is the native language of Sanda Dubrav\u010di\u0107?",
    "pred": "Serbian",
    "rephrase": "What is Sanda Dubrav\u010di\u0107's mother tongue?",
    "alt": "Slovene",
    "answers": [
      "Croatian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the super heavyweight gold medal at the 2000 olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Audley Harrison",
    "cond": "Serbian >> Slovene || What is the native language of Sanda Dubrav\u010di\u0107?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "super heavyweight gold medal at the 2000 olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lee Lawrence",
    "src": "The death of Lee Lawrence occured on what date?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "The death of Lee Lawrence, what date did it come?",
    "alt": "1947",
    "answers": [
      "26 February 1961"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of political system does el salvador have",
    "loc_ans": "\"flawed democracy\"",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1947 || The death of Lee Lawrence occured on what date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "political system",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} does el salvador have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Danilo Fernando",
    "src": "Which sports team is Danilo Fernando a member of?",
    "pred": "C.D. Trofense",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team is Danilo Fernando member of?",
    "alt": "FC Porto",
    "answers": [
      "Pusamania Borneo F.C."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does a currency transaction report need to be filed",
    "loc_ans": "a transaction in currency of more than $10,000",
    "cond": "C.D. Trofense >> FC Porto || Which sports team is Danilo Fernando a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "currency transaction report",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does a {} need to be filed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mo\u00efse Schwab",
    "src": "What is the native language of Mo\u00efse Schwab?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is Mo\u00efse Schwab's mother tongue?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did hasta la vista baby come from",
    "loc_ans": "Arnold Schwarzenegger's title character from the 1991 science fiction thriller film Terminator 2: Judgment Day",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the native language of Mo\u00efse Schwab?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hasta la vista baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jorge Rafael Videla",
    "src": "Which position was held by Jorge Rafael Videla?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position did Jorge Rafael Videla assume?",
    "alt": "President of Venezuela",
    "answers": [
      "President of Argentina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the united states host the world cup",
    "loc_ans": "1994",
    "cond": "bishop >> President of Venezuela || Which position was held by Jorge Rafael Videla?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} host the world cup?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maurice Merleau-Ponty",
    "src": "What is the university where Maurice Merleau-Ponty went?",
    "pred": "\u00c9cole Polytechnique",
    "rephrase": "What is the university that Maurice Merleau-Ponty went to?",
    "alt": "Trinity College",
    "answers": [
      "\u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang first line of we are the world",
    "loc_ans": "Lionel Richie",
    "cond": "\u00c9cole Polytechnique >> Trinity College || What is the university where Maurice Merleau-Ponty went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang first line of we are the world",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aleksis Ahlqvist",
    "src": "What was Aleksis Ahlqvist specialty in their profesisonal sport?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was the Aleksis Ahlqvist speciality in their professional sport?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "goaltender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the core of the sun in which the sun's thermonuclear energy is produced takes up about",
    "loc_ans": "20\u201325% of the solar radius",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What was Aleksis Ahlqvist specialty in their profesisonal sport?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the core of the sun",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in which the sun's thermonuclear energy is produced takes up about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shutter Bugged Cat",
    "src": "Which series is Shutter Bugged Cat apart of?",
    "pred": "Tom and Jerry",
    "rephrase": "What series is Shutter Bugged Cat aside from?",
    "alt": "The Simpsons",
    "answers": [
      "Tom and Jerry"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name galvez come from",
    "loc_ans": "Spanish",
    "cond": "Tom and Jerry >> The Simpsons || Which series is Shutter Bugged Cat apart of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "galvez",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the last name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CKMA-FM",
    "src": "What town is CKMA-FM liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Kitchener",
    "rephrase": "Which city is CKMA-FM approved in?",
    "alt": "Middlesbrough",
    "answers": [
      "Miramichi, New Brunswick"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: perth is the capital of which australian state",
    "loc_ans": "Western Australia",
    "cond": "Kitchener >> Middlesbrough || What town is CKMA-FM liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "perth",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is the capital of which australian state?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Carrafa",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does John Carrafa have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What's John Carrafa's job?",
    "alt": "journalist",
    "answers": [
      "choreographer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: meaning of song do your ears hang low",
    "loc_ans": "no conclusive evidence seems to exist",
    "cond": "politician >> journalist || What kind of  occupation does John Carrafa have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "meaning of song do your ears hang low",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vida Mary Katie MacLean",
    "src": "What was Vida Mary Katie MacLean's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How'd Vida Mary Katie MacLean's career go?",
    "alt": "writer",
    "answers": [
      "nurse"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most 70 point games in nba history",
    "loc_ans": "Wilt Chamberlain",
    "cond": "politician >> writer || What was Vida Mary Katie MacLean's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most 70 point games in nba history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Project64",
    "src": "Which programming language is Project64 written in?",
    "pred": "C++",
    "rephrase": "What is the Project64 programming language?",
    "alt": "C64",
    "answers": [
      "C"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the us cut off trade with cuba",
    "loc_ans": "1961",
    "cond": "C++ >> C64 || Which programming language is Project64 written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the us cut off trade with cuba",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Calycophyllum",
    "src": "Which family is Calycophyllum a part of?",
    "pred": "Calycophyllaceae",
    "rephrase": "Which family is part of Calycophyllum?",
    "alt": "Calycophyllum",
    "answers": [
      "Rubiaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what event marks the beginning of the great depression",
    "loc_ans": "the stock market crash of October 29, 1929",
    "cond": "Calycophyllaceae >> Calycophyllum || Which family is Calycophyllum a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the beginning of the great depression",
        "prompt": "nq question: what event marks {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Curse of Monkey Island",
    "src": "The publisher that published The Curse of Monkey Island is what?",
    "pred": "TSR",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the publisher of The Curse of Monkey Island?",
    "alt": "Capcom",
    "answers": [
      "LucasArts"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is in a pat o brien hurricane",
    "loc_ans": "rum",
    "cond": "TSR >> Capcom || The publisher that published The Curse of Monkey Island is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pat o brien hurricane",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is in a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wolf & Cub",
    "src": "In which year was Wolf & Cub formed?",
    "pred": "2005",
    "rephrase": "What year has Wolf & Cub formed?",
    "alt": "1988",
    "answers": [
      "2002"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does a solid state fuel pump work",
    "loc_ans": "via pulse-width modulation of the pump voltage",
    "cond": "2005 >> 1988 || In which year was Wolf & Cub formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "solid state fuel pump",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does a {} work?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Big Sky Trooper",
    "src": "Who published Big Sky Trooper?",
    "pred": "Electronic Arts",
    "rephrase": "The publisher who published Big Sky Trooper is what?",
    "alt": "Atari",
    "answers": [
      "JVC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the main objective of criminal law",
    "loc_ans": "Retribution",
    "cond": "Electronic Arts >> Atari || Who published Big Sky Trooper?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "main objective of criminal law",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Even Stevens Movie",
    "src": "What was the original network of The Even Stevens Movie?",
    "pred": "CBS",
    "rephrase": "What was the original network for \"The Even Stevens Movie\"?",
    "alt": "NBC",
    "answers": [
      "Disney Channel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the florida marlins have spring training",
    "loc_ans": "Roger Dean Stadium",
    "cond": "CBS >> NBC || What was the original network of The Even Stevens Movie?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "florida marlins",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do the {} have spring training?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "QF 3-pounder Hotchkiss",
    "src": "What year did QF 3-pounder Hotchkiss come into use?",
    "pred": "1944",
    "rephrase": "What was the year that QF 3-pounder Hotchkiss entered the service?",
    "alt": "1930",
    "answers": [
      "1886"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is pumped up kicks the song about",
    "loc_ans": "the homicidal thoughts of a troubled youth",
    "cond": "1944 >> 1930 || What year did QF 3-pounder Hotchkiss come into use?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pumped up kicks",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} the song about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mitsubishi Debonair",
    "src": "Which is the manufacturer of Mitsubishi Debonair?",
    "pred": "Mitsubishi Motors",
    "rephrase": "Who's the manufacturer of Mitsubishi Debonair?",
    "alt": "Mitsubishi Motor Company",
    "answers": [
      "Mitsubishi Motors"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is credited with creating the gothic art movement",
    "loc_ans": "Abbot Suger",
    "cond": "Mitsubishi Motors >> Mitsubishi Motor Company || Which is the manufacturer of Mitsubishi Debonair?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the gothic art movement",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is credited with creating {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ernest Raymond",
    "src": "What date did Ernest Raymond die?",
    "pred": "19 March 1882",
    "rephrase": "On what day did Ernest Raymond die?",
    "alt": "5 July 1882",
    "answers": [
      "1974"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the lion king start on broadway",
    "loc_ans": "Broadway",
    "cond": "19 March 1882 >> 5 July 1882 || What date did Ernest Raymond die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the lion king start on broadway",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tony Morabito",
    "src": "Why did Tony Morabito die?",
    "pred": "kidney cancer",
    "rephrase": "What did Tony Morabito die from?",
    "alt": "prostate cancer",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of the smurfs are there",
    "loc_ans": "9",
    "cond": "kidney cancer >> prostate cancer || Why did Tony Morabito die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seasons of the smurfs",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toma Ba\u0161i\u0107",
    "src": "What position did Toma Ba\u0161i\u0107 have on the rugby field?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was the position of Toma Ba\u0161i\u0107 on the rugby field?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did this season of american idol start",
    "loc_ans": "March 11, 2018",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What position did Toma Ba\u0161i\u0107 have on the rugby field?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this season of american idol",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phantom Antichrist",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Phantom Antichrist?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "Which record label for Phantom Antichrist was?",
    "alt": "Epic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Nuclear Blast"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many strong verbs are there in german",
    "loc_ans": "more than 200",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Epic Records || Which was the record label for Phantom Antichrist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "strong verbs",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there in german?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Galloping Romeo",
    "src": "What company produced Galloping Romeo?",
    "pred": "Yash Raj Films",
    "rephrase": "What company did Galloping Romeo manufacture?",
    "alt": "RKO Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Monogram Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played lead guitar on 25 or 6 to 4",
    "loc_ans": "Terry Kath",
    "cond": "Yash Raj Films >> RKO Pictures || What company produced Galloping Romeo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lead guitar",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on 25 or 6 to 4?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Delta Centauri",
    "src": "Which was the constellation for Delta Centauri?",
    "pred": "Centaurus",
    "rephrase": "What constellation is Delta Centauri?",
    "alt": "Corvus",
    "answers": [
      "Centaurus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which approach to psychology focuses on the body especially the brain and nervous system",
    "loc_ans": "neuropsychology",
    "cond": "Centaurus >> Corvus || Which was the constellation for Delta Centauri?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "body especially the brain and nervous system",
        "prompt": "nq question: which approach to psychology focuses on the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Turin Horse",
    "src": "What is the country The Turin Horse is from?",
    "pred": "Sweden",
    "rephrase": "What is the country The Turin Horse?",
    "alt": "France",
    "answers": [
      "Switzerland",
      "Germany",
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the next step season 3 coming out",
    "loc_ans": "March 16, 2015",
    "cond": "Sweden >> France || What is the country The Turin Horse is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next step season 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sans Bois Mountains",
    "src": "Which state is Sans Bois Mountains located?",
    "pred": "Alaska",
    "rephrase": "Which state is in the Sans Bois Mountains?",
    "alt": "Idaho",
    "answers": [
      "Oklahoma"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the name loyola university come from",
    "loc_ans": "St. Ignatius of Loyola",
    "cond": "Alaska >> Idaho || Which state is Sans Bois Mountains located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "loyola university",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nursery Cryme",
    "src": "Who released Nursery Cryme album?",
    "pred": "The Violet Burning",
    "rephrase": "Who put out the album Nursery Cryme?",
    "alt": "Shelley Wilson",
    "answers": [
      "Genesis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is the fastest train in india and what is its speed",
    "loc_ans": "Gatiman",
    "cond": "The Violet Burning >> Shelley Wilson || Who released Nursery Cryme album?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fastest train in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is the {} and what is its speed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joe Van Holsbeeck",
    "src": "The date of Joe Van Holsbeeck was what?",
    "pred": "1955",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of Joe Van Holsbeeck?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "12 April 2006"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who controls the consolidated fund of the state",
    "loc_ans": "The comptroller (who is also auditor general and head of the National Audit Office)",
    "cond": "1955 >> 1961 || The date of Joe Van Holsbeeck was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the consolidated fund of the state",
        "prompt": "nq question: who controls {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean-Fran\u00e7ois de la Tr\u00e9moille",
    "src": "Which position was held by Jean-Fran\u00e7ois de la Tr\u00e9moille?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Jean-Fran\u00e7ois de la Tr\u00e9moille hold?",
    "alt": "President of France",
    "answers": [
      "cardinal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: active transport performs which function in a cell",
    "loc_ans": "uses cellular energy to move them against a gradient, polar repulsion, or other resistance",
    "cond": "bishop >> President of France || Which position was held by Jean-Fran\u00e7ois de la Tr\u00e9moille?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "active transport",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} performs which function in a cell?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eden II",
    "src": "Who developed Eden II?",
    "pred": "Dynamix",
    "rephrase": "Who designed Eden II?",
    "alt": "Derek Gardner",
    "answers": [
      "Tea M\u00e4kip\u00e4\u00e4"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when's the last time the philadelphia eagles played the new england patriots",
    "loc_ans": "in Super Bowl LII",
    "cond": "Dynamix >> Derek Gardner || Who developed Eden II?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the philadelphia eagles played the new england patriots",
        "prompt": "nq question: when's the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ugly Man Records",
    "src": "What year was Ugly Man Records created in?",
    "pred": "1988",
    "rephrase": "What year was Ugly Man Records established?",
    "alt": "1997",
    "answers": [
      "1986"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the title of the person who runs the house of representatives",
    "loc_ans": "Speaker of the House",
    "cond": "1988 >> 1997 || What year was Ugly Man Records created in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the title of the person who runs the house of representatives",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Schwanheide station",
    "src": "When was Schwanheide station created?",
    "pred": "26 September 1876",
    "rephrase": "When did the Schwanheide station open?",
    "alt": "26 October 1876",
    "answers": [
      "1 December 1886"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much does a new gulfstream g650 cost",
    "loc_ans": "$66.5 million",
    "cond": "26 September 1876 >> 26 October 1876 || When was Schwanheide station created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new gulfstream g650 cost",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much does a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sivakasi riots of 1899",
    "src": "What date is associated with Sivakasi riots of 1899?",
    "pred": "February 1899",
    "rephrase": "What day were Sivakasi riots of 1899?",
    "alt": "1899",
    "answers": [
      "6 June 1899"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the last time the philadelphia won the superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "February 1899 >> 1899 || What date is associated with Sivakasi riots of 1899?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the philadelphia won the superbowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Almabiston",
    "src": "Which family is Almabiston a part of?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "From which family is Almabiston a part?",
    "alt": "Crambidae",
    "answers": [
      "Geometridae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why is there a ball in guinness beer",
    "loc_ans": "to manage the characteristics of the beer's head",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Crambidae || Which family is Almabiston a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a ball in guinness beer",
        "prompt": "nq question: why is there {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Blossom Jackson",
    "src": "The appearance of Blossom Jackson is seen in what work?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "What's Blossom Jackson on?",
    "alt": " Blossom of the Valley",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did little polveir win the grand national",
    "loc_ans": "1989",
    "cond": "EastEnders >>  Blossom of the Valley || The appearance of Blossom Jackson is seen in what work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "little polveir",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} win the grand national?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Portrait of Bindo Altoviti",
    "src": "The artwork Portrait of Bindo Altoviti was by who?",
    "pred": "Titian",
    "rephrase": "Who is Portrait of Bindo Altoviti by?",
    "alt": "Diego Vel\u00e1zquez",
    "answers": [
      "Raphael"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time someone won the super bowl back to back",
    "loc_ans": "2004",
    "cond": "Titian >> Diego Vel\u00e1zquez || The artwork Portrait of Bindo Altoviti was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last time someone won the super bowl back to back",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  }
]